<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<helpSystem>
<module name="My Home Page" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>This is the "Home Page". The Top set of Tabs shows the individual modules that you can access. The second row are the functions available to you in this module.&#13;
If you are looking for a particular module or function you have seen during training or on someone else's machine, and it's NOT there it probably means that you don't have permission for that module or function.&#13;
Permissions within the system are assigned to Roles and then Users are assigned to Roles by the System Administrator.&#13;
If you are looking for a module and can't find it, it generally means you don&#146;t have permission to it.&#13;
&#13;
</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Home Page system has six main features.&#13;
&#13;
Welcome: This is the welcome page. This displays the different modules present in the system, based on their titles and the corresponding security for the title. For a particular user all the scheduled actions for the next seven days are displayed in this page.&#13;
&#13;
Mailbox: The Message System is designed to support INTERNAL business messaging needs and to prepare OUTGOING emails to addresses who are already in the system. Messaging is NOT a normal email replacement. It will not send email to address assigned "on-the-fly" and it will not receive OUTSIDE email&#13;
&#13;
Tasks: The Task System is designed to create and assign tasks. Tasks created can be assigned to the owner/creator of the task or an employee working in the system. This page lists the tasks present along with their priorities, their due dates and age.&#13;
&#13;
Action Lists: The Action List System is designed to create new Action Lists and assign contacts to the Action Lists created. For each of the contacts in a List, you can add a call, opportunity, ticket, task or send a message, which would correspondingly show up in their respective tabs. For example, adding a ticket to the contact would be reflected in the Ticket tab.&#13;
&#13;
Re-assignments: A user can reassign data from one employee to another employee working under him. The data can be of different types related to accounts, contacts opportunities, activities, tickets etc, which the newly reassigned employee could view in his schedule.&#13;
&#13;
Settings: This is the personal settings system page, where in you can modify/update the information about yourself, your location and also change your password to the system </detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyCFS.do</action>
<section>Home</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>You are looking at Home Page view, which has a dashboard view of all your assigned tasks, tickets, assignments, calls you have to make and accounts, which need attention. This view is based on a time selected from the calendar; by default it shows the schedule for the next seven days. You can optionally view the calendar of those below you.&#13;
 &#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the accounts that need attention</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can make calls with the contact information readily accessible</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the tasks assigned to you</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the tickets assigned to you</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>On this QA page, rename NOTES to QA NOTES and move them to the bottom of the QA screen</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>QA breaks on adding a note and marking it as complete</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Opportunity Alert needs to have a link to the opportunity header and/or contact</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Should expired users be shown in the hierarchy as a filter(ideally there can be no alerts for expired users)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FAQ: Account alerts show up only for the Accounts owned by you</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Updating a task in the pop-up window says "requested page not found"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>IE: On 5.0 a message appears asking to display non-secure items... can that go away?</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>The line breaks in the edit window do not appear in the intro text details</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Contact Details popup: Rename Opportunity shows the modules menu</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Contact Details pop up : Add a component under Opportunities gives a "Page Not Found"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Contact Details pop up: Modify call form does not show one of the "Cancel" buttons</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Contact Details pop up call forward does not work. UPDATE: Removed forward utility from pop up contact details as the forward screens do not remember the sub menu</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Projects needs to go from the filters list</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Scheduled Actions filter needs to say "Opportunities" and not "Opportunity"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Update Contact Opportunity form does not show entries for drop down selections(lookups)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Not having access to Tasks raises a "Page Not Found" error instead of a "Permission Error"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Calendar does not take into account permissions, for example if tasks are disabled it still show tasks as a filter</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Call Alert  shows the title as "null" for contact calls</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>The QA page should POP to to when reqested</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>JAVASCRIPT: edit introduction(QA)-&gt;submit pops error - 'dosubmit.value not an object'</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>DISPLAY: DS21 and the User details overlap at times when you log in</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>JAVASCRIPT: right click on the links 'Help' and 'QA' and click on open in a new window pops and error 'object expected'</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Quick Actions-&gt;Add a Ticket-&gt; Add a new Ticket | Organization  [Select] -&gt; Add 'AmeriGroup'-&gt; This pops up an error stating "Expecting ')' " and another error saying 'Object Expected'.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>IE BUG: Quick Actions-&gt;Add a Ticket-&gt; Add a new Ticket | Organization [Select] -&gt; Contact [Create Contact] pops up an error stating 'Object Expected'.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>IE BUG: Quick Actions-&gt;Add a Ticket-&gt; Add a new Ticket | Organization [Select] -&gt; Contact  [Create New Contact] gives an error saying 'Object Expected'.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription> IE BUG: The cursor does not change to a hand when moved over the tabs 'My home page','General contacts' etc.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>DISPLAY:Adding an account, task, call, opputunity on the same date screws up the nice square arrangements of the calender on the left.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:In the Day View just next to Calender, the Accounts category repeats whenever you add a new account, instead of showing all the accounts under one category 'Account'. Also the number of items under a particular category displayed after the category name in '()' is not updated.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>LINK: Clicking on the 'Assigned Activities' link in my items menu takes you to the Project Management Tab! </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>LINK: The link 'Calls to make' under My Items menu, takes you to the home page and does not show up anything to add calls or edit the same.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>On updating a alert on a next or previous month, the view changes to that month</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:Call details are not displayed, though task description is(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>JS Error: Click on the Contact link for a scheduled Call .Go to the folders tab and create a record. When the "select" button is clicked under the Action column a Java script error occurs. It does not show the menu at all. Priority :High</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>JS Error:Clicking on the QA:module on any page and then clicking the edit link of "Brief Description" gives a  JS error.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>You can view your calendar and calendars of those who work for you</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips>
<tipDescription>Assign due dates for tasks so that you can be alerted</tipDescription>
</tips>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>Inbox</section>
<subSection/>
<title>My Mailbox </title>
<description>This is the  Message System.  &#13;
The  Message System is designed to support INTERNAL business messaging needs and to prepare OUTGOING emails to addresses who are already in the system. Messaging is NOT a normal email replacement.  It will not send email to address assigned "on-the-fly"  and it will not receive OUTSIDE email.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The select button can be used to view the details, reply, forward or delete a particular message.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new message</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the message would show the details of the message</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The drop down can be used to select the messages present in the inbox, sent messages or the archived ones</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Sort on one of the column headers by clicking on the column of your choice</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Message that should go to the outbox goes to the inbox too.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>CFSNoteDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>This page shows the  message details, shows who sent the mail, when it was received and also the text in the mail box.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can reply, archive, forward or delete each message by clicking the corresponding button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>No confirmation before deleting message</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>NewMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>New Message </title>
<description>Sending a email to the recipients present in the system</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A new message can be composed either to the contacts or the employees present in the recipients list. The options field can be checked to send a copy to the employees task list apart from sending the employee an email.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Send and Cancel button need to be there at the top also</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Contact pop up selector needs to have scrollbars on</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Cancel button always goes back to the list even if you came to this screen from the details screen</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: My Home Page-&gt;My Mailbox-&gt;New Message-&gt;[Add Recipients]-&gt;Now in the popup click 'Done' without selecting any contacts-&gt;Now click on Send. It says message sent to the following recipients, but there are no recipients since none were selected from the pop up list.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>DISPLAY : Recipient Field in the new message form does not have an indicator to indicate a mandatory field.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When two recipients are added, the first one from choosing among "all contacts" and the second from "Employees" and later when the first recipient is deleted, the second also gets deleted from the recipient list(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>DISPLAY: "Add Recipients" is a misnomer since it also allows chosen recipients to be deleted(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Deleting a recipient from the list should be allowed by choosing and then clicking the delete key(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG/USABILITY: Currently the message body is mandatory but the does not have a red star beside it. But, most mail applications do not have subject and message body as mandatory(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: when clicked on [Add Recipients], could the popup window show a list of only contacts who have email addresses specified. It as of now shows contacts with no email id specified and hence when a mail is sent, i get a feedback message saying email not sent since there is no email id specified.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>ReplyToMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Reply Message</title>
<description>This pages lets you reply to the email. You can also select the list of recipients for your email by clicking the Add Recipients link.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can send the email by clicking the send button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add to the list of recipients by using the link "Add Recipients"</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click the check box to send an Internet email to the recipients</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Type directly in the Body test field to modify the message</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Cannot reply to an inbox message, error displays with funny illegal address ``</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>SendMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>This page shows the list of recipients for whom your email has been sent to</description>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Message Details link  incorrectly takes you to the Mailbox</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: If an email is not being sent, just going to inbox, the recipient is not listed in the "message has been sent" table</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:do the following -  My Home Page &gt; My Mailbox &gt; New Message. Then click on [Add Recipients]. Now click on DONE without selecting any contacts. Now click on 'Send'. This pops-up and error message  </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>ForwardMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forward message</title>
<description>Each message can be forwarded to any number of recipients</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add the list of recipients by using the link "Add Recipients" and also click the check box which would send a email to the recipients </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can send the email by clicking the send button </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can edit the message by typing directly in the Body text area</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Pop Up for Add Recipients should pop to front</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>My Tasks </title>
<description>This is the Task System. &#13;
&#13;
The Task System is designed to create and assign tasks.  Tasks created can be assigned to the owner/creator of the task or an employee working in the system. This page lists the tasks present along with their priorities, their due dates and age.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add a quick task. This task would have just the description and whether the task is personal or not</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For each of the existing tasks, you can view, modify, forward or delete the tasks by clicking on the Action button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select to view your tasks or tasks assigned by you to others working under you. Each can be viewed in three different modes. i.e. the completed tasks, uncompleted tasks or both.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a detailed (advanced) task, where you can set up the priority, status, whether the task is shared or not, task assignment, give the estimated time and add some detailed notes for it.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Contact Link gives a exception when a ticket task is linked to a contact which does not have a owner</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USAGE : when I am adding a new Task, I am able to select the status complete. Is this the intended normal operation??</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:view tasks assigned by -&gt; click on one of the tasks -&gt; All the includes (menu, my items, recent items etc) disappear and only task details are shown. (In the same page and not a popup)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: The drop down to select between My Tasks and Assigned Tasks raises a javascript expression when the permission for Add, Edit and Delete are turned off. Browser: IE5.0</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section>New</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Advanced Task</title>
<description>Allows an advanced task to be created</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Link this task to a contact and when you look at the task list, there will be a link to the contact record next to the task, allowing you to go directly to the contact</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Filling in a Due Date will make ths task show up on that date in the Home Page calendar</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Making the task personal will hide it from your hierarchy</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign a task to people lower than you in your hierarchy</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Marking a task as complete will document the task as having been done, and immediately remove it from the Task List</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyTasksForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forwarding a Task </title>
<description>A task can be forwarded to any of the recipients. The recipients can be either the users of the system or any of the contacts not present in the system. Checking the options fields check box indicates that if the recipient is a user of the system, then a copy of the task is also send to the recipient's mailbox.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Allows you to forward a task to one or more users of the system. Checking the options fields check box indicates that if the recipient is a user of the system, then a copy of the task is send to the recipient's Internet email.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Subject line is mandatory</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add more text to the body of the message by typing directly in the Body text area</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>After forwarding a task, the screen goes over into My Mailbox for showing the confirmation message</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify task</title>
<description>Allows you to modify any infomation about a task</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Due dates will show on the Home Page calendar</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Completing a task will remove it from the task list</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign a task to someone lower than you in your heirarchy</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can Add or Change the contact that this task is linked to. When viewing the task, you will be able to view the contact information with one click.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyActionLists.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>My Action Lists </title>
<description>This is the Action List System. &#13;
&#13;
The Action List System is designed to create new Action Lists and assign contacts to the Action Lists created. For each of the contacts in a List, you can add a call, opportunity, ticket, task or send a message, which would correspondingly show up in their respective tabs. For example, adding a ticket to the contact would be reflected in the Ticket tab.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view all the in progress Action Lists, completed list or both together.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also keep track of the Progress of your contacts. The number of them Completed and the Total are shown in the Progress Columns.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new Action List with a description and status. You can select the contacts for this new Action List. For each of the contacts in the Action List, you can select a corresponding action with the Action Button: view details, modify contact, add contacts or delete the Action List.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>No permissions implemented for Action Lists UPDATE:  If user has only view permissions for action lists, clicking on a action contact should just pop up the details without the other tabs to prevent adding a action item</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyActionContacts.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Action Contacts</title>
<description>This page will list out all the contacts present for the particular contact list. This also shows the status of the call, opportunity, ticket, task, or the message associated with the contact. This also shows when the contact information was last updated.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the contact name will give you a pop up with more details about the contact and also about the related folders, calls, messages and opportunities.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add contacts to the list and also Modify the List using "Add Contacts to list" and "Modify List" respectively.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For the Action List you can also view all the in progress contacts, completed contacts or both.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For each of the contacts you can add a call, opportunity, ticket, task or send a message, which would correspondingly show up in their respective tabs. For example, adding a ticket to the contact would be reflected in the Ticket tab.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Add Task against a action contact throws a "Page Not Found"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"Send Message" does not send the message even when all the fields are filled in correctly</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>The history shows up correctly the first time under mozilla but not after that.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Added the image editor feature to "Send Message"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Trying to add a Call gives a Page Not Found</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Select menu does not show all icons</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When choosing "save" in the "add opportunity" window, the error "alertDate.value is not an object" pops up</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: If an action contact only has the company name, then the company name needs to be shown in the Name column</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Looking at an Action List threw an exception - Ticket Not Found</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyActionLists.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Action List</title>
<description>Allows you to add an action list. Basically, you describe the group of contacts you will add, then design a query to generate the group of contacts.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Select where the contacts will come from (General Contact, Account Contacts) in the From dropdown</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Enter some search text, depending on the Operator you chose.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choose an Operator base on the Field you chose.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choose one of the many Field Names on which to base your query.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can Add or Remove contacts manually with the Add/Remove Contacts link</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add your query with the Add button at the bottom of the query frame. You can have multipe queries that make up the criteria for a group. You will get the result of all the queries.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Save the Action List and generate the list of contacts by clicking the Save button at the bottom or top of the page.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyActionLists.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Action</title>
<description>The Action Lists details like the description and the status of the Action Lists can be modified.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can check the status checkbox to indicate that the New Action List is complete</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The details of the New Action List can be saved by clicking the save button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Modify Action displays only the action description</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Reassignments.do</action>
<section>Reassign</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Re-assignments </title>
<description>This is the Reassignment system. &#13;
&#13;
A user can reassign data from one employee to another employee working under him. The data can be of different types related to accounts, contacts opportunities, activities, tickets etc, which the newly reassigned employee could view in his schedule. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Click Update at the bottom of the page to save your reassignment, Cancel to quit the page without saving, and Reset to reset all the fields to their defaults and start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choose a User to reassign date from in the top dropdown. Only users below you in your hierarchy will be present here.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Select one or more To Users in the To User column to reassign the various assets to. The number of each type of asset available to be reassigned is shown in parentheses after the asset in the first column.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>CRITICAL: When Mathur selected his name from the hierarchy list, the system hangs and then gives a "Page Not Found". Interestingly this does not happen with other users. Similar bug in Pipeline Calls -- &gt; Add a Call HINT: The contact list is the possible problem as Mathur has 25000 against him</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: "User to assign to" should be a required field -- there is no checking</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>With "nothing selected" and UPDATE the message is: An Error Has Occurred The system administrator has been notified.&#13;
&#13;
You do not have the permissions to perform this action. </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Exception when I try to re-assign data from myself when I have nothing to reassign.UPDATE: This bug is already resolved </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:The list of possible users to reassign contains certain users with *. An explanatory label for what it means would be useful.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: The "To User" Dropdown does not show the list of all users to whome an item can be assigned to(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyCFS.do</action>
<section>MyProfile</section>
<subSection/>
<title>My Settings </title>
<description>This is the personal settings system page, where in you can modify/update the information about yourself, your location and also change your password to the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The location of the employee can be changed, i.e. the time zone can be changed by clicking on "Configure my location"</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update your personal information by clicking on "Update my personal information"</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can change your password by clicking on "Change my password"</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSProfile.do</action>
<section>MyCFSProfile</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Personal Information </title>
<description>This page lets you update/add your personal information</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Save your changes by clicking the Update button at the top or bottom of the page. The Cancel button forgets the changes and quits the page. The Reset button resets all fields to their original values so you can start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The only required field is your last name, but you should fill in as much as you can to make the system as useful as possible. Email address is particularly useful.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>UI: The 'mark to remove' field could be moved up by reducing some space in the previous text field.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSSettings.do</action>
<section>MyCFSSettings</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Location Settings</title>
<description>You can change your location settings</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The location settings can be changed by selecting the time zone from the drop down list and click the update button to update the settings</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSPassword.do</action>
<section>MyCFSPassword</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Update password</title>
<description>Your password to the system can be changed</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update your password by clicking on the update button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>On entering all the passwords correctly and hitting "Update" button a popup window asks about the system you want to update. It seems obvious that the user is trying to update it for the system he/she is logged in UPDATE: Happens only under mozilla, in hitting "Cancel" on the popup window the password gets updated anyhow</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When I select 'change my password'. The form shown, has a value already present for the current password field which is incorrect as it does not match with my current password.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section>ListTasks</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>This is the Action List System. &#13;
&#13;
The Action List System is designed to create new Action List and assign contacts to the Action list created. For each of the contacts you can add a call, opportunity, ticket, task or send a message, which would correspondingly show up in their respective tabs. For e.g. adding a ticket to the contact would be reflected in the Ticket tab.&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>For each of the existing tasks, you can view, modify, forward or delete the tasks by clicking on the Action button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a quick task. This task would have just the description and whether the task is personal or not</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add or update a detailed task called advanced task, wherein you can set up the priority, the status, whether the task is shared or not, also is the task assigned to self or someone working under the owner of the tasks, give the estimated time and add some detailed notes in it.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Checking the existing task's check box indicates that the particular task is completed.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select to view your tasks or tasks assigned by you to others. Each task can be viewed in three different modes i.e. the completed tasks, uncompleted tasks or all the tasks.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Delete asks "Do to delete this "OBJECT" ...,  user doesen't know no OBJECTS</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Tasks is not taking permissions into account</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>The clicking of image to mark a task as complete needs to take permissions into account</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Under Quick Actions, adding a new task and saving does not update or refresh the new task immediately. For example, the Tasks(4 incomplete) under My Items section does not show the 5th task that was added.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:Might be a good idea to denote the age of the task in days and hours and not just days.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: A user if he does not have the permission to delete a task assigned by him to somebody else should not be shown the  delete option in the selet menu when he is viewing all the tasks assigned by him to others.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: allows the user to add a blank task.  could check to see if the string has blanks and alert the user to enter a valid task name</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips>
<tipDescription>USABILITY: If my Task list has,  say 10 items out of which 6 are already complete and I wish to delete all of them. I will have delete each one. Could we have an option of deleting all at once? </tipDescription>
</tips>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyTasks.do </action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyCFS.do</action>
<section>Home </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyTasksForward.do</action>
<section>SendMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyCFSProfile.do</action>
<section>UpdateProfile</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Although everything is filled up correctly, the form cannot be saved. Possible reason could be the accessType added recently.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>CFSNoteTrash</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyActionContacts.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>No introduction available</description>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>SQL:My Home Page &gt; My Action Lists &gt; List Details &gt; Modify Action List &gt; This shows a list of contacts included for this Action. Now deselect all the contacts and click on [DONE]. This gives an error:java.sql.SQLException: ERROR:  parser: parse error at or near ")" at character 134 </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyActionContacts.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>You can add the new Action List and also select the contacts to be present in the Action List.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add the new Action List here. Along with description and the status you need to select the contacts you want in this Action List. You can populate the list in two ways. The first is to use the Add/Remove contacts</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The second is to define the criteria to generate the list. Once its generated we can add them to the selected criteria and contactsby using the add feature present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG/USABILITY: Existing contacts are are not shown when a user chooses to add contacts(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section>ListTasks </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>Inbox </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyActionContacts.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Action List</title>
<description>Allows you to manually add or remove contacts to or from an existing Action List.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Check new contacts to add them to your list, uncheck existing contacts to remove them from your list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Select All Contact, My Contacts or Account Contacts from the dropdown at the top.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Finish by clicking Done at the bottom of the page.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reassignments.do</action>
<section>DoReassign</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TaskForm.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Addition of a new Advanced task which can be assigned to the owner itself or any other employee working  under him</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add or update a detailed task called advanced task, wherein you can set up the priority, the status, whether the task is shared or not, also is the task assigned to self or someone working under the owner of the tasks, give the estimated time and add some detailed notes in it.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Pop up contact selectors My and All Contacts filters seem slow</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: My Home Page-&gt;My Tasks-&gt;Add a Task-&gt;[Change Contact]-&gt;Add a contact without a name-&gt;[Save]-&gt;Now click on the task and the Link Contact field shows 'none'</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: My Home Page -&gt; My Tasks -&gt; Update a Task(with already a Link contact eg:Adaskus, Matt)-&gt;[Clear Contact]-&gt;Click Update-&gt;Click on the task to view and the contact which was cleared earlier still remains.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:My Home Page-&gt;My Tasks-&gt;Select 'Tasks assigned by me' from the 'My Tasks' Drop down menu. Now click on the task and an error is reported stating - The system administrator has been notified. You do not have permissions to perform this action. </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Contacts" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>This is the Contacts system.&#13;
&#13;
The purpose of this system is for the users to view contacts and add new contacts into the existing system. You can search for contacts in the existing list and also export the data present in the system to different formats.&#13;
&#13;
</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Contacts system has three main features&#13;
&#13;
Add: A new contact can be added into the system. The contact can be a general contact, or one that is associated with an account. All the details about the contact like the email address, phone numbers, address and some additional details can be added.&#13;
&#13;
Search: Use this page to search for contacts existing in the system based on different filters&#13;
&#13;
Export: Contact data can be exported and displayed in different formats, and can be filtered in different ways. The Export page also lets you view the data, download it, and show the number of times the exported data has been downloaded. </detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Contact</title>
<description>A new contact can be added into the system. The contact can be a general contact, or one that is associated with an account. All the details about the contact like the email address, phone numbers, address and some additional details can be added.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select the contact category using the radio button and if the contact category is someone permanently associated with an account, then you can select the contact using the &#147;select&#148; link next to it</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can save the details about the employee using the &#147;Save&#148; button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &#147;Save &amp; New&#148; button saves the details of the employee and also opens up a blank form start another contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The only mandatory field is the Last Name, however, it is important to fill in as much as possible. These fields can be used for various types of queries later.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The contact type can be selected using the &#147;select&#148; link next to the contact type.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>SearchContactsForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search Contacts </title>
<description>Use this page to search for contacts existing in the system based on different filters</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>If the contact already exists in the system, you can search for that contact by name, company, title, contact type or source.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: a "Starts With" option would be really a useful addition.  One use would be to split work assignments on a Large List.  Possible implementation "pattern" = anywhere,  "%patter" = only at the front.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Seems like the From filter is not working as intended</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Reports</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Export Data </title>
<description>Contact data can be exported and displayed in different formats, and can be filtered in different ways. The Export page also lets you view the data, download it, and shows the number of times the exported data has been downloaded.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated by choosing the "Generate new export" link at the top of the page</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the dropdown to choose which data to display: the list of all the exported data in the system or only your own.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed in html format by clicking on the report name. The exported data can also be downloaded in CSV format or deleted by clicking the Select button in the action field.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>GenerateForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Exporting data</title>
<description>Use this page to generate a Contacts export report.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add all the fields or add / delete single fields from the report by using the buttons in the middle of the page. First highlight a field on the left to add or a field on the right to delete.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the Up and Down buttons on the right to sort the fields</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Subject is mandatory. Select which set of contacts the export will come from with Criteria. Select the Primary sort with the Sorting dropdown.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Click the Generate button when you are ready to generate the exported report</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>CRITICAL: If you have a lot of contacts then you get a "Page Not Found" error which stems from a java.lang.outOfMemory error caused by the ContactList </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>JAVASCRIPT: click on the UP/DOWN buttons without selecting an item </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ModifyContact</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Contact </title>
<description>The details about the contact can be modified here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update, cancel or reset the details of the contact using the corresponding buttons present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do </action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>It is possible to add nonsense names to contacts. For instance, I added one with a last name of "-".</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>We don't check for validity of email addresses. I added "darth#vader.com".</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Access Type drop down does not change on changing the Contact Category but does change once focus is taken off from it. Note: I am using IE5.0</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>The calls related to the contact are listed here along with the other details like the length of the call and the date when the call was made. You can also add a call.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click on the select button under the action field to view, modify, forward or delete a call</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the subject of the call will give complete details about the call.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a call associated with a contact</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Deleting a Call fromt the list view causes the navigation menu to disappear</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a Call</title>
<description>New call can be added which is associated with the contact. The type of call can be selected using the drop down list present</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The save button lets you create a new call which is associated with the call</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Needs "Send" and "Cancel"  buttons both at the top and bottom</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>SendMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>ViewOpps</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>All the opportunities associated with the contact are shown here, with its best possible total and the when the opportunity was last modified. You can filter the different types of opportunities that can be selected using the drop down and display them.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the action column for viewing, modifying and deleting an opportunity</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the opportunity will let you view the details about the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choosing the different types of opportunities from the drop down can filter the display.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add an opportunity associated with a contact</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Errors MUST provide a LOGOUT or a LINK back.  Otherwise the user must hit the BACK BUTTON.   I did and entered three duplicat opertunities.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Component modification from the  opportunity details screen does shows 2 cancel buttons</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>Calls associated to the contacts are displayed. The call details are shown with the length of the call, the notes associated, alert description, alert date etc.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or forward each call using the corresponding buttons</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>ERROR: On the Calls Details page, always get a "Page Not Found" error when clicking the Modify button.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: If Delete and modify buttons are disabled then there is not space between the forward button and the details table</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a component</title>
<description>A component can be added to an opportunity and assigned to any employee present in the system. The component type can also be selected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &#147;select &#148; link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employee present using the dropdown list present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>DetailsOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details </title>
<description>You can view all the details about the components here like the status, the guess amount and the current stage. A new component can also be added to a particular opportunity. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>An opportunity can be renamed or deleted using the buttons present at the bottom of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the select button lets you view, modify or delete the details about the component  </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the component would show the details about the component</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new component associated with the contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: The "Add a Component" link is BROKEN on the Opportunity Details page</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Unable to modify a component although I have Edit Permissions on General Contacts Opps</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>DetailsComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details </title>
<description>This page shows the details about the opportunity like what is the probability of closing the opportunity, what is the current stage of the opportunity etc</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify and delete the opportunity created using the modify and the delete buttons</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>When only View Permissions are there, there is a space between the Content and Name of the Opportunity</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modifying call details </title>
<description>You can modify all the details of the calls.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The type of the call can be selected using the drop down list and all the other details related to the call are updated using the update button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Adding and modifying a call should show that subject is required</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>InsertFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>UpdateFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ListContacts</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Sorting on Company did not seem to work as expected for me when reversing the sort. TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"Name" field is picking up the name of the company if there isn't a contact name.  It shouldn't</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Clone</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: If you come to this page from the contact details, it does not take you back to the details screen on hitting the Cancel button</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>AddFolderRecord</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Typo : Fireworks spelt as Firewiorks</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Add a Component link give me "page not found"</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>SearchContacts </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>MessageDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>The selected message is displayed with the message text and attachments if any.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click the attachments or the surveys link present along the message text</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>SaveComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>This page shows the details about the opportunity like what is the probability of closing the opportunity, what is the current stage of the opportunity etc</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify and delete the opportunity created using the modify and the delete buttons</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>It is possible to enter a low estimate that is higher than the high estimate, which should be trapped for.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>SearchContacts</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Contacts</title>
<description>This page shows the list of contacts existing in the system. The names of the contact along with the company name and phone numbers are shown. If the name of the contact is an account it's shown right next to it. You can also add a contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the action field to view, modify, clone or delete a contact</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the name of the contact will show the details about the contact</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a contact using the link  &#147;Add a contact&#148; at the top of the page</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>After deleting a contact, a page not found error displays, url should go to search not list</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ExportReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>The data present can be used to export data and display that in different formats. The exported data can be filtered in different ways. This would also let you view the data download it. This also shows the number of times an exported data has been downloaded. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed as a .csv file or in the html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action field is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated, which lets you choose from the contacts list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ContactDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contact Details </title>
<description>The details about the contact are displayed here along with the record information containing the owner, the employee who entered the details and finally the person who last modified these details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, clone, or delete the details of the contact. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:  Contact "history" shows a chronological history of all activities associated with the contact.  The history shows up in place of where details are today.  And can add another task like you do from "action lists"  today</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>When I have view only permission, there is still a clone button on this page, which generates an error when I click it.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>One time Bug:  When I tried to change a general to an account contact, the first time I got an error message about the ACCESS type.  I clicked again and with no change it WORKED the SECOND TIME.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>SQLException : General Contacts-&gt;Add Contact-&gt;Search for this Contact-&gt;view the contact-&gt;Delete Contact-&gt;Error:requested page could not be found-&gt;hit backspace-&gt;SQLException Error:Contact record not found </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: get the error and denied page when the contact is clicked although the permissions for the role allows view,add,edit,delete on action lists(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>When a contact is selected and the 'modify' button pressed, I get an error in the next page after some significant delay. The error is "The included page caused a problem."</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: If edit and delete permissions are turned off then there is not space between the Clone button and the details</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ViewMessages</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>This page lists all the messages associated with the contact, showing the name of the message, its date and its status.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the message gives more details about the message.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the messages in two different views i.e. all the messages present or the messages created/assigned by you</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Filter does not need the Controlled=Hierarchy and Personal messages here</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Sorting on any of the columns resets the filter View to My Messages</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardCall</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forwarding a call</title>
<description>The details of the calls that are associated with a contact can be forwarded to different employees present in the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select the list of the recipients to whom you want to forward the particular call to by using the &#147;Add Recipients&#148; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>SendCall</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of recipients</title>
<description>This page shows the list of recipients to whom the call details that are associated with an contact have been forwarded.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>ModifyComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modifying the component details  </title>
<description>The details of the component, associated with an opportunity can be modified</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &#147;select &#148; link</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employee present using the dropdown list present. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>ModifyOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify the opportunity</title>
<description>The description of the opportunity can be Renamed / updated.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update or cancel the information changed using the &#147;update&#148; or &#147;cancel&#148; button present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Fields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Folder Records</title>
<description>Each contact can have several folders and each folder further can have multiple records. You can add a record to a folder. Each record present in the folder displays the record name, when it was entered, who modified this record last and when.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The folders can be selected using the drop down list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also click on the record name, to view the folder record details. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details and modify them by clicking the select button under the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new record to a folder using the &#147;Add a record to this folder&#148; link present.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The folders can be selected using the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:  We need FORWARD and BACK button to page thru folder records.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Folder Data export to spreadsheet needed.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Multiple Records/Page needed as folder data output option.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ModifyFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Folder Record </title>
<description>Here you can modify the details of the folder record.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The changes made in the details of the folders can be updated or canceled using the &#147;update&#148; or &#147;cancel&#148; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Sub menu needs to have tabs</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>UpdateOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>All the opportunities associated with the contact are shown here, with its best possible total and the when the opportunity was last modified. You can filter the different types of opportunities that can be selected using the drop down and display them.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the action column for viewing, modifying and deleting an opportunity </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the opportunity will let you view the details about the opportunity</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choosing the different types of opportunities from the drop down can filter the display. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add an opportunity associated with a contact </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>If a contact already exists in the system, you can search for that contact by name, company, title, contact type or source, by typing the search term in the appropriate field, and clicking the Search button.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>If the contact already exists in the system, you can search for that contact by name, company, title, contact type or source, by typing the search term in the appropriate field, and clicking the Search button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The data present can be used to export data and display that in different formats by clicking the Export link at the top of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Click Add to add a new contact into the system</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: "Import Contacts" from a csv file is something we have had to do several times,  It needs to be on the General Contacts page.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>There are two "Add a Contact" links on the page, one on the secondary tabs, and one as an actual link above the contact dropdown. Only one is needed.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILIITY: The Contacts main page should display all contacts instead of displaying the search page (bpk) </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ContactsList.do</action>
<section>ContactList</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Enables you to select the contacts from the list and then add them to the Action List. It shows the name of the contact along with the email and the type of contact. &#13;
&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can filter the contact list in three different views. The views are all contacts, your contacts and Account contacts.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Check any or all the contacts from the list you want to assign to your action List.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contact detail page</title>
<description>The contact details associated to the account are displayed here. The details like the account number, email address, phone number and the addresses are shown here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify, clone and delete the contact by clicking the corresponding button </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can associate calls, messages and opportunities with each of the contact already existing in the system </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify contact</title>
<description>The details of the contact can be modified or updated here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The contact type can be selected using the &#147;select&#148; link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The details can be updated using update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>ViewMessages</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Messages</title>
<description>The list of the messages related to the contacts.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view all the messages related to the contact or only the messages related the owner (My messages)</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ContactForm.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Adding/Modifying a new contact</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This is for adding or updating a new detailed employee record into the system. The last name is the only compulsory field in creating an employee record.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>It is possible to add "nonsense names" like a last name of "-". Maybe we should do some simple checking?</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Inserting an Employee breaks with a referential integrity violation error</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Cancel button does not take you back to the details page </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Company should NOT be editable for account contacts because it doesn't change anyway.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Contact Type pop up does not remember the types selected across multiple pages</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Clicking on 'AddContact' tab highlights the 'SearchResults' tab </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: click on [Select] for Contact Type(s) and then click DONE and then click on Save. This gives a message in red !</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:Clone Account Contact-&gt;Access Type=Controlled-Hierarchy-&gt;Fill other details-&gt;save-&gt;"error:form could not be submitted, review messages below". But there are no review messages and the Access Type drop down menu now only has 'public' as its items. '</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Pipeline" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>This is the Pipeline System&#13;
&#13;
Pipeline helps in creating opportunities or leads in the company. Each opportunity helps to follow up a lead, who might eventually turn into a client. Here you can create an opportunity, search for an existing opportunity in the system, or export the data to different formats. The dashboard reflects the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the hierarchy of the owner/creator of the opportunity.&#13;
&#13;
</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Pipeline System has four main features:&#13;
&#13;
Dashboard: Gives you a quick, visual overview of the whole Pipeline System.&#13;
&#13;
Add: This page lets you add an opportunity into the system. Here a new opportunity can be added by giving the description of the opportunity. You can add a component that is associated with the opportunity. Each component can be assigned to an employee and the type of the component can be selected. For each component the probability of closing the component, the date estimated, the best guess for closing the deal and the duration for that component can be entered.&#13;
&#13;
Search: You can search for an opportunity already existing in the system based on different filters.&#13;
&#13;
Export: The data can be exported and displayed in different formats. The exported data can be filtered in different ways. </detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Dashboard</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>The progress chart is displayed in different views for all the employees working under the owner or creator of the opportunity. The opportunities are shown, with their names and the probable gross revenue associated with that opportunity. Finally the list of employees reporting to a particular employee/supervisor is also shown below the progress chart</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the owner or creator of the opportunity. The views can be selected from the drop down box present under the chart. The mouse over or a click on the break point on the progress chart will give the date and exact value associated with that point.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The opportunities created are also shown, with their names and the probable gross revenue associated with that opportunity. Clicking on the opportunities shows a details page for the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The list of employees reporting to a particular employee/supervisor is also shown below the progress chart. Clicking on an employee shows the Opportunity page from that person's point of view. You can then work your way back up the chain by clicking the Up One Level link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG:  Closed opportunities not dropped from dashboard view ... though are dropped in "View Opportunities"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>LOGIC: Pipeline / Dashboard:  When looking at Bill Roberts Dashboard, who reports to me, on his opportunity it shows (3) components to an opportunity when only 1 was assigned to him -- other 2 were somebody elses.  Shouldn't it only show 1</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Graphing:  The system will accept a negative commission rate (e.g. -10%) and will graph it correctly.  Should we allow this?  Not sure why not.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>CALC ALGORITHM BUG:  Calculated graphs wrong.  If date closed is 1'st of month, it does it correctly across term.  If start is mid-month, some dollars are dropped.  Appears because it demonstrates it by "area under the curve" approach</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>When using "Up One Level" in Pipeline/Dashboard to navigate back to "Self" the "Up One Level" remains as a option even there are no superior levels.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Clicking on the 'add' option produces a page with the following message. "The included page caused a problem."</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Opportunity</title>
<description>This page lets you add a opportunity into the system.&#13;
&#13;
Here a new opportunity can be added by giving a description of the opportunity, then adding a component that is associated with the opportunity. An opportunity can have one or more components. Each component can be assigned to a different employee and the type of the component can be selected. For each component the probability of closing the component, the date estimated, the best guess for closing the deal and the duration for that component are required. &#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The probability of Close, Estimated Close Date, Best Guess Estimate (what will the gross revenue be for this component?), and Estimated Term (over what time period?), are mandatory fields.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to yourself or one of the users in your hierarchy.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Component Description is a mandatory field. Be descriptive as you will be using this to search on later.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the Save button to save your changes and exit, Cancel to cancel your changes and exit, and Reset to cancel your changes and start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Enter and Alert Description and Date to remind yourself to follow up on this component at a certain time.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You must associate the component with either a Contact or an Account. Choose one of the radio buttons, then one of the Select links.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>SearchForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search Opportunities </title>
<description>You can search for an opportunity already existing in the system based on different filters</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The opportunities already present in the system can be searched using this featureOpportunities can be searched on description, the account name or the contact name with whom the opportunity is associated. It can also be searched by current progress / stage of the opportunity or the closing date range.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: not sure what the search is based on. Indicating to the user that the 5 input fields are individual choices could be useful. Suggestion...could use a simple 'or' label.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>LOGIC:  When should an opportunity with multiple components be considered closed?</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Need to have an "All Stages" at top of search item</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>LeadsReports.do</action>
<section>Default</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Export Data</title>
<description>Pipeline data can be exported, filtered, and displayed in different formats. You can also view the data online in html format, and see number of times an exported data has been downloaded.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed or downloaded as a .csv file or in html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action column is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated by choosing from the contacts list. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>SearchOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:  In next release the "Organization" drop down should be replaced by the ability to pick from a list (like we just changed in Tickets).  Drop down unwieldy when lots of organizations</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY:  Search on "Organization" brings back components, and not opportunities.  I'm expecting to see opportuntities</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY:  Search on "Description" returns a results page that shows the components -- and thus the term searched on might not be anywhere in the component description.  Should return what field is searched on</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>PERFORMANCE: Account selection should be a pop up selection</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>NOMENCLATURE:  The "Description" should be renamed "Opportunity Description".  And "Organization" should be "Account"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:  After doing a search, and assume nothing is found, it reflects these results in "View Opportunities" -- and nothing is shown because the criteria weren't met.  But, these parameters are now somehow remembered and nothing will show up in "View Opportunities" if you click on that.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:  Search Pipeline based on "Contact" doesn't seem to work.  Put in a contact and it brings back everything.  Also, does it default to looking at "My" opp's or "All" opp's?  I think it should default to look at your hierarchy.  Thus, "all". UPDATE: It defaults to the view selected in View Opportunities</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Reports</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE (2.6.1):  Change the current "reports" to something like "export", and then create some canned, basic reports  through Jasper UPDATE: Done for 2.6</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsComponents.do</action>
<section>ModifyComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Component</title>
<description>You can modify the component details associated with an opportunity in a pipeline.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Component Description is a mandatory field</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use Update at the top or bottom to save your changes, Cancel to quit this page without saving, and Reset to reset all fields to default and start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add an Alert Description and Date to alert you via a CRM System Message to take a new action</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Probability of close, Estimated Close Date (when you will get the revenue), Best Guess Estimate (how much revenue you will get), and Estimated Term (what term the revenue will be realized over) are all the mandatory fields.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select a Component Type from the dropdown. These component types are configurable by your System Administrator.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any User using the dropdown list present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a call</title>
<description>You can add a new call here associated with the opportunity. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The type of the call can be a phone, fax or in person. Some notes regarding the call can be noted. You can add an alert to remind you to follow up on this call.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Contact dropdown is automatically populated with the correct contacts for the company or account you are dealing with.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>ModifyOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify the opportunity:</title>
<description>The description of the opportunity can be modified / updated.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update or cancel the information changed using the &#147;update&#148; or &#147;cancel&#148; button present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Document</title>
<description>Modify the Subject or filename of a document.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update the details of the documents using the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>There is some extra space at the top of the Opportunity name</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Needs "Send" and "Cancel" buttons at the top too</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>GenerateForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: (NetDec) Output closed boolean field on report</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: (NetDec) Have a selection when running the report that will filter out all&#13;
opptys below a % probability (e.g. if we enter 20% as the value in that&#13;
field, only opptys with 20% or higher prob will print on that report run).</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: (NetDec) Have UK opps report in £ rather than $ - defaulting  by salesman user's location</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: (NetDec) Add a sales territory (or similar) field for a sales person user</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: (NetDec) change date format, for example UK  "15 Jan 03" as opposed to "1/15/03" or "15/1/03" this has caused a bit of confusion as the UK reports dates in the latter format</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>LOGIC:  The report generates "components", not "opportunities", even though the type is called "Opportunities Listings".  The simple fix (2.6) is simply to just change what's in the "Type" dropdown to "Component Listing".  But also need to export (2.6.1?) the component description with it, too.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Clicking on 'up' or 'down' button produces the a pop-up error window.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsComponents.do</action>
<section>DetailsComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details</title>
<description>The component details for the opportunity are shown here </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component details are shown with the additional options for modifying and deleting the component</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>QUESTION: Entering a 1.5 value in months is accepted.  Should this be the case?  How does the calculation work?</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>QUESTION: Can make Probability of Close &gt; than 100% and it will be accepted.  Is there a business reason for allowing values &gt; 100% or should there be a limit?  A key reason for only accepting values between 0 and 1 is otherwise the calculation of risk adjusted is screwy</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Adding a component allows dates in the past to be entered for estimated close date. This is a feature I'm not sure we need.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>ERROR:Update Component's details and refreshing the window throws an error</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>QUESTION: My Best Guess can be lower than the Low Estimate? Shouldnt the Best Guess be between the Low estimate and the High estimate</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Upload a new version of document</title>
<description>You can upload a new version of the document and the new version of the file can be selected and uploaded</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The document can be uploaded using the upload button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The new version of the document can be selected using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Search</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of components</title>
<description>The components resulted from the search are shown here. Different views of the components and its types are displayed. The name of the component with the estimated amount of money associated with the opportunity and the probability of that components being a success is shown. This also displays the time for closing the deal (term) and the organization name or the contact name if they are associated with the opportunity. A new opportunity can also be added.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>For each of the component you can view the details, modify the content or delete it completely using the select button in the Action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add an opportunity here by giving complete details about the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The search results for the opportunities present in the system are displayed here.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>There are different views of the opportunities you can choose from the drop down list and the corresponding types for the opportunities</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>QUESTION:Search Oppurtunity-&gt;shows a list of components without the tab structure  -&gt; clicking on a component to view its details again shows a list of components but now with a tab structure. So it actually takes two clicks to see a component after searching. Is this ok?</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>UpdateOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about the components here and also add a new component to a particular opportunity. The calls and the documents can be associated with that particular opportunity</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>In the Documents tab, the documents associated with the particular opportunity can be added. This also displays the documents already linked with this opportunity and other details about the document. The details can be viewed, downloaded, modified or deleted by using the select button in the action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the Calls tab you can add a call associated with the opportunity. This also displays the calls already linked with this opportunity and other details about the call. The call details can be viewed, modified, forwarded or deleted by using the select button in the action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can rename or delete the opportunity itself using the buttons below</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify, view and delete the details of any particular component by clicking the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the Components tab, you can add a component. It also displays the status, amount and the date when the component will be closed. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>There are three tabs in each opportunity i.e. components, calls and documents</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You get the organization name or the contact name at the top, which on clicking will take you to the Account details </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardCall</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forwarding a call</title>
<description>The details of calls associated with a contact can be forwarded to different users present in the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select the list of the recipients to whom you want to forward the particular call to by using the &#147;Add Recipients&#148; link. This will bring up a window with all users, from which you can then choose using check boxes.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can email a copy of the call to a user's Internet email by checking the Email check box.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add to the message by simply typing in the Body text box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>In the Documents tab, the documents associated with a particular opportunity can be added and viewed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The version of the particular document can be modified using the add version link present.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A document can be viewed, downloaded, modified or deleted by using the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A click on the subject of the document will show all the versions present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>The color on this isn't right</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: I reach an opportunity by the Dashboard trial. While trying to upload a document, the trial is " Pipeline &gt;  Dashboard &gt; Opportunity Details &gt; Documents &gt; Upload Document". But after I upload the document, the trial changes into "Pipeline &gt;  Search Results &gt; Opportunity Details &gt; Documents" instead of "pipeline&gt;dashboard&gt;...."</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify call details</title>
<description>You can modify the details of the calls.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The type of the call can be selected using the drop down list and all the other details related to the call are updated using the update button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>DetailsOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about opportunity components here and also add a new component to a particular opportunity. Calls and the documents can also be added to an opportunity or viewed by clicking on the appropriate tab.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>In the Calls tab you can add a call associated with the opportunity. This also displays the calls already linked with this opportunity and other details about the call. The call details can be viewed, modified, forwarded or deleted by using the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the Components tab, you can add a component. It also displays the status, amount and the date when the component will be closed.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>There are three tabs in each opportunity i.e. components, calls and documents.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can rename or delete the whole opportunity (not just one of these components) using the buttons at the bottom.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The organization or contact name appears on top, above the Components Tab, which will take you to the Account details, when clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify, view and delete the details of any particular component by clicking the select button in the Action column, on the far left.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the Documents tab, the documents associated with the particular opportunity can be added. This also displays the documents already linked with this opportunity and other details about the document. Details can be viewed, downloaded, modified or deleted by using the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>When I reach an oppurtunity from the Dashboard, the trail list has "Pipeline&gt;Dashboard&gt;Oppurtunity details" in it. However, when I select the view details, the trial changes to "Pipleline&gt;Search&gt;..." instead of  "Pipeline&gt;Dashboard&gt;...."</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Trying to add a component or modify an existing component produces a page with the message "The included page caused a problem."</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: What I think is happeneing is, when any action is selected by using the select option in the left column, the "dashboard" trial gets relaced by the "search results" trial.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>Calls associated with the opportunity are shown. Calls can be added to the opportunity, and details about listed calls can be examined.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>In the Calls tab you can add a call associated with the opportunity. This also displays the calls already linked with this opportunity and other details about the call. The call details can be viewed, modified, forwarded or deleted by using the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the call subject is clicked then it will show you complete details about the call. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Call forwarding has no text in the body </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Add a Call gives a "Page Not Found" UPDATE: Related to large number of contacts as one of the fields on this form is a dropdown selection of contact associated with the call</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>ViewOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>The opportunities resulted from the search are shown here. Different views of the opportunities and its types are displayed. The name of the component with the estimated amount of money associated with the opportunity and the probability of that opportunity being a success is shown. This also displays the time for closing the deal (term) and the organization name or the contact name if they are associated with the opportunity</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>There are different views of the opportunities you can choose from the dropdown list and the corresponding types of the opportunities </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add an opportunity here by giving complete details about the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The search results for the opportunities present in the system are displayed here.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For each of the component you can view the details, modify the content or delete it completely using the select button in the Action column. You can click on any of the component names, which shows more details about the component like the calls and the documents associated with it.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUS. LOGIC (2.6.1):    When using the sort capability on the "Component" column (ascending/descending) it sorts on the opportunity (which you can't see) and not on he component.  Should sort alphabetically on the Component </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Although the vie shows components on clicking on one of them it takes me to the opportunity</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USEABILITY  (2.6):  "View Opportunities" sub-module should be renamed "View Components".  Then, we could create another, related sub-module (2.6.1?) called "View Opportunities" -- which would show Opportunity information versus component info.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"Not Mine" component was open (Kristin's), another component was closed (Matt's), opportunity showed up under "All closed opps".  Shouldn't</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>REMINDER: Put "All Users" first in list, only show users drop-down when not "My Open Opportunities"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Might be a good idea to show the oppurtunity in the table.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG or FEATURE ? Selecting "My Open Oppurtunites" takes me to the component list and not the oppurtunities list.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:When clicked on the alphabetic links for navigation (0 A B C ...) and if the selected link does not have any results, the following label is displayed (Records 5 to 4 of 4 total ) for my example.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:When search criteria cannot find any results, the labelling appears to be wrong.(1 -4 of 4 total) in my eample when 0 records were returned.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>EA: The count feature of the number of results is stilll not corect. Even when there 4 records, the label says "No records to display".</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>This is the Pipeline System&#13;
&#13;
Pipeline helps in creating prospective opportunities or leads in the company. Each opportunity helps to follow up a lead, who might eventually turn into a client. Here you can create an opportunity, search for an existing opportunity in the system, export the data to different formats. The dashboard reflects the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the owner/creator of the opportunity. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The list of employees reporting to a particular employee/supervisor is also shown below the progress chart.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The opportunities created are also shown, with its name and the probable amount of money associated with that opportunity. Clicking on the opportunities would give a better understanding of the details of the opportunity</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the owner or creator of the opportunity. The views can be selected from the drop down box present under the chart. The mouse over or a click on the break point on the progress chart will give the date and exact value associated with that point.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsComponents.do</action>
<section>SaveComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details</title>
<description>&#13;
The component details for the opportunity are shown here&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component details are shown with the additional options for modifying and deleting the component</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: When I enter 30000 in the Prob. of close, the system rightly asks me to enter something below a 100....but when I enter 120...it accepts the input. Bug in error checking.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsComponents.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a component</title>
<description>A component can be added to an opportunity and assigned to any employee present in the system. The component type can also be selected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &#147;select &#148; link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employee present using the dropdown list present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>The calls associated with the opportunity are shown. The calls can be added to the opportunity.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>In the Calls tab you can add a call associated with the opportunity. This also displays the calls already linked with this opportunity and other details about the call. The call details can be viewed, modified, forwarded or deleted by using the select button in the action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the call subject is clicked then it will show you complete details about the call</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details </title>
<description>Details about the call associated with the opportunity</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete and forward each of the calls.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG:  An Account/Opportunity/Call shows up, but can't be modified.  It throws a "requested page not found" error</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Pipeline: Pipleline Management&gt;View Components &gt;Oppurtunity Details&gt;Calls &gt;Call Details&gt;----When I click on the Forward button this it gives a page not found.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Upload a document</title>
<description>New documents related to the opportunity can be uploaded into the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking the Upload button will upload the selected document into the system.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the Browse button opens a file browser on your own system. Simply navigate to the file on your drive that you want to upload and click Open. This will close the window and bring you back to the Upload page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a very descriptive Subject for the file. This is a mandatory field.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>IE: Extra space between trails and header</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Extra space between the trails and the Opportunity symbol &amp; description</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Feature ? Is there a limiting size on the documents. I tried 17 MB...Works fine.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details </title>
<description>This shows all versions of the updated document. The name of the file with the size, the version and the number of downloads are shown here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>All the versions of the particular document can be downloaded from here. Simply select the version you want and click the Download link on the far left.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsReports.do</action>
<section>ExportList</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of exported data</title>
<description>The data present can be used to export data and display that in different formats. The exported data can be filtered in different ways. This would also let you view the data download it. This also shows the number of times an exported data has been downloaded</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed as a .csv file or in the html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action field is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated, which lets you choose from the contacts list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Click on the subject of the new export, the data is displayed in html format</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsReports.do</action>
<section>ExportForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Generating Export data</title>
<description>Generate an exported report from pipeline data</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Click the Generate button at top or bottom to generate the report from the fields you have included. Click cancel to quit and go back to the Export Data page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Highlight the fields you want to include in the left column and click the Add or All link. Highlight fields in the right column and click the Del link to remove them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the Sorting dropdown to sort the report by one of a variety of fields</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the Criteria dropdown to use opportunities from My or All Opportunities</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Subject is a mandatory field.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Accounts" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>This is the Accounts System&#13;
&#13;
You are looking at Accounts home, which has a dashboard view of all your accounts. This view is based on a date range selected from the calendar; by default it shows the schedule for the next seven days. You can optionally view the calendar of those below you in your hierarchy. The scheduled actions of each user can also be viewed. In the Accounts Module, new accounts can be added, existing accounts can be searched based on different filters, revenue for each account can be created/maintained and finally, data can be exported to different formats&#13;
&#13;
</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>The Accounts System has five main features&#13;
&#13;
Dashboard: Displays a dashboard view of the whole Account System.&#13;
&#13;
Add: Add new Account&#13;
&#13;
Search: This page provides a search feature for the accounts present in the system&#13;
&#13;
Revenue: Graphically visualizes revenue if the historical data is present in the system. All the accounts with revenue are shown along with a list of employees working under you under the progress chart. You can add accounts, search for the existing ones in the system based on different filters and export the data to different formats&#13;
&#13;
Export: Data can be exported and displayed in different formats. The exported data can be filtered in different ways. You can view the data, download it, and see the number of times an exported report has been downloaded </detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Dashboard</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>The date range can be modified which is shown in the right hand window by clicking on a specific date on the calendar. Accounts with contract end dates or other required actions appear in the right hand window reminding the user to take action on them. The schedule, actions, alert dates and contract end dates are displayed for user or the employees under him by using the dropdown at the top of the page. Clicking on the alert link will let the user modify the details of the account owner. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the alert link will let you modify the details of the account owner.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Accounts with contract end dates or other required actions will appear in the right hand window where you can take action on them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the schedule, actions, alert dates and contract end dates for yourself or your employees by using the dropdown at the top of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify the date range shown in the right hand window by clicking on a specific date on the calendar, or on one of the arrows to the left of each week on the calendar to give you a week's view. Clicking on "Back To Next 7 Days View" at the top of the right window changes the view to the next seven days. The day or week you are currently viewing is highlighted in yellow. Today's date is highlighted in blue. You can change the month and year using the dropdowns at the top of the calendar, and you can always return to today by using the Today link, also at the top of the calendar.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Only the account alerts show up on this calendar so the relevance for the description for other icons is little.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: To remove popup "this page has secure and nonsecure items"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Since an account name is clickable the way it is displayed should indicate that(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:add two accounts with expiry on the same date. This shows a category account on the dashboard, but the number of accounts is not updated.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: https://ds21.darkhorseventures.com/Accounts.do?command=Dashboard produced and error message saying "The included page caused a problem" in red. There was a long delay before this came up.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Account</title>
<description>A new account can be added here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Use the Insert button at top or bottom to save your changes, Cancel to quit without saving, and Reset to reset all the fields to their default values and start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>It's a faily straightforward "fill in the blanks" exercise. There should be a "Primary" or "Business", or "Main" version of phone/fax numbers and addresses because other modules such as Communications Manager use these to perform other actions.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Fill in as many fields as possible. Most of them can be used later as search terms and for queries in reports.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Depending on whether you have chosen Organization or Individual, there are mandatory description fields to fill out about the account.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choose whether this account is an Organization or an Individual with the appropriate radio button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the Select link next to Account Type(s) will open a window with a variety of choices for Account Types. You cah choose and number by clicking the checkboxes to the left. It is important to use this feature as your choice(s) are used for searches and as the subject of querries in reports in other parts of the application.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: max characters in a text field should be declared according to the database</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Account</title>
<description>The details of an account can be modified here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The account owner can also be changed using the drop down list</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The account type can be selected using the &#147;Select&#148; link</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>This is for adding or updating account details. The last name or the organization name, based on the classification, is the only mandatory field in creating a new account. The type of account can be selected using the select option given next to the account type</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the Account has a contract, you should enter a contract end date in the fields provided. This will generate an icon on the Home Page and an alert for the owner of the account that action must be taken at a prearranged time.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>VALIDATION: Email address needs to be validated</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>VALIDATION: Entering a non-integer in the phone number field throws a "Page Not Found"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>VALIDATION: Entering a non-integer in the revenue should alert the user</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Adding an individual account shows up as an organization account on the update screen. After fixing this check  if the org_name is being consistently maintained when the last and first name changes</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Exception "object expected" when an account is modified, the changes are recorded though(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Account Details&gt; Modify Account--- The Update button gives a java script error. The url is https://ds21.darkhorseventures.com/Accounts.do?command=Modify&amp;orgId=80</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contact Details</title>
<description>A contact can be associated with an account. The lists of the contacts associated with the account are shown along with the title.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify, clone and delete the contact by clicking the select button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the name of the contact is clicked, it shows details of that contact, with the options to modify, clone and delete the contact details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a contact, which is associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: On completing a QA item I want to mark it as complete and might want to add some comments</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Although I do not have permissions to add a account contact, I can do so from the general contacts module if I had permissions to add a general contact. Pipeline also would have the same issue. Pipeline Management would have the same issue with Account and Contact Opps having different business rule. This issue also would also This goes to show that we should have a Business Rule Manager in place soon to enforce the business rules based on objects.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>None of the fields on the list are sortable COMPLETE: Name is sortable now</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Fields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Folder Record Details</title>
<description>You create folders for accounts. Each folder can have one or more records associated with it, depending on the type of the folder. The details about records associated with the folder are shown</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Using the select button in the action column you can view details and modify the record.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click on the record type to view the folders details and modify them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new record can be added to the folder.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The folders can be populated by configuring the module in the admin tab.. The type of the folder can be changed using the drop down list shown.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Opportunities.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>Opportunities associated with the contact, showing the best guess total and last modified date.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Opportunities associated with the contact, showing the best guess total and last modified date.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add an opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Three types of opportunities are present which can be selected from the drop down list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the description of the opportunity is clicked, it will give you more details about the opportunity and the components present in it.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Edit Action throws a "Page Not Found"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Although I do not have access to adding Account Opportunities, changing the URL string "View" to "Prepare" gives me access</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When a new opportunity is added, existing opportunities are not listed unless the opportunity tab is refreshed(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Revenue Details</title>
<description>The revenue associated with the account is shown here. The details about the revenue like the description, the date and the amount associated are displayed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>By clicking on the description of the revenue you get the details about that revenue along with the options to modify and delete its details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view your revenue or all the revenues associated with the account using the drop down box </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify and delete the details of the revenue by clicking the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add / update a new revenue associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Although I have permissions to delete Revenue records on trying to delete a record, a permission error is raised</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"All Revenue" view needs to show the owner field</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Revenue Details</title>
<description>The revenue associated with the account is shown here. The details about the revenue like the description, the date and the amount associated are displayed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>By clicking on the description of the revenue you get the details about that revenue along with the options to modify and delete its details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view your revenue or all the revenues associated with the account using the drop down box </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify and delete the details of the revenue by clicking the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add / update a new revenue associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Although I have permissions to delete Revenue records on trying to delete a record, a permission error is raised</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"All Revenue" view needs to show the owner field</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Revenue </title>
<description>Adding a new revenue which is associated with the account</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Add new revenue associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Revenue </title>
<description>Here the revenue details can be modified</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The revenue details can be updated or reset the changes</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>ViewTickets</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Details</title>
<description>This page shows the complete list of the tickets present related to a account. Also lets you add a new ticket</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the action column to view, modify and delete the ticket.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the ticket number will let you view the details, modify and also lets you delete the ticket.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new ticket.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>The issue appears in a little section here, but in tickets it gets a whole line</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>Here the documents associated with the account are listed. New documents related to the account can be added</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the documents can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The document versions can be updated by using the "add version" link </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new document can be added which is associated with the account</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details, modify, download or delete the documents associated with the account</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>SearchForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search Accounts </title>
<description>This page provides the search feature for the accounts present in the system</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can search for the accounts present in the system. The search can be based on the Account name, phone number or the Account type. Three types of accounts can be selected from the drop down list shown, which can also be used for searching</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>On searching on an Account Number field, results gotten do not have a account number column.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Search fails both on account number and phone number(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Account Details</title>
<description>This shows the details of the account, which can be modified. Each account can have folders, contacts, opportunities, revenue, tickets, and documents, for which there are separate tabs.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Click Modify at the top or bottom of the page to modify these datails.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Any thing can be typed for Account number/URL. Even junk values !</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: All tabs should indicate whether they have information or not, currently the user has to click on every tab to know whether any other infohas been recorded for the account(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Dashboard</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Revenue Dashboard </title>
<description>This is the dashboard view of Revenue&#13;
&#13;
This shows the progress chart for different years and types. All the accounts with the revenue are also shown along with the list of employees working under you are also listed under the progress chart. You can add accounts, search for the existing ones in the system based on different filters and export the data to different formats</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The list of employees reporting to a particular employee/supervisor is also shown below the progress chart. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Accounts present are also shown, with its name and the amount of money associated with that Account. Clicking on the Account would give a better understanding of the details of the Account</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the owner or creator of the Account. The views can be selected from the drop down box present under the chart. The mouse over or a click on the break point on the progress chart will give the date and exact value associated with that point. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Reports</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Export Data </title>
<description>The data can be exported and displayed in different formats. The exported data can be filtered in different ways. This would also let you view the data and also download it. This also shows the number of times an exported data has been downloaded&#13;
&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed as a .csv file or in the html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action field is clicked. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated using the "Generate new export" link</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>The FileItem object inefficiently used getEnteredByName() and getModifiedByName() -- most actions are iterating the list to set these</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>ModifyFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify folder record </title>
<description>The Folder record details can be updated. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details are updated by clicking the Update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>ReopenTicket</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Delete</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>ERROR:when a new account is created and then SELECT-&gt;'Archive' gives an error:You do not have permissions to perform this action.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>GenerateForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Generate New Export</title>
<description>To generate the Export data</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>There are filters through which you can exactly select the data needed to generate the export data. Apart from selecting the type of accounts and the criteria, you can also select the fields required and then sort them.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Generated a full report of All Contacts with all columns but the columns entered, enteredby, modified, modifiedby, owner, notes did not get generated with the report </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: The Up and Down buttons and also the Add All, Remove buttons have the table border around them . Browser: IE5.0</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>Calls associated with the contact</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Using the select button under the action column you can view the details about the call, modify the call, forward the call or delete the call on the whole.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the subject of the call will show you the details about the call that was made to the contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a call associated with the contact using the &#147;Add a call&#148; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>AddFolderRecord</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add folder record</title>
<description>A new Folder record can be added to the Folder.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The record details can be saved using the save button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a call</title>
<description>You can add a new call, which is associated with a particular contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the new call can be saved using the save button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The call type can be selected from the dropdown box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>UI: The manadatory subject field does not have an asterisk in red.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Upload Document </title>
<description>New documents can be uploaded and be associated with the account</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can browse to select a new document to upload if its related to the account</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Some uploaded files have an extra 2 bytes appended CRLF</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Adding a file with Apple Safari breaks  NOTE: Should be fixed now</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>UpdateOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Althought opportunity modify permissions are turned on, I am not able to modify a component. Add &amp; Delete permissionss are turned off</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Upload a New Version of a existing Document </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can upload a new version of a existing document.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Details </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>On doing a "Search Accounts" on the name of a company it takes you to "View Accounts" and shows the search results. In the filter though it still says "All Accounts" instead of "Search Results". Also for all further queries of "All Accounts" only the "Search Results" are returned</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>AddTicket</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a new Ticket</title>
<description>This page lets you create a new ticket for the account </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can insert a new ticket, add the ticket source and also assign new contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>When adding a new contact using the popup, if the name has a ' or a " then a javascript error is thrown</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"Create New Contact" link gives a "Page Not Found"</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>Here the documents associated with the ticket are listed. New documents related to the ticket can be added</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the documents can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details, modify, download or delete the documents associated with the ticket</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new document can be added which is associated with the ticket</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The document versions can be updated by using the "add version" link</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Account Ticket Documents need to have their own permissions</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"Add a Document" gives a permission error although I have permission to edit tickets.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Clicking on the Subject of the uploded document i.e. the Item column gives a Java Script error. Clicking on the select button under "Action" and going to the view details also gives a JS erro</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>UpdateTicket</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Extra space between trails and Account Name. Browser: IE 5.0</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>InsertFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG/DISPLAY: requires a top level message idicating all mandatory feilds have not been filled</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Search</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Lists the Accounts present and also lets you create an account</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the account name, shows complete details about the account</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new account</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The select button in the Action column allows you to view, modify and archive the account. Archiving makes the account invisible, but it is still in the database.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Page shows all the versions of the current document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download all the versions of the documents</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Modify the current document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify / update the current document information like the subject and the filename</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Account Details</title>
<description>This shows the details of the account, which can be modified. Each account can have several folders, the contacts for that account, probable opportunities, the revenue generated, and the tickets for each of the account can also be added here. You can update several documents associated with each account. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the account can be modified here. The details can be saved using the Modify button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG:When the page is submitted with just the"account type", an appropriate message is displayed, but the "account type(s)" list becomes empty(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Phone/fax should have seperate text feild for area code(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Phone number strictly accepts 10 digits, may not be suitable for internationalization</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call details</title>
<description>The details of the call are shown here which can be modified, deleted or forwarded to any of the employees.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or forward the calls using the corresponding buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: There is a space between the tabbed sub menu for account and the contact. Check all other screens on fixing</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: When the permissions for add,edit and delete are turned off the forward button does not have a space after it</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add / update a call</title>
<description>You can add a new call, which is associated with a particular contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the new call can be saved using the save button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The call type can be selected from the dropdown box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call details</title>
<description>The details of the call are shown here which can be modified, deleted or forwarded to any of the employees</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or forward the calls using the corresponding buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>ForwardCall</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forward Call </title>
<description>The details of the calls that are associated with a contact can be forwarded to different employees present in the system</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select the list of the recipients to whom you want to forward the particular call to by using the &#147;Add Recipients&#148; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>ViewOpps</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Opportunities</title>
<description>Opportunities associated with the contact, showing the best guess total and last modified date.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify and delete the opportunity associated with the contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the description of the opportunity is clicked, it will give you more details about the opportunity and the components present in it.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add an opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Three types of opportunities are present which can be selected from the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>DetailsOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about the components here and also add a new component to a particular opportunity. The opportunity can be renamed and its details can be modified</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can rename or delete the opportunity itself using the buttons below</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify, view and delete the details of any particular component by clicking the select button in the action column. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new associated with the account component. It also displays the status, amount and the date when the component will be closed. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>TicketDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Details </title>
<description>This page lets you view the details of the ticket also lets you modify and delete the ticket.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Lets you modify or delete the ticket information</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also view the tasks, documents related to a ticket along with the history of that document by clicking on the corresponding links.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>ModifyTicket</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify ticket</title>
<description>This page lets you modify the ticket information and update the details</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also have tasks, documents related to a ticket along with the history of that document.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Lets you modify / update the ticket information</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>PERFORMANCE: The drop down selection of a contact is inefficient from a performance standpoint</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"close" checkbox is not retained if the validation on some other field on the form fails</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: A ticket source "other" should involve a description(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketTasks.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Task Details</title>
<description>This page lists the tasks assigned for a particular account. New tasks can be added, which would then appear in the list of tasks, showing their priority and their assignment.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the task can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update the task by clicking on the description of the task</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a task which is associated with the existing ticket</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Account Ticket Tasks need their own permissions</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Business Rules of a Ticket Tasks are not defined clearly</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>The task description has the table border showing around the description and the status image, also if there is a contact linked to it then the details of that has a similar issue</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Permission needs to be added for Account Ticket Tasks </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: permission issue in ticket tasks. Only when a user is given permission to both edit and add a task, he is able to add the task. If no edit permissions, he cannot add a ticket although he has add permissions.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Uploading a Document</title>
<description>New document related to the account can be uploaded</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The document can be uploaded using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>ViewHistory</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Log History</title>
<description>This page maintains the complete log history about each ticket from it's creation till the ticket is closed</description>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Coloring scheme is not very appealing on this screen</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details </title>
<description>All the versions of the current document are listed here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download all the different versions of the documents using the "Download" link in the Action column</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Document </title>
<description>Here the document information can be modified</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The subject and the filename of the document can be modified</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Upload New Version </title>
<description>New versions of the document are uploaded</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The subject and the file name can be changed. The version number is updated when a updated document is uploaded</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>ExportReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Exported data</title>
<description>The data can be exported and displayed in different formats. The exported data can be filtered in different ways. This would also let you view the data and also download it. This also shows the number of times an exported data has been downloaded</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed as a .csv file or in the html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action field is clicked. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated using the "Generate new export" link </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Revenue Details </title>
<description>Details about the revenue</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Revenue details along with the option to modify and delete the revenue</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Dashboard </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunityForm.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Opportunity</title>
<description>A new opportunity associated with the contact can be added </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add / update an opportunity here and assign it to an employee. The opportunity can be associated with an account or a contact. Each opportunity created requires the estimate or the probability of closing the deal, the duration and the best estimate of the person following up the lead.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Cancel button takes you to Pipeline / View Opp's -- should take to Pipeline / Add Opportunity</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Date picker calander is too narrow - both month scroll arrows should show</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>If click to modify a component that's already been closed, it brings back the page without the "Close this checkbox" checkbox checked (2.6.1?)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>It is possible to add a low estimate that is higher than the high estimate. We should trap for this.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>I see two (2) cancel buttons</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Matt says this look like...extra space on Internet Explorer</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Error checking needed for closing dates and percentage values.(problem is closing dates could be already past and percentage values even greater then 100 are accepted)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:'Associate With' field does not remember if the Contact radio is selected and when saved, it gives an error saying review message:An account or a contact needs to be selected</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>QUESTION:Low estimate and High estimate can take negative values ?</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: AlertDate.Vale is not an object on saving the opportunity</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Pipeline: Pipleline Management &gt; Add Oppurtunity--- add a oppurtunity and hit "save button" gives you a java script error</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:(inconsistent) https://ds21.darkhorseventures.com/LeadsComponents.do?command=SaveComponent&amp;auto-populate=true. I tried submitting an invalid form and came to this page. The 'Select' buttons in the 'Associate With' part do not do any actions. The links do not respond. I could not successfully submit this form.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:(inconsistent) Got a sql exception in https://ds21.darkhorseventures.com/LeadsComponents.do?command=SaveComponent&amp;auto-populate=true. THe first line of the exceptions said "missing oppurtunity header"</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Opportunities.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add opportunity </title>
<description>A new opportunity associated with the contact can be added</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add / update an opportunity here and assign it to an employee. The opportunity can be associated with an account or a contact. Each opportunity created requires the estimate or the probability of closing the deal, the duration and the best estimate of the person following up the lead. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Opportunities.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about the components here like the status, the guess amount and the current stage. A new component can also be added to a particular opportunity. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>An opportunity can be renamed or deleted using the buttons present at the bottom of the page</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the select button lets you view, modify or delete the details about the component </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the component would show the details about the component </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new component which is associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: On clicking the "Rename Opportunity" button there is an error </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Rename Opportunity button throws a "Page Not Found"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Although I have permissions to edit opportunites I cannot edit components of the opportunity</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>"Add a Component" link is  broken</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Opportunities.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Opportunity </title>
<description>The details of the opportunity can be modified</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The description of the opportunity can be changed using the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunitiesComponents.do</action>
<section>DetailsComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details </title>
<description>This page shows the details about the opportunity like what is the probability of closing the opportunity, what is the current stage of the opportunity etc</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify and delete the opportunity created using the modify and the delete buttons </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>There is an extra space at the top of the Details table when the user has only view permissions </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunitiesComponents.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a component</title>
<description>A component can be added to an opportunity and assigned to any employee present in the system. The component type can also be selected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &#147;select &#148; link</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employee present using the dropdown list present. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunitiesComponents.do</action>
<section>ModifyComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Component </title>
<description>The details of the component can be added / updated to an opportunity and assigned to any employee present in the system. The component type can also be selected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &#147;select &#148; link</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employee present using the dropdown list present. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the update button can save the changes made to the component</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Space between Cancel and Reset buttons at the top</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunitiesComponents.do</action>
<section>SaveComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details</title>
<description>This page shows the details about the opportunity like what is the probability of closing the opportunity, what is the current stage of the opportunity etc</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify and delete the opportunity created using the modify and the delete buttons </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Campaign Manager" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>Communications is a "Campaign Manager" Module where you can manage complex email. fax, or mail communications with your customers. Communications allows you to create and choose Groups, Messages, and Schedules to define communications scenarios from the simple to the very complex. Groups can range from a single contact chosen from a pick list to the result of a complex query of the Account database. Messages can be anything from a single-line email to a rich, multimedia product catalog to an interactive survey.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Communication System has six main features&#13;
&#13;
Dashboard: Track and analyze campaigns that have been activated and executed.&#13;
Messages can be sent out by any combination of email, fax, or mail merge. The Dashboard shows an overview of sent messages and allows you to drill down and view recipients and any survey results.&#13;
&#13;
Add: This page lets you add a new campaign.&#13;
&#13;
Campaign List: This page lets you add a new campaign into the system.&#13;
&#13;
Groups: Each campaign needs at least one group to send a message to. Use criteria to filter the contacts you need to reach and use them over and over again. As new contacts meet the criteria, they will be included in future campaigns. This page lists the group names. It shows the groups created by you or everybody i.e. all the groups. &#13;
&#13;
Messages: Compose a message to reach your audience. Each campaign requires a message that will be sent to selected groups. Write the message once, then use it in any number of future campaigns. Modified messages will only affect future campaigns. Displays the list of messages, with the description and other details.&#13;
&#13;
Attachments: Customize and configure your Campaigns with attachments. Attachments can include interactive items, like surveys, or provide additional materials like files. </detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Dashboard</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Communications Dashboard </title>
<description>Track and analyze campaigns that have been activated and executed.&#13;
 &#13;
Messages can be sent out by any combination of email, fax, or mail merge. The Dashboard shows an overview of sent messages and allows you to drill down and view recipients and any survey results.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking the select button under the action column gives you the option to view the details about the campaign, download the mail merge and also lets you to export it to excel</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the campaign name, gives you the complete details about the campaign </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can display the campaigns created and their details using three different views. Selecting from the drop down list can do these</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: ?? Message not send when created with date to send BEFORE todays date.  Could be a problem on campains run around midnite or if the system goes down over a date change with messages in the output spool.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Cannot cancel a campaign that has a survey -- referential integrity error</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a campaign</title>
<description>This page lets you add a new campaign into the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This creates a new Campaign. This takes in both the campaign and its description</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign List </title>
<description>Create or work on existing campaigns.&#13;
 &#13;
The Campaign Builder allows you to select groups of contacts that you would like to send a message to, as well as schedule a delivery date. Additional options are available.&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the details, modify and delete the details by clicking the select button under the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For each of the campaign, the groups, message and the delivery columns show whether they are complete or not. Clicking on these will help you choose the group, choose the message and the delivery date</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the name of the campaign would show you more details about the campaign and also show the list of the things to be selected before a campaign can be activated</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view your incomplete campaigns or all the incomplete campaign&#146;s.  You can select the view by the drop down list present at the top</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a campaign </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>View Groups </title>
<description>Each campaign needs at least one group to send a message to. Use criteria to filter the contacts you need to reach and use them over and over again. As new contacts meet the criteria, they will be included in future campaigns. This page lists the group names. It shows the groups created by you or everybody i.e. all the groups.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the Action column for viewing, modifying or deleting the details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the group name will show the list of contacts present in the group.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a contact group using the link  &#147;Add a Contact Group&#148;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can filter the list of groups displayed by selecting from the drop down</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>PERFORMANCE:  When click to view the details of a specific group I got some slow performance (e.g. 10000 ms)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Group</title>
<description>A new contact group can be added. Separate criteria can be specified when creating the group. The criteria can be defined to generate a list. The list to be added can be previewed before saving the group details. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can preview the details of the group by clicking on the preview button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also select from the list of &#147;Selected criteria and contacts&#148; and remove them by clicking the remove button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can define the criteria to generate the list by using the different filters present and then add them to the &#147;Selected criteria and contacts&#148;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select the criteria for the group to be created. Clicking the &#147;Add/Remove Contacts&#148; can choose the specific contacts.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USEABILITY:  The size of the preview box to too small.  The NEXT and CLOSE buttons are off the dialog AND the are NO SCROLL bars.  To get to the next page you have to resize the box.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: In the define criteria section, select Area Code/Zip code  for 'Field ' from the drop down menu  and in the search Text enter '#@!' and add . Then hit the preview button and this generates a  java.lang.NullPointerException</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:Enter sone numbers for the date and say preview and it gives a java.util.NoSuchElementException</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:Select Company name and enter ' @#$#' and say preview. It shows all the contacts. Now hit BackToCriteria button and it gives a java.lang.NumberFormatException</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message List </title>
<description>Compose a message to reach your audience.&#13;
Each campaign requires a message that will be sent to selected groups. Write the message once, then use it in any number of future campaigns. Modified messages will only affect future campaigns. Displays the list of messages, with the description and other details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view, modify, clone or delete each of the messages</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The dropdown list act as filters for displaying the messages that meet certain criteria </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the message name will show details about the message, which can be updated</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new message</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a Message</title>
<description>you can add a new message for the campaign, which would show up in the message list</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The new message can be saved by clicking the save message button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The permissions or the access type for the message can be chosen from drop down box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILTIY: When I create a new message, I am forced to enter all details of the message, but not the actual message. Hence I can create a campaign with a message, but with no content. </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerAttachment.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Create Attachments </title>
<description>Customize and configure your Campaigns with attachments. Attachments can include interactive items, like surveys, or provide additional materials like files. &#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the "surveys" will let you create new interactive surveys</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Surveys do not show up if only view permissions are turned on</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Contacts of the group are displayed</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can use the preview button to view the details about the contacts in a group </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify or delete a group.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>QUESTION:view Groups-&gt;Group Details(Group which does not have a criteria defined)-&gt;Preview-&gt;shows a list of all the contact records available(around 25000)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>version change of a document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can change the version of the document when ever a updated document is uploaded</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Upload button does not do any action</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Dashboard </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>New documents can be uploaded and be associated with the campaign</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can browse to select a new document to upload if it&#146;s related to the campaign</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ResponseDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Quantitative and ItemList responses are not aligned left</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Preview</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Here details about the contacts i.e. the name, and their company and also their email address  are displayed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This has a option to take you back from the current detailed view to the group details criteria</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>PrepareDownload</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Details</title>
<description>This page shows the details about the campaign and also shows the list of documents, that are available which are related to the campaign.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download the list of the documents available by using the  "download" link under the action column</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG ??: Did a campaign with delivery as "letter only" and when I go and try and "Download" I come up with a blank screen.  How do I get the document?</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewGroups</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Groups</title>
<description>The group name along with the contacts present in the Group are listed </description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a survey</title>
<description>You can add a new survey here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The name of the survey is a mandatory field for creating a survey. The description, introduction and the thank you note can also be added</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>JAVASCRIPT:Click SAVE without entering any details and  it results in an error:questionText.value is not an object</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>MoveQuestion</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Details </title>
<description>Campaign details are the number of groups selected for the campaign, the text message of the campaign, when is it scheduled to run, how the delivery of the message done, who entered these details and who modified it are shown here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download the mail merge shown at the bottom of the details.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: After revoking the permission for accessing Campaign records, if we try to see the details of a record (comm. manager/dashboard/record)...We get a permission error page.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>All Versions of this current Document are shown here with the details like the size of the uploaded file , the number of downloads etc.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Different versions of the document can be downloaded using the "download" link in the action column</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>"Update" button does not work</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Exra space between the campaign sub menu and the form</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>SQL Exception:Add a Campaign-&gt;type a space for the Campaign Name field and hit Insert. It gives a exception:Invalid ID specified!</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>ViewReturn</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: The name of the survey is a mandatory field, but i can enter a 'space' and the form is saved. </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Details </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewSchedule</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>For the campaign you can schedule a delivery date to send the message to the recipients</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update the campaign schedule by filling the run date and the delivery method whether it&#146;s an email, fax or letter or any other method.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Here you can update the group details and also the update contact criteria for the same.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also generate a list of contacts be selecting from the filters and adding them to the &#147;selected criteria and contacts&#147; list</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can choose the contacts in the group using the &#147;Add / Remove contacts&#148; link present.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update the name of the group </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG:  After saving a group that was built, it changes terminology from "My General Contacts" to "My Contacts"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:  Criteria won't be saved if when building a group you don't "preview" it before you save it</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY (2.6):  The sorting of the "Search Text" drop down is all screwed up.  No rhyme or reason that I can see.  Ought to be alphabetical</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG (Maybe):  If try to add the exact same criteria again, by just pushing the "add" button (so it will pop up in the window to the right a second time) it comes backwith an error message about having to enter text.  Even  though there is something in the "Search Text" window</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>PreviewRecipients</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Recipients</title>
<description>The page displays a list of recipients with their name, their company name, the date when the campaign was sent to those recipients and the status of it. </description>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY:  Letter sent process needs to be explained very well in "Tips" or else it will be unusable for most.  Like for me.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: In the list of recipients the 'Sent date' and 'status' were empty. Some status message would be more informatory.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>PreviewMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details </title>
<description>The message details are shown here. It? in the form of an email with the subject and the message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>There can be multiple attachments to a single message. The attachment that needs to be downloaded has to be selected first and then downloaded.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG:  Two messages looked good in my CFS view, but when I received them in my email after sent, they had lots of the ????.  One particular message I sent was composed long before the Unicode install, the new message also had ???'s.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Sent a message with a link to a survey.  When click on to see what survey I sent via the "Dashboard"/ then "message" tab, nothing shows up.  Error says something like "survey not found".</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: A link is provided in the message text for a survey(http://ds21.darkhorseventures.com/ProcessSurvey.do?id=${surveyId=17}). Clicking on that produces a blank web page with no content and no links.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>PreviewSchedule</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Schedule</title>
<description>This shows the delivery date and the delivery method or the campaign. </description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewResults</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Results</title>
<description>This page shows the results of the responses received from all the recipients in the group. This also shows the Last response received.</description>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE (2.6.1 if possible): Ability to export the key contact information from "results" area.  We now have a "View Item Details", we need a "Export Item Details" and perhaps just put it right into excel</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: If a question is open ended the comments given show up in a column whose size too small.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewResponse</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Response</title>
<description>This page shows the responses of all the recipients along with their system IP addresses and their email address</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Document details</title>
<description>This page list all the documents associated with this campaign and for each document it lists the size of the file, the extension and the version of the file.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the documents can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details, modify, download or delete the documents associated with the account </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new document can be added which is associated with the account </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The document versions can be updated by using the "add version" link </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE? (2.7/3.0): If a survey isn't sent, do we want the "Results" and "Responses" tabs to appear?  Relevant?  Could be confusing</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE? (2.7/3.0)  If sending a survey through the mail, and they mail it back, we need a capability to enter the information into CFS so we can capture it.  At which point we do need the "results" and "responses" tabs for letters sent</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Details </title>
<description>This is the detail page for the campaign where the step-by-step information is given on how to activate the campaign is given i.e. what should be selected before a campaign is activated.&#13;
&#13;
This campaign can be configured and can now be activated.&#13;
Once active, today's campaigns will begin processing in under 5 minutes and cannot be cancelled.&#13;
&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The name of the campaign can be changed or deleted by using the buttons at the bottom of the page</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can choose a group / groups, a message for the campaign, a delivery date for campaign to start. You can also add attachments to the messages you send to recipients.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: I can create a campaign today and schedule it to be on a prior date. what happens if I activate it? How will the server treat it?</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: If only view permissions are turned on, I should still be able to view which group is selected, the survey selected and also the message in view only mode</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>AddGroups</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Choose Groups </title>
<description>Selecting or updating the group / groups for the campaign can be done here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can check the groups you want for the current campaign.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also add attachments to the messages you send to recipients by clicking the preview recipient&#146;s link next to each group.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view all the groups present or the groups created by you just by choosing from the drop down box</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>Updating a message for the campaign</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select a message for this campaign from the dropdown list of all the messages or just your messages</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The messages can be four types, which can be used as filters and can be selected from the drop down list. For each type you have further classification.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewAttachmentsOverview</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Attachment Details</title>
<description>For each message, we can add the attachments.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The attachments configured are the surveys or the file attachments. Using the links &#147;change survey&#148; and &#147;change file attachments&#148; can change both of them.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewAttachment</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Surveys </title>
<description>A survey can be selected for this campaign</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The surveys viewed can be of all the surveys or only the surveys he has created and a corresponding list of surveys will be previewed</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ManageFileAttachments</section>
<subSection/>
<title>File Attachments </title>
<description>Campaign can also have the file as a attachment</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download or remove the file name. You can also upload files using the browse button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Campaign Details</title>
<description>Updating the campaign name /description</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The name and the description of the campaign can be changed</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details </title>
<description>This page shows the details of the message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or clone the message details by clicking on corresponding buttons</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: there is a line break between [Modify] and [Delete] [Clone] buttons</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Space needed below the "Modify" button</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Message </title>
<description>This page lets you Add/update a new message. The message can have an access type, as to who can view a message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select font properties for the text of the message along with the size and indentation</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The name of the message and the access type can be given, which specifies who can view the message</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG IE:Object expected on submitting a modification, the modification is recorded though(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details </title>
<description>This page shows the details of the message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or clone the message details by clicking on corresponding buttons</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Clone</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a Message </title>
<description>This page lets you Add/update a new message. The message can have an access type, as to who can view a message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select font properties for the text of the message along with the size and indentation </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The name of the message and the access type can be given, which specifies who can view the message </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG:  The message editor seems both finicky and hard to use.  Can we remove some of the more troubling functions of it (e.g. tables) and leave the others?</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: In trying to "save" a "cloned" message I got a big error message.  I had left some required fields empty, but not sure that caused it.  I now notice that the "Access Type" field has nothing in it.  Probably related to it</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:  The "Insert Image" icon on the message editor doesn't seem to work...or I don't know how to use it</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Surveys</title>
<description>This page displays the surveys created and also lets you update them.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view the details, modify them and delete the details about a survey. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the survey shows the details about the survey</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new survey</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view all the surveys created by all or surveys created by you using the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY:  (2.6.1)  Need to go through application and address issue of "delete", and where we need ability to archive.  Need it in surveys...ability to "archive" one to get it out of the list view (e.g. an old survey).  You can't do if today if there's an existing relationship</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>InsertAndAdd</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Survey Questions</title>
<description>Here you can add a new survey question. If the question type is &#147;Item List&#148;, you can edit the list of items present in that list and also mark whether the particular question is required or not.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The &#147;save &amp; Add&#148; button saves the current question and lets you add another one immediately.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also specify whether the particular question is required or not by checking the checkbox.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the selected question type is &#147;Item List&#148;, then a Edit button is enabled which helps in selecting adding new elements to the existing list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The new question type can be selected through the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY:  Default size of Item edit box doesn't show the save buttion.  Size should be increase or a set of SAVE/CANCEL buttons placed near the top of the dialog.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Survey Details </title>
<description>The details about the survey are displayed here along with the option to modify, delete  and preview the survey </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The preview button shows you the survey questions in a pop window</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete and preview the survey details using the buttons at the top of the page</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the survey introduction text, the questions and the thank you text </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Survey Details</title>
<description>This page displays all the questions added to a particular survey. It also enables you to add new questions. The questions can be moved up or down the order. They could be edited or deleted. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add the questions to the survey here</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the &#147;Done&#148; button can save the survey and you can also traverse back by clicking the &#147;back&#148; button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The survey questions can be moved up or down using the &#147;Up&#148; or &#147;Down&#148; links present in the action field.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can edit or delete any of the survey questions using the &#147;edit&#148; or &#147;del&#148; link present under the action field.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add new survey questions here. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: When I  Click on Edit Items, I get a small popup which allows me to add items. But i can add a space and this is added to the item list. When i preview the survey, I get a check box with no text next to it.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>JSERROR: I click the Edit Items and rename the item list, I get a JS error</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>You are looking at the communications System home. This page reviews and manages campaigns with the following options: Dashboard, Campaign Builder, Build groups, Create messages and create attachments.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click on &#147;Create Attachments&#148; and include interactive items, like surveys, or provide additional materials like files.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the &#147; Create Message&#148; lets you compose a message to reach your audience.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click the &#147;Build Groups&#148; to assemble dynamic distribution of groups. Each campaign needs at least one group to send a message to.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &#147;Campaign Builder&#148; can be clicked to select groups of contacts that you would like to send a message to, schedule a delivery date, etc.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click on the &#147;Dashboard&#148; to view the sent messages and allows you to drill down and view recipients and any survey results.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DISPLAY: 'Add' should be renamed as add campaign to directly reflect its functionality(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Tickets" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>This is the Tickets System&#13;
&#13;
You are looking at the ticket System home page. The dashboard shows the most recent tickets that have been assigned to you, as well as tickets that are in your department, and tickets that have been created by you. You can add new tickets, search for the existing ones based on different filters and export the data to different formats&#13;
&#13;
</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Tickets System has four main features&#13;
&#13;
View: Lists all the tickets assigned to you and the ones assigned in your department. The details like the ticket number, priority, age i.e. how old the ticket is, the company and the tickets assignment are displayed.&#13;
&#13;
Add: You can add a new ticket here&#13;
&#13;
Search: Form used for searching the tickets that already exist in the system based on different filters and parameters&#13;
&#13;
Export: This is the page shows exported data. The data can be exported to different formats. The exported data can be viewed with its subject, the size of the exported data file, when it was created and by whom. It also shows the number of times that particular exported file is downloaded. The exported data, created by you or all the employees can be viewed in two different views. A new data file can also be exported. </detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Details </title>
<description>This page lets you view the details of the ticket also lets you modify and delete the ticket.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Lets you modify or delete the ticket information </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also have tasks, documents related to a ticket along with the history of that document.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Should have a ticket documents permission like account ticket documents</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: When the overview of the tickets are provided, such as source, issue..etc, it might be a good idea to show the number of tasks or documents associated with it . This could link to the "Tickets" section to make it more navigatable</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Ticket</title>
<description>You can add a new ticket  here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>For each new ticket you can select the organization, the contact and also the issue for which the ticket is being created. The assignment and the resolution of the ticket can also be mentioned</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>On assigning a ticket to a user, the email which is sent as a alert does not have any content in it</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Error checking not performed for date. It is possible to add a task whose due date has already passed.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Need to have a "Users without a department" like projects so tickets can be assigned to users that are not in a department</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>SearchTicketsForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search Existing Tickets</title>
<description>Form used for searching the tickets that are already existing in the system based on different filters and parameters</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The search can be done based on different parameters like the ticket number, account associated, priority, employee whom the ticket is assigned etc.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Search form should give the option for sorting by certain fields like status, entered date, number, severity</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Add a freeform text search to find tickets based on issue text</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Add a freeform text search to find tickets based on resolution text</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Search form should remember the search criteria</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Add search criteria to view tickets assigned to a specific user</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:The first search criteria is to search based on ticket number. This ticket number is system assigned and not provided by the creator. A user would have to have seen the ticket earlier to retrive it using this feature.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:The 'organization' should have the label "All" by default and the 'assigned to' should have the label "Any" by default. The current labelling belies the search criteria.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Reports</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Export Data </title>
<description>This is the page shows exported data.&#13;
The data can be exported to different formats. The exported data can be viewed with its subject, the size of the exported data file, when it was created and by whom. It also shows the number of times that particular exported file is downloaded. The exported data, created by you or all the employees can be viewed in two different views. A new data file can also be exported.&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the subject of the exported data shows you the details of the ticket like the ticket ID, the organization and its issue (why the particular ticket was generated)</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the select button under the action column lets you view the data, download the data in .CSV format or delete the data.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the exported date generated, by you or all the employees. This view can be filtered using the dropdown list</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can generate a new exported data by clicking the link &#147;Generate new export&#148;</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: On the reports page we should have sortable headers for "Subject", "Created Date", and "Created By".</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: As options for the select button, along with "view details, delete and download", a "print" option would be useful. </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: The feature is downloaded as a CSV that could be opened in a Excel. Would be a useful feature to download a PDF file depending on user preferences.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Ticket Details</title>
<description>Here you can modify the ticket details like ticket information, it's classification, the ticket&#146;s assignment and it's resolution.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can save the details of the modified ticket by clicking the Update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: A solution is mandatory when closing a ticket. This is not indicated anywhere. Might be a good idea to inform the user with a label or *.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:When the user closes a ticket without providing a solution, "The included page caused a problem. " appers on the next screen with no navigatable links. Might be a good idea to do the error checking and popup a warning frame instead.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Alert user that the solution will not be saved unless the ticket is closed.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Ticket Details</title>
<description>Here you can modify the ticket details like ticket information, it's classification, the ticket&#146;s assignment and it's resolution.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can save the details of the modified ticket by clicking the Update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: A solution is mandatory when closing a ticket. This is not indicated anywhere. Might be a good idea to inform the user with a label or *.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:When the user closes a ticket without providing a solution, "The included page caused a problem. " appers on the next screen with no navigatable links. Might be a good idea to do the error checking and popup a warning frame instead.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Alert user that the solution will not be saved unless the ticket is closed.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketTasks.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Tasks</title>
<description>This page lists the tasks assigned for a particular ticket. New tasks can be added, which would then appear in the list of tasks, showing their priority, their assignment and other details</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the task can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update the task by clicking on the description of the task </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a task which is associated with the existing ticket </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: I cannot see any tasks that have been added to a ticket except my own, I don't expect to be able to EDIT it, but I should be able to view it</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When adding a ticket task, the task should only be allowed to be assigned to users of the system OR at least let the person who created the task modify it if the person is not a user of the system</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Cannot add a Task in tickets. I think I was able to a few minutes ago. Not sure if it is only under some circumstances. UPDATE: Not able to simulate the bug</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:The task associated with a ticket is shown in the ticket section. However, the task could be modified or editied only under the tickets section. A link connecting the task from the ticket section to the task section would be useful.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: The due date for the task could be given as a date which is already passed.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: The age of the task is mentioned in terms of days. Would be more descriptive to mention it in terms of hours and days as in the case of tickets.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE ? or BUG ?   When creating a task associated with a ticket, the dude date could be a date earlier than date of entry. Should that be disallowed ?</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Documents </title>
<description>Here the documents associated with the ticket are listed. New documents related to the ticket can be added </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the documents can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details, modify, download or delete the documents associated with the ticket </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new document can be added which is associated with the ticket </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The document versions can be updated by using the "add version" link </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:Might be useful to tell the user that clicking on the navigational alphabets on top would actually produce all the matches from that alphabet and after.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Once in a while the text in the links "Details","tasks","document" and "History" appear to be skewed or only half visible. Becomes corrected when the mouse is moved over.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: There is no way to tell that there is a document associated with a ticket until you actually go to the documents tab for the particular ticket. There should be an icon on the ticket summary page and on every page below.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Add Document link shows up although the permissions are turned off</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>Fields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Folder Records</title>
<description>New folders can be created for each of the ticket. Configuring the admin module creates these custom folders. This page also displays the list of records with their details like when the particular record was created, last modified, the action performed on the record etc. associated with a particular folder</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A new record is added into the folder using the link &#148;Add a record to this folder&#147;. Multiple records can be added to this folder, if the custom folder has the necessary settings.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>you can select the custom folder using the drop down list. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>AddFolderRecord</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Folder Record</title>
<description>The details of  the record are added&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details are saved by clicking the save button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>ViewHistory</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Log History</title>
<description>The log history of the ticket is maintained. </description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This history of the ticket, i.e. right from when the ticket was created to the time when the ticket was closed, the entire history log of that ticket is maintained</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:In the 'Ticket log History' table, it might be a good idea to label the columns and tell the user what they mean. An example would be "Ticket creator, Modification time and modification".</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: On creating a ticket, the email which is sent should not have the "Comment" field if no comment was entered</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>InsertFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>GenerateForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: For report generation, the subject line is a must. However, ther subject line in the report is not marked with a red * to indiacate that it is mandatory.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: It might be a good idea to actually have a "delete all" button similar to the "add all" button.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When the "up" and "down" buttons are pressed, an "errors on page" window is pops up in IE. </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Along with "add all, add and delete", it might be a good idea to have a button which provides the option "Add all non-empty fields".</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: It might be a good idea to project the report to the user and ask for a confirmation before saving it. This might be useful because the users dont have any direct feedback on what is selected even when they press the generate button.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Details </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: The table shown in the left reflects correctly the tickets assigned to and by me. The My Items box does not seem to reflect the changes. There is something wrong with the counts.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>ExportReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Download link throws a Page Not Found</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>ModifyFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Folder Record</title>
<description>This lists the details of the folder record, which can be modified.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The changes can be saved using the Update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>UpdateFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Folder Record Details </title>
<description>The detail about the folder along with the record information like when the record was created and when it was modified is displayed here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify the folder information along with the record details by clicking on the Modify button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>SearchTickets</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: TM</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Search tickets needs to go back to search form after a previous search was done.  Not to the view tickets form.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When we delete a ticket, using the option in the 'search results', a warning frame pops up. When ok is clicked a warning frame pops up in IE indicating errors in the page and a blank page with no content or links is shown. </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Action Column in the header of the list is missing</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Home </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a Document</title>
<description>New document related to the ticket can be uploaded</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The document can be uploaded using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>Page shows all the versions of the current document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download all the versions of the documents</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Document Details</title>
<description>This page lets you modify the ticket information and update the details</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also have tasks, documents related to a ticket along with the history of that document. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Lets you modify / update the ticket information </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add version number to Documents</title>
<description>You can upload a new version of a existing document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The new version file can be uploaded using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Home</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>This page displays the complete list of the tickets assigned to the user, the list of the tickets present in his department and finally the list of the tickets created by the user. For each ticket, the details about the ticket like the ticket number, priority; age of the ticket, the company and finally the assignment details are displayed. The issue details are also shown separately for each ticket.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can delete a record by clicking on "Del" next to the record</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a record by clicking on "Add Ticket"</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view more records in a particular section by clicking "Show More"</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view more details by clicking on the record</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update a record by clicking on "Edit" next to the record</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>It is possible to have permission to view the ticket module, but not have permission to view tickets, which generates an error. UPDATE: It is a permissionError which is raised and one resolution could be to define minimal permissions you need to have turned on to have view access to a module and also to exclude add/edit/delete permissions when you do not have view permissions. This is a system wide issue.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>It looks like a ticket entered by me and assigned to me will only be shown on the entered by me section, and not the assigned to me section. I now see that this is only sometimes true.UPDATE: Any ticket created by you and assigned to yourself is showing up in both the Tickets Assigned to Me and Tickets Created By Me, not sure what the real issue is  here</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:The number of assigned/unassigned tickets shown in the 'View Tickets' and counts shown in the 'My Items' dont correlate.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Would be a good idea to rename the link 'Tickets&gt;View Tickets' to where the 'Tickets&gt;View Open Tickets'.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>Other Tickets in My Department: These are records that are assigned to anyone in your department, are unassigned in your department, and are open</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>Tickets Assigned to Me: These are records that are assigned to you and are open</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>Tickets Created by Me: These are records that have been entered by you and are open</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips>
<tipDescription>Make sure to resolve your tickets as soon as possible so they don't appear here!</tipDescription>
</tips>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Employees" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>You are looking at the Employee System home page. This page displays the details of all the employees present in the system.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription> &#13;
The main feature of the employee module is the view.&#13;
&#13;
View: This page displays the details of each of the existing employee, which can be viewed, modified or deleted. Each employee record contains details like the name of the employee, the department they are in, his title and phone number. This also lets you add a new employee into the system</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>ListEmployees</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>The details of each of the existing employee can be viewed, modified or deleted and a new detailed employee record can be added</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A new detailed employee record can be added </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The details of each of the existing employee can be viewed, modified or deleted. This can  be done through the  select button present in the action column</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Cannot delete an employee to whom a communication has been sent</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>I am a EMPLOYEE and Do Not Show up as an employee (roberts) HINT(Mathur) : Contact List object still uses the contact_type_levels for an employee, there is a employee field in contact which can be used for this</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Sub menu should also have a 'Add' option</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>EmployeeDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Employee Details </title>
<description>This is the employee detail page. This page displays the email, phone number, addresses and additional details of each employee</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify or delete the employee details using the modify or delete buttons</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add an Employee</title>
<description>You can add an employee into the system. The details of the employee like his email address; phone numbers, address and other additional details can be given along with his name</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The &#147;Save &#148; button saves the details of the employee entered. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &#147;Save &amp;New&#148; button lets you to save the details of one employee and lets you enter another employee details.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>ModifyEmployee</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Employee Details </title>
<description>The employee details like the name of the employee, email address, phone numbers and address can be modified here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the update button saves the modified details of the employee.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>This page shows the details of the employee record, which could be either modified or deleted</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The employee record can be modified or deleted from the system completely.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Reports" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>This is the Reports system.&#13;
&#13;
You are looking at the Reports System home page. This page displays the list of generated reports that are ready to be downloaded. It also displays the list of reports, which are scheduled to be processed by server. You can add new reports too.&#13;
&#13;
</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Reports System has two main features.&#13;
&#13;
Queue: Queue shows the list of reports that are scheduled to be processed by server&#13;
&#13;
Add: This shows the different modules present and displays the list of corresponding reports present in each module. </detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>ViewQueue</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>This is the home of the reports. &#13;
&#13;
A list of customized reports can be viewed and the queue of the reports that are scheduled to be processed by the server are also displayed. Each report that is ready to be retrieved is displayed along with its details like the subject of the report, the date when the report was generated, report status and finally the size of the report for the user to download.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can cancel the reports that are scheduled to be processed by server by the clicking the select button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The generated reports can be deleted or viewed/downloaded in .pdf format by clicking the select button under the action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new report</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>RunReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Modules</title>
<description>This shows the different modules present and displays the list of corresponding reports present in each module.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>There are four different modules and you can click on the module where you want to generate the report</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do </action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>CancelReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Refreshing screen produces java.sql.SQLException: Queue record not found.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>ParameterList</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Parameters specification</title>
<description>This page takes the parameters that need to be specified to run the report</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can use the "generate report" button to run the report</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the parameters exist, you can specify the name of the criteria for future reference and click the check box present at the bottom of the page</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>ListReports</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Lis of Reports</title>
<description>In this module, you can choose the report that you want to run from the list of the reports</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can run the report by clicking on the title of the report</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>CriteriaList</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Criteria List </title>
<description>You can choose to base this report on previously saved criteria, or continue and create new criteria</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>If the criteria is present select the criteria then continue to enter the parameters to run the report</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>GenerateReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Reports Added to queue</title>
<description>This page shows that the requested report is added to the queue. Also lets you know the details about the report and queue status</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the queue either by using the link in the text or using the view queue button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>This&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can cancel the report that is scheduled to be processed by server by clicking the select button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the reports generated, download them or delete them by clicking on the select button under the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new report can be generated by clicking on the link "Add a Report"</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Admin" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>The admin module lets the user review the system usage, configure the specific modules and also configure the global/system parameters.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Admin System has five main features.&#13;
&#13;
Users: This section allows the administrator to view and add users and manage user hierarchies. The users are typically employees in your company who interact with your clients or customers.&#13;
&#13;
Roles: This page lists the different roles present in the system, their role description and the number of people present in the system who carry out that role. New roles can be added into the system&#13;
&#13;
Modules: This page lets you configure modules that meet the needs of your organization including configuration of lookup lists and custom fields. There are four types of modules. Each module has different number of configure options. The changes in the module affect all the users&#13;
&#13;
System: You can configure the system for the session timeout and set the time for the time out&#13;
&#13;
Usage: Current System Usage and Billing Usage Information is displayed&#13;
 &#13;
</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>ListUsers</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Users</title>
<description>This section allows the administrator to view and add users and manage user hierarchies. The users are typically employees in your company who interact with your clients or customers.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The alphabetical slide rule allows users to be listed based on their last name of the alphabet that is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The columns "Name", 'Username" and "Role" can be clicked to display the users in the ascending or descending order of the chosen criteria.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "Add New User" link opens a window that allows the administrator to add new users.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "select" buttons in the "Action" column alongside the name of each user opens a pop up menu that provides the administrator with options to view more information, or modify user information or disable (or inactivate) the user.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The list is displayed by default with 10 names per page, additional items in the list may be viewed by clicking on the "Previous" and "Next" navigation links at the bottom of the table or by changing the number of items to be displayed in a page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The users of the CRM system are listed in alphabetical order of their name. Their user name, role and the reporting person are also listed to provide a quick overview of information for each user.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The drop list provides a filter to either view only the active or only the inactive users. Inactive users are those who do not have the privilege to use the system currently either because their user name's have been disabled or they have expired. These users may be activated (enabled) at a later time.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DEVELOPER: ListUsers method raises an exception at the server level , a Nullpointer in the UserNameHandler tag lib </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>JAVASCRIPT ERROR: System Administration-&gt;Add User-&gt;[Select Contact] opens a popup window. Now minimize the popup. Click on View users. Now maximize the popup and click on Add in the popup. This shows an error.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:The 'disable login' button should be enabled only when the role of the user permits deletion of users. Currently it is enabled even for users who dont have that permission.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:The alphabet slide should display  "No users" when an alphabet is clicked if there are not users whose last name start with the clicked alphabet.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>InsertUserForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a New User</title>
<description>This form allows new users to be added to the system and records their contact information.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The 'Reports To" field allows the administrator to setup a user hierarchy. The drop list displays all the users of the system and allows one to be chosen.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "Role" drop list allows a user to be associated with a role. This association determines the privileges the user may have when he accesses the system.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "Password" fields allows the administrator to setup a password for the user. The password is used along with the Username to login to the system. Since the password is stored in encrypted form and cannot be interpreted, the administrator is asked to confirm the users password. The user may subsequently change his password according to personal preferences.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Username is the phrase that would be used by the user to login to the system. It should be unique.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>An "Expire Date" may be set for each user after which the user is disabled. If this field is left blank the user is active indefinitely. This date can either be typed in the mm/dd/yyyy format or chosen from a calendar that can be accessed from the icon at the right of the field.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The contact field allows the administrator to associate contact information with the user. The administrator may either create new contact information or choose one from the existing list of contacts. This information provides the administrator with the users e-mail, telephone and (or) fax number, postal address and any other information that may help the administrator or the system manager to contact the user.
</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>HINT:  A user being added MUST be either an ACCOUNT CONTACT or an EMPLOYEE.  You CANNOT make a GENERAL CONTACT into a USER</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Create New Contact form allows you to add a General Contact by selecting the Account Contact option but not selecting an Account. General Contact should not be allowed as users</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Add User Page - Create New Contact - Exception - java.sql.SQLException: ERROR:  $2 referential integrity violation - key referenced from contact_type_levels not found in lookup_contact_types&#13;
&#13;
	at org.aspcfs.modules.contacts.base.Contact.insert(Unknown Source)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: User being added (or activated) from a future starting date (bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Multiple Contacts my be required (one for home, work, etc) Only 1 contact seems to be allowed now(bpk) </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>ModifyUser</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify User Details</title>
<description>This form provides the administrator with an editable view of the user information, and also allows the administrator  to view the users login history and view points.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The "Cancel" button allows current and uncommitted changes to be undone.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the "Generate new password" field is checked, the system constructs a password for the user and uses the contact information to mail the new password.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "Disable" button provides a quick link to the administrator to disable the user.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "Username", "Role", "Reports To" and password of the user are editable. For more information about each of these fields see help on "Add user".</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Generate New Password - nice to have link to change the email address.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY/BUG: An invalid date can be typed in the date field (e.g., 14/41/04), though the date gets adjusted to a valid date, it does not provide any warning (bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>ViewLog</section>
<subSection/>
<title>User Login History</title>
<description>Provides a login history of the chosen user.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The list is displayed by default with 10 items per page, additional items in the login history may be viewed by clicking on the "Previous" and "Next" navigation links at the bottom of the table or by changing the number of items to be displayed in a page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The login history of the user displays the IP address of the computer from which the user logged in, and the date/time when the user logged in.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>ListViewpoints</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Viewpoints of User</title>
<description>The page displays the viewpoints of the employees regarding a particular module in the system. Lets you add a new viewpoint. The details displayed are when the viewpoint was entered and whether it enabled or not.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the select button under the action column would let you to view the details about the viewpoint also modify them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click on the contact under the viewpoint column to know more details about that viewpoint and its permissions.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can Add New Viewpoint using the link &#147;Add New Viewpoint&#148;.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>InsertViewpointForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Viewpoint</title>
<description>The contact name can be selected and the permissions /access for the modules can be given.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add a new viewpoint by any employee by clicking the add button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The permissions for the different modules can be given by checking the Access checkbox.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The contact can be selected and removed using the links &#148;change contact&#148; and &#147;clear contact&#148;.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>ViewpointDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Update Viewpoint </title>
<description>You can update a viewpoint and set the permissions to access different modules.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details can be updated using the update button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also set the permissions to access different modules by checking the check box under the Access column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can enable the viewpoint by checking the &#147;Enabled&#148; checkbox.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section>ListRoles</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Roles</title>
<description>You are looking at roles. &#13;
&#13;
This pages lists the different roles present in the system, their role description and the number of people present in the system who carry out that role. New roles can be added into the system</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click on the select button under the action column to view or modify the details of roles</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the role name would give you details about the role and his permissions in the system. </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new role into the system.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:In the select options even when the 'View Details' is selected, the user is lead to the 'Modify' screen which is editable.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:Trying to delete a role provokes an exception. The resulting page states that an error has occured and exception is "java.sql.SQLException: Parameter index out of range."</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: A change in role privileges should ideally be followed by a message to the affected users (bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:the slide rule(A-Z) produces incorrect results when no records exist starting with the character that was clicked(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: It may be nice to see the users assigned to each role. This may be useful when role permissions need to be modified and the administrator needs to be aware of the users who would be affected by a change in user privileges (bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section>InsertRoleForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a New Role</title>
<description>This page will let you Add/update the roles present in the system. Also lets you change the permissions. The permissions can be changed or set for each every module separately depending on the role.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking the update button can do the update of the role</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:  While adding a new Role, have a "Check All" for permissions across modules as well as for columns withing modules</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Change the disabled checkboxes to "--" like on the modify role page</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section>RoleDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Update Role </title>
<description>This page will let you update the roles present in the system. Also lets you change the permissions. The permissions can be changed or set for each every module separately depending on the role.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The update of the role can be done by clicking the update button </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Under "Tickets", there are two entries for "Reports". UPDATE: The reports permission for tickets was not in the build script for permissions(permissions.xml). Some how it got added twice on ds21.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: If the user does not have permission to 'Re-assign', the update button in Re-assign is hidden. It might be a better idea to provide a label actually informing the user about the lack of permissions. Same problem in 'Personel Information' edit option.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:When permission for 'My Profile' is revoked, the display in the welcome page is distorted with multiple frames and same content in multiple frames.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When the permission for ADD in 'My Home Page'/'My Tasks' is revoked and the user clicks on the 'My Tasks' button in the 'My Home Page' module, a warning script pops up warning about page errors.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When the permission for 'My Home Page'/'View Performance Dashboard ' has been revoked and the user clicks on the 'Welcome' tab in the 'My Homepage' module, this produces an error. </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When permission for 'Pipeline Mgmt'/'Opportunity Records' Access/view is revoked, clicking on 'View Components' in Pipeline management produces a permission error. Suggestion: Could remove the 'View Components' tab.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:'Campaign Manager' could be renamed as 'Communication manager'. The names are different here and in the menu.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: When the communication manager is selected from the menu, a list of possible options (5.....example dashboard, build groups..etc are shown to the user). When certain permission are revoed, clicking on either of the options returns an error page. It might be better to not show these options at all to the user if he/she does not have permissions.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:When permission for Access/view in 'Account Management'/'Accounts Records' has been revoked, pressing on the Account Management tab, shows an error page with the permission denied method. Might be a better idea to redirect to one of the other available options (Ex: add account, Reports ...etc). Similar case with tickets module.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: There are two groups of check boxes to control the 'Reports' in 'Tickets' module when actually only one is needed. </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:Even when the 'view' permissions to the 'Help' system are removed, the help icon still shows up at the top pf the screen.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:The access, view and control of the QA system, seem to be based on the Edit option leaving the other options as dummies.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:having "Add" and "Edit" permissions without "view" is immaterial, an errroneas permission set that has "add" and "edit" enabled and "view" disabled prevents the user from adding and editing since the link is unavailable to the user. A feature that automatically enables "view" when "add, edit or delete" is chosen would be appropriate(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:"System Configuration" is editable even if "edit" is disabled for software developer (bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Custom folders are editable (new groups can be added and deleted) even when "edit" is disabled, the "up" and "down" keys behave appropriatly though(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>Config</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Configure Modules </title>
<description>This is the Modules page.&#13;
&#13;
This page lets you configure modules that meet the needs of your organization including configuration of lookup lists and custom fields. There are four types of modules. Each module has different number of configure options. The changes in the module affect all the users</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on Tickets configures categories, Lookup Lists, Object Events, and Scheduled Events</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on Pipeline management configures only Lookup Lists</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on Account Management configures custom folders &amp; fields and also Lookup Lists</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on General contacts configures custom folders &amp; fields and also Lookup Lists</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>admin &gt; Setup &gt; Configure Modules &gt; Clicking on any of the modules has the same QA window for all the modules</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>ConfigDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Configuration Options </title>
<description>You can configure different options present in each module.The following are some of the configuration options that you might see in the modules. Some of these options are specific to the module so they might NOT be present in all the modules.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Scheduled Events: A timer triggers a customizable workflow process.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Object Events: The Action triggers customizable workflow process when a object is inserted, updated, deleted or selected.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Categories: This lets you create categories for the tickets, which can be of two types active and the other is a draft category.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Lookup Lists: You can view the List's name and edit it by clicking on the "Look up Lists</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Custom Folders and fields: For each of the contacts Custom Folders and fields can be added, which would let you enable or disable the folders. You can do this by clicking on the "Custom Folders &amp; Fields"</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Categories does not have a separate permission, it is linked to folders</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Clicking on object events  displays a blank page with a breif message informing an error(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>ModifyList</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Edit Lookup List </title>
<description>This page lets you edit and add the list items.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can create a new item type using the add button and add it to the existing list. You can position the item in the list using the up and down buttons, remove it using the remove button and also sort the list. The final changes can be saved using the &#147;save changes&#148; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>When a Contact Type is added to a FULL list, it cannot be seen till you SCROLL to the end of the list.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>The is no check for duplicates when entering contact types.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>If  you select multiple contact types to DELETE only the LAST ONE is Deleted</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>IE BUG: The Up and Down buttons throw errors if no item is selected ! </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: The list allows multiple items to be selected but only the first item among those selected is deleted(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: The "up"and "down" buttons are redundant(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>AdminFieldsFolder.do</action>
<section>AddFolder</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a New Folder</title>
<description>Add/Update the existing folder here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update the existing the folder, set the options for the records and the permissions for the users</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>AdminFieldsFolder.do</action>
<section>ModifyFolder</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Existing Folder</title>
<description>Update the existing folder here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update the existing the folder, set the options for the records and the permissions for the users</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>AdminConfig.do</action>
<section>ListGlobalParams</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Configure System </title>
<description>You can configure the system for the session timeout and set the time for the time out&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The "Edit" link will let you alter the time for which the users session ends</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AdminConfig.do</action>
<section>ModifyTimeout</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Timeout </title>
<description>The session timeout is the time in which a user will automatically be logged out if the specified period of inactivity is reached.&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The time out can be set by selecting the time from the drop down and clicking the update button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>Usage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Resource Usage Details</title>
<description>Current System Usage and Billing Usage Information is displayed</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The usage can be displayed for the current date or a custom date can be specified. This can be selected from the drop down of the date range</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The start date and the end date can be specified if the date range is "custom date range". The update can be done using the update button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Custom Date only shows 2 digit year - calculation is on  4 digit year OK.  Checked  2000 to 2004 and 2100 - 2104 got data and no data respectively but both show 00 and 04 as two digit year</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABLITY: For the custom date range, i can go into the future either for the start date or the end date. Also start date can be after the end date.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: When a an end date less the start date is provided, the user should be given a message rather than just  automatically re-adjusting to current date(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do </action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>DisableUserConfirm</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFieldsFolder.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Custom Folders </title>
<description>This page lists all the custom folders created in the general contacts; let's you edit them and also allow you to enable/disable the folders.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also enable or disable the custom folders by clicking the &#147;yes&#148; or &#147;no&#148; </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the custom folder will give details about that folder and also lets you add groups.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update an existing folder using the edit button under the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update an existing folder using the edit button under the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a folder to the general contacts module.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFieldsFolder.do</action>
<section>ListFolders</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Custom Folders </title>
<description>This page lists all the custom folders created in the general contacts; let's you edit them and also allow you to enable/disable the folders.&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also enable or disable the custom folders by clicking the &#147;yes&#148; or &#147;no&#148; </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update an existing folder using the edit button under the action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the custom folder will give details about that folder and also lets you add groups</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update an existing folder using the edit button under the action column </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a folder to the general contacts module. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>The BACK button on this page creates additional folders.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>NICE: a FLAG to indicate if the folder is set for "single/multiple" records </noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFields.do</action>
<section>ModifyField</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: Allows field length to be negative (bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>ListGlobalParams</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE:  works fine</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>ModifyTimeout</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE: Works OK</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminObjectEvents.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Object Events:</title>
<description>The list of Object Events are displayed along with the corresponding Triggered Processes.  The number of components and whether that Object Event is available or not is also shown.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the process details by clicking on the select button under the Action column or by clicking on the name of the Triggered Process.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the process details by clicking on the select button under the Action column or by clicking on the name of the Triggered Process.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>I don't understand what or why this page is supposed to do.   Edit button is not active and all the "ticket" boxes are checked.  Update as a interesting display but I couldn't figure it our.  The insert list is blank with nothing to do.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>BUG: HIGH Priority: page cannot be found. Error shown "The included page caused a problem. " </ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFieldsGroup.do</action>
<section>AddGroup</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Add a group</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add a group name and save it using the "save" button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFields.do</action>
<section>AddField</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>UpdateList</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>The Lookup List displays all the list names, which can be edited, the number of items can be known and the ones present can be previewed&#13;
&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click the "Edit" in the Action column to update a contact type or delete one </featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can preview all the items present in a List name using the drop down in the preview column </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminScheduledEvents.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: When no events are scheduled a message needs to shown saying the same</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>Config </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>EditLists</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Lookup Lists </title>
<description>The Lookup List displays all the list names, which can be edited, the number of items can be known and the ones present can be previewed</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click the "Edit" in the Action column to update a contact type or delete one</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can preview all the items present in a List name using the drop down in the preview column</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Notes under contact types apply to ALL lists about (Duplicates, Adding, &amp; Deleting).</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>NONE of the CHANGES to ANY LIST showed up when I checked in General Contacts. UPDATE: It is possible that you could be making changes to Account Contact Types</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFieldsGroup.do</action>
<section>ListGroups</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Folder Details</title>
<description>This page lists the folder details and the groups added to this folder. Each group can further have a custom field created or deleted. You can also place it in the desired position in the dropdown list.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also delete the folder and all the fields using the button &#147;Delete this folder and all fields&#148; present at the bottom of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The groups can also be moved up or down using the &#147;Up&#148; and &#147;Down&#148;.  They can also be edited and deleted using the &#147;edit&#148; and &#147;del&#148; links.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The custom field can also be edited and deleted using the corresponding links &#148;Edit&#148; and &#147;Del&#148;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The custom field created can be moved up or down for the display using the corresponding links &#148;Up&#148; and &#147;down&#148;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a custom field for the group using the &#147; Add a custom field&#148; link</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a group to the folder selected</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select the folder by using the drop down box under the general contacts module</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE:  (1) Column Listing of Records - N/page &amp; (2) Folder Records export to spreadsheet.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>DONE:</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>NOTE:  I find the term GROUP confusing definition easy to forget.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: A new "Group" is shown only at the end of the page, hence, when it is outside the view area, there is  no immediate visual imact of the successful addition unless the user scrolls down(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY/BUG: The Up/Down links allow custom fields to be moved across groups (This may cause unintentional errors)(bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminCategories.do</action>
<section>ViewActive</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Active Category Details</title>
<description>The four different levels for the "Active" and the "Draft" categories are displayed. The level1 has the category name, which is further classified into sub directories/levels. The level1 has the sublevel called level2 which in turn has sublevel called level3 and so on.&#13;
&#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the list of categories displayed in level1 shows you its sub levels or sub-directories present level2 and clicking on which in turn would show its subdirectories in level3 and so on.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select to display either the Active Categories or the Draft Categories by clicking on the tabs &#147;Active Categories&#148; and &#147;Draft Categories&#148; respectively.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminCategories.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Draft Category Details</title>
<description>The four different levels for the active and the draft categories are displayed. The level1 has the category name, which is further classified into sub directories/levels. The level1 has the sublevel called level2 which in turn has sublevel called level3 and so on.  The draft categories can be edited and activate. The activated draft categories would be then reflected in the Active Categories list. The modified/updated drafted category can also be reverted to its original state.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The activated list can be brought back / reverted to the active list by clicking the &#147;Revert to Active List&#148;</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can activate each level by using the &#147;Activate now&#148; button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the draft categories you can edit your category using the edit button present at the bottom of each level.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select to display either the Active Categories or the Draft Categories by clicking on the tabs &#147;Active Categories&#148; and &#147;Draft Categories&#148; respectively.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the list of categories displayed in level1 shows you its sub levels or sub-directories present level2 and clicking on which in turn would show its subdirectories in level3 and so on.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Trying to save the items in a level after editing them should not ask for a confirmation</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: The first time you go to DRAFT categories you cannot navigate all of the category levels</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>JAVASCRIPT:Draft Categories-&gt;Edit Categories-&gt;Click on rename button without selecting any item. This pops an error:itemList[].description is not an object</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG:Categories-&gt;Draft Categories(Level 1)-&gt;Edit-&gt;Click on an item to rename-&gt;click Rename-&gt;now select a differenct item-&gt;Edit the description in the text box on the left-&gt;Add-&gt; this edits the current item instead of the original one.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>InsertUserForm </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>UpdateUser</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>AddUser</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>USAGE: When I create a new User, I can select a previous date for his account to expire. Is this valid? Also when i create a new account and view the details, it shows me that that the new user i just created had a last login on - 'The time i created this account'. Is this valid?</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Error: when I create a new role which has none of the privileges available in the system, and then i create a new user with that role. If i login as that user. I get a page where i can see the user name on the top but get an error in place of the actual menu.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>UserDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>User Details</title>
<description>This form provides the administrator with more information about the user, namely information pertaining to the users login history and view points.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The "Modify" button in the "Details" tab provides a quick link that allows the users information to be modified without having to browse back to the previous window.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "Employee Link" in the 'Primary Information" table header provides a quick link to view the users contact information.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "Details" tab displays the information about the user in a non-editable format.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The "Disable" button provides a quick link to disable/inactivate the user.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>Can't see which contact this user is associated with.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY:An account can be created which can expire backwards in time. </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: Clicking on "Employee Link" forwards you to "My Home Page". Does not feel appropriate.(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: When "Details-&gt;Modify" user details is chosen and the user goes to another tab and then clicks on details again, only the non-editable view is provided (bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DISPLAY: when you set up permissions for general contacts with just the seach permissions and not the add permission, it shows redundant seperators '|'. </noteDescription>
<noteDescription>QUESTION: Should every role in the system start with a minimal set of permissions under each module ? Otherwise the display when the user with such a role logs in is screwed up.</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: Giving a role, access to just the home page module and the general contacts module with the least set of permissions causes a bug. When you log into the system as an user with that particular role, it will show the two modules, but clicking on the General contacts will take you back to the home page module.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section>ListRoles </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>InsertViewpoint </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>InsertViewpoint</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>DISPLAY:When I select a contact whose name is really long say - 'Ananth Balasubramanyam', the [Change Contact] and [Clear Contact] are misplaced!</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>This is the Admin system.&#13;
&#13;
You are looking at the Admin System home page. Here you can manage the system by reviewing its usage, configuring specific modules and system parameters.  &#13;
</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The user and module  section allows the administrator to manage users, roles, role hierarchy and manage modules.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The global parameters and server configuration module allows the administrator to set session timeout parameter.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The usage section allows the administrator to view the total number of users, memory used, and system usage parameters for various time intervals.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The administration module is divided into distinct categories like managing the  users, module configuration, setting the global parameters, server configuration and for monitoring system usage and resources.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Reorder the blocks on the page moving "Usage" below "Global Parameters"</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>FEATURE: Blue Line Menu -- ( Users, Roles, Usage )</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>Exception when (roberts) chooses Modify Users : No such attribute c.type_id</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>BUG: On clicking "Manage Roles" the browsing sequence shows "Setup -&gt; View Roles"(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY/BUG: On Clicking "Check system resource" the navigation sequence shows "Setup -&gt; usage"(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>APPEARANCE: "s" and "r" are lower case in "Check system resources" and is hence inconsistent compared to the other links(bpk)</noteDescription>
<noteDescription>USABILITY: If 'Session Timeout " remains the only parameter that can be set, the nomenclature of the link "Global Parameters and Server Configuration" should be changed to indicate that more clearly (bpk)</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Auto Guide" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>Auto Guide Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>Auto Guide Detail</detailDescription>
</module>
<module name="Project Management" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>Project Management Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>Project Management Detail</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Lists_Categories</subSection>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagementFiles.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>BUG: When creating a new project, error checking for date not performed. Example, the start date could be already past.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter </section>
<subSection>Lists_Categories</subSection>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>File_Library</subSection>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes>
<noteDescription>UI: Better spacing among the column names would make it easier for the user to read.</noteDescription>
</notes>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>PersonalView</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagementRequirements.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Help" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>Help Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>Help Detail</detailDescription>
</module>
<module name="Demo" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>Demo Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>Demo Detail</detailDescription>
</module>
<module name="System" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>System Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>System Detail</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Search.do</action>
<section>SiteSearch </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Search.do</action>
<section>SiteSearch</section>
<subSection/>
<title>General Search</title>
<description>You can search the system for data associated with a particular key term. This can be done using the search data text box present on the left side of the window. The data associated with the corresponding key term is looked for in different modules for a match and the results are displayed per module. The search results are shown with detail description.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the different links of the search results will direct you to the corresponding details in the modules. </featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
</helpSystem>
