<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<helpSystem>
<module name="My Home Page" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>This is the &amp;quot;Home Page&amp;quot;. The top set of tabs shows the individual modules that you can access. The second row are the functions available to you in this module.
If you are looking for a particular module or function you have seen during training or on someone else's machine, and it's NOT visible, then it probably means that you do not have permission for that module or function.

Permissions within the system are assigned to Roles and then Users are assigned to Roles by the System Administrator.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>The Home Page has several main features.

Welcome: This is the welcome page. Here you will see a calendar of all of your upcoming alerts in the system, as well as for users that report to you.

Mailbox: The message system is designed to support INTERNAL business messaging needs and to prepare OUTGOING emails to addresses who are already in the system. Messaging is NOT a normal email replacement. It will not send email to addresses assigned &amp;quot;on-the-fly&amp;quot; and it will not receive OUTSIDE email.

Tasks: Tasks allows you to create and assign tasks. Tasks created can be assigned to the creator of the task or an employee working in the system. This page lists the tasks present along with their priorities, due dates and age.

Action Lists: Action Lists allow you to create a list of contacts that are related in some way. For each of the contacts in a list, you can add calls, opportunities, tickets, tasks or send a message, which would correspondingly show up in their respective tabs. For example, adding a ticket to the contact would be reflected in the Ticket module.

Re-assignments: You can reassign data from one employee to another employee as long as each employee reports to you. The data can be of different types related to accounts, contacts, opportunities, activities, tickets etc, which the newly reassigned employee could view.

Settings: This feature allows you to modify the information about yourself and your location, and also change your password to the system.</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyCFS.do</action>
<section>Home</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>You are looking at Home Page view, which has a dashboard view of all your assigned tasks, tickets, assignments, calls you have to make, and accounts that need attention. This view is based on a time selected from the calendar; by default it shows the schedule for the next seven days. You can optionally view the calendar of those below you in your hierarchy.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the accounts that need attention</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can make calls with the contact information readily accessible</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the tasks assigned to you</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the tickets assigned to you</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>You can view your calendar and the calendars of those who work for you</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips>
<tipDescription>Assign due dates for tasks so that you can be alerted</tipDescription>
</tips>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>Inbox</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Mailbox</title>
<description>The messaging feature is designed to support INTERNAL business messaging needs and to prepare OUTGOING emails to addresses who are already in the system. Messaging is NOT a normal email replacement. It will not send email to address assigned &amp;quot;on-the-fly&amp;quot; and it will not receive OUTSIDE email.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The select button can be used to view the details, reply, forward or delete a particular message.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new message</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the message will show the details of the message</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The drop down can be used to select the messages present in the inbox, sent messages, or archived ones</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Sort on one of the column headers by clicking on the column of your choice</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>CFSNoteDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>This page shows the message details, shows who sent the mail, when it was received and also the text in the mail box.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can reply, archive, forward or delete each message by clicking the corresponding button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>NewMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>New Message</title>
<description>Sending mail to other users of the system</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A new message can be composed either to the contacts or the employees present in the recipients list. The options field can be checked to send a copy to the employees task list apart from sending the employee an email.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>ReplyToMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Reply Message</title>
<description>This pages lets you reply to email. You can also select the list of recipients for your email by clicking the Add Recipients link.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can send the email by clicking the send button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add to the list of recipients by using the link &amp;quot;Add Recipients&amp;quot;</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click the check box to send an Internet email to the recipients</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Type directly in the Body test field to modify the message</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>SendMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>This page shows the list of recipients for whom your email has been sent to</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>ForwardMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forward message</title>
<description>Each message can be forwarded to any number of recipients</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add the list of recipients by using the link &amp;quot;Add Recipients&amp;quot; and also click the check box which would send an email to the recipients</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can send the email by clicking the send button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can edit the message by typing directly in the Body text area</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Tasks</title>
<description>Tasks created can be assigned to the owner/creator of the task or an employee working in the system. This page lists the tasks present along with their priorities, their due dates and age.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add a quick task. This task would have just the description and whether the task is personal or not</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For each of the existing tasks, you can view, modify, forward or delete the tasks by clicking on the Action button, and making a selection.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select to view your tasks or tasks assigned by you to others working under you. Each can be viewed in three different modes. i.e. the completed tasks, uncompleted tasks or both.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a detailed (advanced) task, where you can set up the priority, status, whether the task is shared or not, task assignment, give the estimated time and add some detailed notes for it.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section>New</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Advanced Task</title>
<description>Allows an advanced task to be created</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Link this task to a contact and when you look at the task list, there will be a link to the contact record next to the task, allowing you to go directly to the contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Filling in a Due Date will make ths task show up on that date in the Home Page calendar.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Making the task personal will hide it from your hierarchy.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign a task to people lower than you in your hierarchy.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Marking a task as complete will document the task as having been done, and immediately remove it from the Task List.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyTasksForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forwarding a Task</title>
<description>A task can be forwarded to any of the recipients. Recipients can either be users of the system or any of the contacts stored in the system. Checking the options fields check box indicates that if the recipient is a user of the system, then a copy of the task is also send to the recipient's mailbox.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Allows you to forward a task to one or more users of the system. Checking the options fields check box indicates that if the recipient is a user of the system, then a copy of the task is send to the recipient's Internet email.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Subject line is mandatory</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add more text to the body of the message by typing directly in the Body text area</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify task</title>
<description>Allows you to modify any infomation about a task</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Due dates will show on the Home Page calendar</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Completing a task will remove it from the task list</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign a task to someone lower than you in your heirarchy</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can Add or Change the contact that this task is linked to. When viewing the task, you will be able to view the contact information with one click.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyActionLists.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Action Lists</title>
<description>Action Lists allow you to create new Action Lists and assign contacts to the Action Lists created. For each of the contacts in a list, you can add a call, opportunity, ticket, task or send a message, which would correspondingly show up in their respective tabs. For example, adding a ticket to the contact would be reflected in the Ticket module.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view all the in progress Action Lists, completed lists, or both together.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also keep track of the progress of your contacts. The number of them Completed and the Total are shown in the Progress Columns.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new Action List with a description and status. You can select the contacts for this new Action List. For each of the contacts in the Action List, you can select a corresponding action with the Action Button: view details, modify contact, add contacts or delete the Action List.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyActionContacts.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Action Contacts</title>
<description>This page will list out all the contacts present for the particular contact list. This also shows the status of the call, opportunity, ticket, task, or the message associated with the contact. This also shows when the contact information was last updated.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the contact name will give you a pop up with more details about the contact and also about the related folders, calls, messages and opportunities.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add contacts to the list and also Modify the List using &amp;quot;Add Contacts to list&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Modify List&amp;quot; respectively.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For the Action List you can also view all the in progress contacts, completed contacts or both.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For each of the contacts you can add a call, opportunity, ticket, task or send a message, which would correspondingly appear in their respective tabs. For example, adding a ticket to the contact would be reflected in the Ticket tab.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyActionLists.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Action List</title>
<description>Allows you to add an action list. Basically, you describe the group of contacts you will add, then visually design a query to generate the group of contacts.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Select where the contacts will come from (General Contact, Account Contacts) in the From dropdown.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Enter some search text, depending on the Operator you chose.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choose an Operator based on the Field you chose.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choose one of the many Field Names on which to base your query.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can Add or Remove contacts manually with the Add/Remove Contacts link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add your query with the Add button at the bottom of the query frame. You can have multipe queries that make up the criteria for a group. You will get the result of all the queries.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Save the Action List and generate the list of contacts by clicking the Save button at the bottom or top of the page.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyActionLists.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Action</title>
<description>The Action Lists details, like the description and status of the Action Lists, can be modified.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can check the status checkbox to indicate that the New Action List is complete.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The details of the New Action List can be saved by clicking the save button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Reassignments.do</action>
<section>Reassign</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Re-assignments</title>
<description>A user can reassign data from one employee to another employee working under him. The data can be of different types related to accounts, contacts opportunities, activities, tickets etc, which the newly reassigned employee could view in his schedule.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Click Update at the bottom of the page to save your reassignment, Cancel to quit the page without saving, and Reset to reset all the fields to their defaults and start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choose a User to reassign data from in the top dropdown. Only users below you in your hierarchy will be present here.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Select one or more To Users in the To User column to reassign the various assets to. The number of each type of asset available to be reassigned is shown in parentheses after the asset in the first column.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>MyCFS.do</action>
<section>MyProfile</section>
<subSection/>
<title>My Settings</title>
<description>This is the personal settings page, where you can modify the information about yourself, your location and also change your password to the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The location of the employee can be changed, i.e. the time zone can be changed by clicking on &amp;quot;Configure my location.&amp;quot;</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update your personal information by clicking on &amp;quot;Update my personal information.&amp;quot;</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can change your password by clicking on &amp;quot;Change my password.&amp;quot;</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSProfile.do</action>
<section>MyCFSProfile</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Personal Information</title>
<description>This page lets you update/add your personal information.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Save your changes by clicking the Update button at the top or bottom of the page. The Cancel button forgets the changes and quits the page. The Reset button resets all fields to their original values so you can start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The only required field is your last name, but you should fill in as much as you can to make the system as useful as possible. Email address is particularly useful.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSSettings.do</action>
<section>MyCFSSettings</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Location Settings</title>
<description>You can change your location settings</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The location settings can be changed by selecting the time zone from the drop down list and clicking the update button to update the settings.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>MyCFSPassword.do</action>
<section>MyCFSPassword</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Update password</title>
<description>Your password to the system can be changed</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update your password by clicking on the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section>ListTasks</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features>
<featureDescription>For each of the existing tasks, you can view, modify, forward or delete the tasks by clicking on the Action button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a quick task. This task would have just the description and whether the task is personal or not</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add or update a detailed task called advanced task, wherein you can set up the priority, the status, whether the task is shared or not, also is the task assigned to self or someone working under the owner of the tasks, give the estimated time and add some detailed notes in it.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Checking the existing task's check box indicates that the particular task is completed.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select to view your tasks or tasks assigned by you to others. Each task can be viewed in three different modes i.e. the completed tasks, uncompleted tasks or all the tasks.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyCFS.do</action>
<section>Home </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyTasksForward.do</action>
<section>SendMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyCFSProfile.do</action>
<section>UpdateProfile</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>CFSNoteTrash</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyActionContacts.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>No introduction available</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyActionContacts.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>You can add the new Action List and also select the contacts to be present in the Action List.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add the new Action List here. Along with description and the status you need to select the contacts you want in this Action List. You can populate the list in two ways. The first is to use the Add/Remove contacts.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The second is to define the criteria to generate the list. Once it's generated we can add them to the selected criteria and contacts by using the add feature present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyTasks.do</action>
<section>ListTasks </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyCFSInbox.do</action>
<section>Inbox </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>MyActionContacts.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Action List</title>
<description>Allows you to manually add or remove contacts to or from an existing Action List.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Check new contacts to add them to your list, uncheck existing contacts to remove them from your list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Select All Contact, My Contacts or Account Contacts from the dropdown at the top.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Finish by clicking Done at the bottom of the page.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reassignments.do</action>
<section>DoReassign</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TaskForm.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Addition of a new Advanced task that can be assigned to the owner or any other employee working  under him.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add or update a detailed task called advanced task, wherein you can set up a priority, status, whether the task is shared or not, also is the task assigned to you or someone working under the owner of the tasks, give the estimated time and add some detailed notes to it.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Contacts" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>The purpose of this module is for the users to view contacts and add new contacts. You can also search for contacts as well as export contact data.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>The Contacts module has three main features&#13;
&#13;
Add: A new contact can be added into the system. The contact can be a general contact, or one that is associated with an account. All the details about the contact like the email address, phone numbers, address and some additional details can be added.&#13;
&#13;
Search: Use this page to search for contacts in the system based on different filters.&#13;
&#13;
Export: Contact data can be exported and displayed in different formats, and can be filtered in different ways. The Export page also lets you view the data, download it, and show the number of times the exported data has been downloaded.&#13;
&#13;
Import: The contacts importer is a sophisticated tool for importing contacts into DHV CRM. Features include the ability to custom/auto map fields to application properties, perform error checking and examine import progress.</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Contact</title>
<description>A new contact can be added to the system. The contact can be a general contact, or one that is associated with an account. All the details about the contact such as the email address, phone numbers, address and some additional details can be added.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select the contact category using the radio button and if the contact category is someone permanently associated with an account, then you can select the contact using the &amp;quot;select&amp;quot; next to it.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can save the details about the employee using the &amp;quot;Save&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Save &amp; New&amp;quot; button saves the details of the employee and also opens up a blank form start another contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The only mandatory field is the Last Name, however, it is important to fill in as much as possible. These fields can be used for various types of queries later.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The contact type can be selected using the &amp;quot;select&amp;quot; link next to the contact type.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>SearchContactsForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search Contacts</title>
<description>Use this page to search for contacts in the system based on different filters</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>If the contact already exists in the system, you can search for that contact by name, company, title, contact type or source.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Reports</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Export</title>
<description>Contact data can be exported and displayed in different formats, and can be filtered in different ways. The Export page also lets you view the data, download it, and shows the number of times the exported data has been downloaded.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated by choosing the &amp;quot;Generate new export&amp;quot; link at the top of the page</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the dropdown to choose which data to display: the list of all the exported data in the system or only your own.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed in html format by clicking on the report name. The exported data can also be downloaded in CSV format or deleted by clicking the Select button in the action field.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>GenerateForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Exporting data</title>
<description>Use this page to generate a Contacts export report.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add all the fields or add / delete single fields from the report by using the buttons in the middle of the page. First highlight a field on the left to add or a field on the right to delete.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the Up and Down buttons on the right to sort the fields.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Subject is mandatory. Select which set of contacts the export will come from with Criteria. Select the Primary sort with the Sorting dropdown.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Click the Generate button when you are ready to generate the exported report.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ModifyContact</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Contact</title>
<description>The details about the contact can be modified here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update, cancel or reset the details of the contact using the corresponding buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do </action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>The calls related to the contact are listed here along with the other details such as the length of the call and the date the call was made. You can also add a call.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click on the select button under the action field to view, modify, forward or delete a call.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the subject of the call will give complete details about the call.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a call associated with a contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a Call</title>
<description>A new call can be added which is associated with the contact. The type of call can be selected using the drop down list present.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The save button lets you create a new call which is associated with the call.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>SendMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>ViewOpps</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>All the opportunities associated with the contact are shown here, with its best possible total and the when the opportunity was last modified. You can filter the different types of opportunities using the drop down.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click the select button under the action column for viewing, modifying and deleting an opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the opportunity will show a detailed description of the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choosing the different types of opportunities from the drop down can filter the display.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add an opportunity associated with a contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>Calls associated with the contacts are displayed. The call details are shown with the length of the call, associated notes, alert description, alert date etc.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or forward each call using the corresponding buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a component</title>
<description>A component can be added to an opportunity and associated to any employee present in the system. The component type can also be selected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &amp;quot;select&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employees present using the dropdown list present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>DetailsOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about the components here, such as the status, the guess amount and the current stage. A new component can also be added to an existing opportunity.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>An opportunity can be renamed or deleted using the buttons present at the bottom of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the select button lets you view, modify or delete the details about a component.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the component shows the details about that component.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new component associated with the contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>DetailsComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details</title>
<description>This page shows the details about the opportunity such as the probability of closing the opportunity, the current stage of the opportunity, etc.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify or delete the opportunity using the modify or delete button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modifying call details</title>
<description>You can modify all the details of the calls.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The type of the call can be selected using the drop down list and all the other details related to the call are updated using the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>InsertFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>UpdateFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ListContacts</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Clone</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>AddFolderRecord</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>SearchContacts </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>MessageDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>The selected message is displayed with the message text and attachments, if any.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click the attachments or the surveys link present along with the message text.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>SaveComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>This page shows the details of an opportunity, such as the probability of closing the opportunity, the current stage of the opportunity, etc.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify or delete the opportunity using the modify or the delete button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>SearchContacts</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Contacts</title>
<description>This page shows the list of contacts in the system. The name of the contact along with the company name and phone numbers are shown. If the name of the contact is an account, it's shown right next to it. You can also add a contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the action field to view, modify, clone or delete a contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the name of the contact will display additional details about the contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a contact using the link &amp;quot;Add a Contact&amp;quot; at the top of the page</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ExportReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>Data can be filtered, exported and displayed in different formats. This also shows the number of times an exported data has been downloaded.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed as a .csv file or in html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action field is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated, which lets you choose from the contacts list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ContactDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contact Details</title>
<description>The details about the contact are displayed here along with the record information containing the owner, the employee who entered the details and finally the person who last modified these details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, clone, or delete the details of the contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ViewMessages</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>This page lists all the messages associated with the contact, showing the name of the message, its date and its status.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the message displays more details about the message.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the messages in two different views, i.e. all the messages present or the messages created/assigned by you.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardCall</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forwarding a call</title>
<description>The details of the calls that are associated with a contact can be forwarded to different employees present in the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select the list of the recipients to whom you want to forward the particular call to by using the &amp;quot;Add Recipients&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>SendCall</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of recipients</title>
<description>This page shows the list of recipients to whom the call details that are associated with a contact have been forwarded.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>ModifyComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modifying the component details</title>
<description>The details of the component associated with an opportunity can be modified.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &amp;quot;select&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any user using the dropdown list provided.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>ModifyOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify the opportunity</title>
<description>The description of the opportunity can be renamed / updated.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update or cancel the information changed using the &amp;quot;update&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;cancel&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>Fields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Folder Records</title>
<description>Each contact can have several folders, and each folder further can have multiple records. You can add a record to a folder. Each record present in the folder displays the record name, when it was entered, who modified this record last and when.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The folders can be selected using the drop down list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click on the record name, to view the folder record details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details and modify them by clicking the select button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new record to a folder using the &amp;quot;Add a record to this folder&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The folders can be selected using the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section>ModifyFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Folder Record</title>
<description>Here you can modify the details of the folder record.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The changes made in the details of the folders can be updated or canceled using the &amp;quot;Update&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Cancel&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>UpdateOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>All the opportunities associated with the contact are shown here, with its best possible total and the when the opportunity was last modified. You can filter the different types of opportunities that can be selected using the drop down and display them.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the action column for viewing, modifying and deleting an opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the opportunity will display the details of the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choosing the different types of opportunities from the drop down filters the display.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add an opportunity associated with a contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ContactsList.do</action>
<section>ContactList</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Enables you to select contacts from a list and then add them to the Action List. It shows the name of the contact along with his email and type of contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can filter the contact list in three different views. The views are all contacts, your contacts and Account contacts.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Check any or all the contacts from the list you want to assign to your action List.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contact detail page</title>
<description>The contact details associated with the account are displayed here. The details such as the account number, email address, phone number and the addresses are shown.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify, clone or delete the contact by clicking the corresponding button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can associate calls, messages and opportunities with each of the contacts already in the system.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>ViewMessages</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Messages</title>
<description>The list of messages related to the contacts.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view all the messages related to the contact or only the messages owned by you. (My messages)</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ContactForm.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Adding/Modifying a new contact</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This is for adding or updating a new detailed employee record into the system. The last name is the only mandatory field in creating an employee record, However it is important to add as much information as you can.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContacts.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>If a contact already exists in the system, you can search for that contact by name, company, title, contact type or source, by typing the search term in the appropriate field, and clicking the Search button.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>If the contact already exists in the system, you can search for that contact by name, company, title, contact type or source, by typing the search term in the appropriate field, and clicking the Search button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can filter, export, and display data in different formats by clicking the Export link at the top of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Click Add to add a new contact into the application.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You may also import your existing contacts from microsoft outlook( or comparable cvs format) into the application.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsImports.do</action>
<section>New</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Import</title>
<description>This page allows you to upload a cvs file and import contacts from the uploaded file.  Once uploaded, the import is tagged as &amp;quot;Import Pending.&amp;quot;&#13;
&#13;
Once the file is uploaded, the import process can be started off by mapping the contents (the columns) of the file to the the fields of the application.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsImports.do</action>
<section>InitValidate</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Process Import</title>
<description>This page displays the first five records of the cvs file, and then maps known columns to the fields of the application. It allows you to cusomize your import by allowing you to map the columns of the cvs file to the fields of the application.&#13;
&#13;
If the uploaded file is erroneous in its content (not in cvs format, or if the number of headings and columns do not match), you are not allowed to process the import until the errors are corrected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page is four sections.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The 'Import Properties&amp;quot; section displays the file that was imported and the Name provided to identify the import.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The next section displays the heading of the import file and four records following it.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;general errors/warnings&amp;quot; section displays errors in the CVS file.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Field Mappings&amp;quot; section lists all the columns in the file based on the heading and maps known columns in the file to the fields in the application.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Against each listed column heading in the field mappings section is a drop list that displays the list of fields that exist to store contact information in the CRM application. Using this drop list you may modify automatically identified field mappings and map those that the application failed to automatically identify.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>Apart from email addresses, you may not map more than one column of the cvs file to the same field of the application. An attempt to do so, displays error messages against the rows for which such a mapping was specified.</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ExternalContactsImports.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contact Imports</title>
<description>This page lists contact imports and their status. An import may either be unprocessed, queued for processing, running, awaiting approval or approved.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>An import goes though various stages before finally being approved and locked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The first stage of an import is the unprocessed stage. In this stage, an import file in cvs format is uploaded to the application. In this stage the import is tagged as 'Import Pending.'</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the second stage, the unprocessed contacts file that was uploaded is queued to be processed. To do so, you need to map the various columns in the cvs file to the relevant contact fields(names, emails, telephones, etc) in the application. When the columns are mapped, the import is queued to be processed. Only one import is processed at a time, hence subsequent imports are queued until all previous imports are processed.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When an import is being processed (or running) the CRM application reads the cvs file, and creates contacts in the application. After the entire file is processed, the contacts are tagged as 'Pending approval'.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the contacts are tagged as &amp;quot;Pending approval&amp;quot;,  you may examine whether the import worked as it was expected, and decide whether the imported contacts can be used for the due course of business. If you find that the mappings you specified were erroneous or insufficient, you may delete the import (which also deletes all contacts of the import) and create another one.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>During the import process, some records in the cvs file may fail to import to the application. The failure is usually due to an incorrect specification of phone number, or very large names, etc. Such failed records are copied to an &amp;quot;error file&amp;quot; and available for you to examine. You may correct the information in the error file and run an import for this file alone, or you may add the records to the application manually.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When an import is approved, the contacts of this import are visible in the contacts list view and these contacts are ready to be used in the application.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When a import is approved, its results can only be viewed. The contacts of an approved import cannot be deleted en mass.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Pipeline" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>Pipeline helps in creating opportunities or leads in the company. Each opportunity helps to follow-up on a lead, which might eventually turn into a client. Here you can create an opportunity, search for an existing opportunity in the system, or export the data in different formats. The dashboard displays a progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the hierarchy of the owner of the opportunity.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Pipeline System has four main features:

Dashboard: Gives you a quick, visual overview of opportunities.

Add: This page lets you add an opportunity into the system. Here a new opportunity can be added by giving the description of the opportunity. You can add a component that is associated with the opportunity. Each component can be assigned to an employee and the type of the component can be selected. For each component the probability of closing the component, the date estimated, the best guess for closing the deal and the duration for that component can be entered.

Search: You can search for an opportunity already existing in the system based on different filters.

Export: The data can be filtered, exported and displayed in different formats.</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Dashboard</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>The progress chart is displayed in different views for all the employees working under the owner or creator of the opportunity. The opportunities are shown, with their names and the probable gross revenue associated with that opportunity. Finally the list of employees reporting to a particular employee/supervisor is also shown below the progress chart</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the owner or creator of the opportunity. The views can be selected from the drop down box present under the chart. The mouse over or a click on the break point on the progress chart will give the date and exact value associated with that point.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The opportunities created are also shown, with their names and the probable gross revenue associated with that opportunity. Clicking on the opportunities shows a details page for the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The list of employees reporting to a particular employee/supervisor is also shown below the progress chart. Clicking on an employee shows the Opportunity page from that person's point of view. You can then work your way back up the chain by clicking the Up One Level link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Opportunity</title>
<description>This page lets you add a opportunity into the system.

Here a new opportunity can be added by giving a description of the opportunity, then adding a component that is associated with the opportunity. An opportunity can have one or more components. Each component can be assigned to a different employee and the type of the component can be selected. For each component the probability of closing the component, the date estimated, the best guess for closing the deal and the duration for that component are required.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The probability of Close, Estimated Close Date, Best Guess Estimate (what will the gross revenue be for this component?), and Estimated Term (over what time period?), are mandatory fields.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to yourself or one of the users in your hierarchy.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Component Description is a mandatory field. Be descriptive as you will be using this to search on later.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the Save button to save your changes and exit, Cancel to cancel your changes and exit, and Reset to cancel your changes and start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Enter an Alert Description and Date to remind yourself to follow up on this component at a later date.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You must associate the component with either a Contact or an Account. Choose one of the radio buttons, then one of the Select links.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>SearchForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search Opportunities</title>
<description>You can search for an existing opportunity based on different filters.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Existing opportunities can be searched using this feature. Opportunities can be searched on description, account name, or contact name with whom the opportunity is associated. It can also be searched by current progress / stage of the opportunity or the closing date range.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>LeadsReports.do</action>
<section>Default</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Export Data</title>
<description>Pipeline data can be exported, filtered, and displayed in different formats. You can also view the data online in html format, and see number of times the exported data has been downloaded.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed or downloaded as a .csv file or in html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action column is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated by choosing from the contacts list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>SearchOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Reports</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsComponents.do</action>
<section>ModifyComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Component</title>
<description>You can modify the component details associated with an opportunity in a pipeline.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Component Description is a mandatory field</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use Update at the top or bottom to save your changes, Cancel to quit this page without saving, and Reset to reset all fields to default and start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add an Alert Description and Date to alert you via a CRM System Message to take a new action</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Probability of close, Estimated Close Date (when you will get the revenue), Best Guess Estimate (how much revenue you will get), and Estimated Term (what term the revenue will be realized over) are all the mandatory fields.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select a Component Type from the dropdown. These component types are configurable by your System Administrator.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any User using the dropdown list present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a call</title>
<description>You can add a new call here associated with the opportunity.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The type of the call can be a phone, fax or in person. Some notes regarding the call can be noted. You can add an alert to remind you to follow up on this call.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Contact dropdown is automatically populated with the correct contacts for the company or account you are dealing with.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>ModifyOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify the opportunity:</title>
<description>The description of the opportunity can be modified / updated.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update or cancel the information changed using the &amp;quot;update&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;cancel&amp;quot; button present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Document</title>
<description>Modify the Subject or filename of a document.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update the details of the documents using the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>GenerateForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsComponents.do</action>
<section>DetailsComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details</title>
<description>The component details for the opportunity are shown here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component details are shown with additional options for modifying and deleting the component.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Upload a new version of document</title>
<description>You can upload a new version of the document and the new version of the file can be selected and uploaded.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The document can be uploaded using the upload button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The new version of the document can be selected from your local computer using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>Search</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of components</title>
<description>The components resulted from the search are shown here. Different views of the components and its types are displayed. The name of the component with the estimated amount of money associated with the opportunity and the probability of that components being a success is shown. This also displays the time for closing the deal (term) and the organization name or the contact name if they are associated with the opportunity. A new opportunity can also be added.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>For each of the component you can view the details, modify the content or delete it completely using the select button in the Action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add an opportunity here by giving complete details about the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The search results for existing opportunities are displayed here.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>There are different views of the opportunities you can choose from the drop down list and the corresponding types for the opportunities.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>UpdateOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about the components here and also add a new component to a particular opportunity. Calls and the documents can be associated with the opportunity</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>In the Documents tab, documents associated with an opportunity can be added. This also displays the documents already linked with this opportunity and other details about the document. Details can be viewed, downloaded, modified or deleted by using the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the Calls tab you can add a call associated with the opportunity. This also displays the calls already linked with this opportunity and other details about the call. The call details can be viewed, modified, forwarded or deleted by using the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can rename or delete the opportunity itself using the buttons below.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify, view and delete the details of any particular component by clicking the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the Components tab, you can add a component. It also displays the status, amount and the date when the component will be closed.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>There are three tabs in each opportunity i.e. components, calls and documents.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You get the organization name or the contact name at the top, which on clicking will take you to the Account details.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCallsForward.do</action>
<section>ForwardCall</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forwarding a call</title>
<description>The details of calls associated with a contact can be forwarded to different users present in the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select the list of the recipients to whom you want to forward a call to by using the &amp;quot;Add Recipients&amp;quot; link. This will bring up a window with all users, from which you can then choose using check boxes.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can email a copy of the call to a user's Internet email by checking the Email check box.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add to the message by simply typing in the Body text box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>In the Documents tab, the documents associated with a particular opportunity can be added to, and viewed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The version of the particular document can be modified using the add version link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A document can be viewed, downloaded, modified or deleted by using the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A click on the subject of the document will show all the versions present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify call details</title>
<description>You can modify the details of the calls.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The type of the call can be selected using the drop down list and all the other details related to the call are updated using the update button</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>DetailsOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about an opportunity components here and also add a new component to a particular opportunity. Calls and documents can also be added to an opportunity or viewed by clicking on the appropriate tab.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>In the Calls tab you can add a call to the opportunity. This also displays the calls already linked with this opportunity and other details about the call. The call details can be viewed, modified, forwarded or deleted by using the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the Components tab, you can add a component. It also displays the status, amount and the date when the component will be closed.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>There are three tabs in each opportunity i.e. components, calls and documents.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can rename or delete the whole opportunity (not just one of these components) using the buttons at the bottom.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The organization or contact name appears on top, above the Components Tab, which when clicked, will take you to the Account details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify, view and delete the details of any component by clicking the select button in the Action column, on the far left.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the Documents tab, documents associated with the particular opportunity can be added. This also displays the documents already linked with this opportunity and other details about the document. Details can be viewed, downloaded, modified or deleted by using the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>Calls associated with the opportunity are shown. Calls can be added to the opportunity, and details about listed calls can be examined.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>In the Calls tab you can add a call associated with the opportunity. This also displays the calls already linked with this opportunity and other details about the call. The call details can be viewed, modified, forwarded or deleted by using the select button in the action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the call subject is clicked then complete details about the call are displayed.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section>ViewOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>The opportunities resulted from the search are shown here. Different views of the opportunities and its types are displayed. The name of the component with the estimated amount of money associated with the opportunity and the probability of that opportunity being a success are shown. This also displays the time for closing the deal (term) and the organization name or the contact name if they are associated with the opportunity.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>There are different views of the opportunities you can choose from the dropdown list and the corresponding types of the opportunities.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add an opportunity here by giving complete details about the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The search results for existing opportunities are displayed here.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For each of the components you can view the details, modify the content or delete it completely using the select button in the Action column. You can click on any of the component names, which shows more details about the component, such as the calls and documents associated with it.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Leads.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Pipeline helps in creating prospective opportunities or leads in the company. Each opportunity helps to follow up a lead, who might eventually turn into a client. Here you can create an opportunity, search for an existing opportunity in the system, export the data to different formats. The dashboard reflects the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the owner/creator of the opportunity.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The list of employees reporting to a particular employee/supervisor is also shown below the progress chart.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Opportunities are displayed, with name and probable revemue. Clicking on the opportunities displays more details of the opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the owner or creator of the opportunity. The views can be selected from the drop down box under the chart. The mouse over or a click on the break point on the progress chart will give the date and exact value associated with that point.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsComponents.do</action>
<section>SaveComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details</title>
<description>The component details for the opportunity are shown here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component details are shown with additional options for modifying and deleting the component.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsComponents.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a component</title>
<description>A component can be added to an opportunity and assigned to any employee in the system. The component type can also be selected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &amp;quot;select&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employee present using the dropdown list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>The calls associated with the opportunity are shown. Calls can be added to the opportunity.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>In the Calls tab you can add a call associated with the opportunity. This also displays the calls already linked with this opportunity and other details about the call. Call details can be viewed, modified, forwarded or deleted by using the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the call subject is clicked then it will display complete details about the call.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsCalls.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>Details about the call associated with the opportunity</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete and forward each of the calls.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Upload a document</title>
<description>New documents related to the opportunity can be uploaded into the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking the Upload button will upload the selected document into the system.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the Browse button opens a file browser on your own system. Simply navigate to the file on your drive that you want to upload and click Open. This will close the window and bring you back to the upload page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a very descriptive Subject for the file. This is a mandatory field.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>This shows all versions of the updated document. The name of the file with it's size, version and the number of downloads are shown here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>All the versions of the document can be downloaded from here. Simply select the version you want and click the Download link on the far left.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsReports.do</action>
<section>ExportList</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of exported data</title>
<description>The data present can be used to export data and display that in different formats. The exported data can be filtered in different ways. This would also let you view the data download it. This also shows the number of times an exported data has been downloaded</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed as a .csv file or in the html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action field is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated, which lets you choose from the contacts list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Click on the subject of the new export, the data is displayed in html format</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>LeadsReports.do</action>
<section>ExportForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Generating Export data</title>
<description>Generate an exported report from pipeline data</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Click the Generate button at top or bottom to generate the report from the fields you have included. Click cancel to quit and go back to the Export Data page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Highlight the fields you want to include in the left column and click the Add or All link. Highlight fields in the right column and click the Del link to remove them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the Sorting dropdown to sort the report by one of a variety of fields</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Use the Criteria dropdown to use opportunities from My or All Opportunities</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Subject is a mandatory field.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Accounts" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>You are looking at the Accounts module homepage, which has a dashboard view of all your accounts. This view is based on a date range selected from the calendar; by default it shows the schedule for the next seven days. You can optionally view the calendar of those below you in your hierarchy. The scheduled actions of each user can also be viewed. In the Accounts Module, new accounts can be added, existing accounts can be searched based on different filters, revenue for each account can be created/maintained and finally, data can be exported to different formats.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>The Accounts module has five main features.

Dashboard: Displays a dashboard view account contract expirations.

Add: Allows you to add a new account

Search: This page provides a search feature for the accounts present in the system

Revenue: Graphically visualizes revenue if the historical data is present in the system. All the accounts with revenue are shown along with a list of employees working under you under the progress chart. You can add accounts, search for the existing ones in the system based on different filters and export the data to different formats

Export: Data can be exported and displayed in different formats. The exported data can be filtered in different ways. You can view the data, download it, and see the number of times an exported report has been downloaded</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Dashboard</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>The date range can be modified which is shown in the right hand window by clicking on a specific date on the calendar. Accounts with contract end dates or other required actions appear in the right hand window reminding the user to take action on them. The schedule, actions, alert dates and contract end dates are displayed for user or the employees under him by using the dropdown at the top of the page. Clicking on the alert link will let the user modify the details of the account owner.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the alert link will let you modify the details of the account owner.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Accounts with contract end dates or other required actions will appear in the right hand window where you can take action on them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the schedule, actions, alert dates and contract end dates for yourself or your employees by using the dropdown at the top of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify the date range shown in the right hand window by clicking on a specific date on the calendar, or on one of the arrows to the left of each week on the calendar to give you a week's view. Clicking on &amp;quot;Back To Next 7 Days View&amp;quot; at the top of the right window changes the view to the next seven days. The day or week you are currently viewing is highlighted in yellow. Today's date is highlighted in blue. You can change the month and year using the dropdowns at the top of the calendar, and you can always return to today by using the Today link, also at the top of the calendar.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add an Account</title>
<description>A new account can be added here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Use the Insert button at top or bottom to save your changes, Cancel to quit without saving, and Reset to reset all the fields to their default values and start over.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>It's a faily straightforward &amp;quot;fill in the blanks&amp;quot; exercise. There should be a &amp;quot;Primary&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Business&amp;quot;, or &amp;quot;Main&amp;quot; version of phone/fax numbers and addresses because other modules such as Communications Manager use these to perform other actions.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Fill in as many fields as possible. Most of them can be used later as search terms and for queries in reports.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Depending on whether you have chosen Organization or Individual, there are mandatory description fields to fill out about the account.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Choose whether this account is an Organization or an Individual with the appropriate radio button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the Select link next to Account Type(s) will open a window with a variety of choices for Account Types. You cah choose and number by clicking the checkboxes to the left. It is important to use this feature as your choice(s) are used for searches and as the subject of querries in reports in other parts of the application.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Account</title>
<description>The details of an account can be modified here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The account owner can also be changed using the drop down list</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The account type can be selected using the &amp;quot;Select&amp;quot; button</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>This is for adding or updating account details. The last name or the organization name, based on the classification, is the only mandatory field in creating a new account. The type of account can be selected using the select option given next to the account type</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the Account has a contract, you should enter a contract end date in the fields provided. This will generate an icon on the Home Page and an alert for the owner of the account that action must be taken at a prearranged time.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contact Details</title>
<description>A contact can be associated with an account. The lists of the contacts associated with the account are shown along with the title.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify, clone and delete the contact by clicking the select button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the name of the contact is clicked, it shows details of that contact, with the options to modify, clone and delete the contact details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a contact, which is associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Fields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Folder Record Details</title>
<description>You create folders for accounts. Each folder can have one or more records associated with it, depending on the type of the folder. The details about records associated with the folder are shown</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Using the select button in the action column you can view details and modify the record.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click on the record type to view the folders details and modify them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new record can be added to the folder.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The folders can be populated by configuring the module in the admin tab.. The type of the folder can be changed using the drop down list shown.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Opportunities.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>Opportunities associated with the contact, showing the best guess total and last modified date.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Opportunities associated with the contact, showing the best guess total and last modified date.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add an opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Three types of opportunities are present which can be selected from the drop down list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the description of the opportunity is clicked, it will give you more details about the opportunity and the components present in it.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Revenue</title>
<description>The revenue associated with the account is shown here. The details about the revenue like the description, the date and the amount associated are displayed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>By clicking on the description of the revenue you get the details about that revenue along with the options to modify and delete its details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view your revenue or all the revenues associated with the account using the drop down box.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify and delete the details of the revenue by clicking the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add / update a new revenue associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Revenue Details</title>
<description>The revenue associated with the account is shown here. Details about the revenue such as the description, the date, and the amount associated are displayed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the description of the revenue displays its details, along with options to modify and delete them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view your revenue or all the revenues associated with the account using the drop down box.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify and delete the details of the revenue by clicking the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add / update a new revenue associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Revenue</title>
<description>Adding new revenue to an account</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Add new revenue to an account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Revenue</title>
<description>Here revenue details can be modified</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Fill in the blanks and use &amp;quot;Update&amp;quot; to save your changes or &amp;quot;Reset&amp;quot; to return to the original values.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>ViewTickets</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Details</title>
<description>This page shows the complete list of the tickets related to an account, and lets you add a new ticket</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the action column to view, modify or delete the ticket.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the ticket number will let you view the details, modify or delete the ticket.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new ticket.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>Here the documents associated with the account are listed. New documents related to the account can be added.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the documents can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Document versions can be updated by using the &amp;quot;add version&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new document can be added which is associated with the account.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details of, modify, download or delete the documents associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>SearchForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search Accounts</title>
<description>This page provides the search feature for accounts in the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can search for accounts in the system. The search can be based on the account name, phone number or the account type. Three types of accounts can be selected from the drop down list shown.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Account Details</title>
<description>This shows the details of the account, which can be modified. Each account can have folders, contacts, opportunities, revenue, tickets, and documents, for which there are separate tabs.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Click Modify at the top or bottom of the page to modify these datails.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Dashboard</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Revenue Dashboard</title>
<description>This revenue dashboard shows a progress chart for different years and types. All the accounts with revenue are also shown along with a list of employees working under you are also listed under the progress chart. You can add accounts, search for the existing ones in the system based on different filters and export the data in different formats.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The list of employees reporting to a particular employee/supervisor is also shown below the progress chart.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Accounts present are also shown, with name and the amount of money associated with that Account. Clicking on the Account displays the details of the Account.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the progress chart in different views for all the employees working under the owner or creator of the Account. The views can be selected from the drop down box present under the chart. A mouse over or a click on the break point on the progress chart will give the date and exact value associated with that point.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Reports</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Export Data</title>
<description>The data can be filtered, exported, displayed, and downloaded in different formats.You can also see the number of times an exported report has been downloaded.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed as a .csv file or in the html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action field is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display the list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated using the &amp;quot;Generate new export&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>ModifyFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify folder record</title>
<description>The Folder record details can be updated.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details are updated by clicking the Update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>ReopenTicket</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Delete</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>GenerateForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Generate New Export</title>
<description>To generate the Export data</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>There are filters through which you can exactly select the data needed to generate the export data. Apart from selecting the type of accounts and the criteria, you can also select the fields required and then sort them.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call Details</title>
<description>Calls associated with the contact</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Using the select button under the action column you can view the details about the call, modify the call, forward the call or delete the call on the whole.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the subject of the call will show you the details about the call that was made to the contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a call associated with the contact using the &amp;quot;Add a call&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>AddFolderRecord</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add folder record</title>
<description>A new Folder record can be added to the Folder.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Record details can be saved using the save button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a call</title>
<description>You can add a new call, which is associated with a particular contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the new call can be saved using the save button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The call type can be selected from the dropdown box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Upload Document</title>
<description>New documents can be uploaded and associated with an account</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can browse your local system to select a new document to upload.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>UpdateOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Upload a New Version of an existing Document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can upload a new version of an existing document.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Details </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>AddTicket</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a new Ticket</title>
<description>This page lets you create a new ticket for the account</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can insert a new ticket, add the ticket source and also assign new contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>Here the documents associated with the ticket are listed. New documents related to the ticket can be added</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the documents can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details, modify, download or delete the documents associated with the ticket</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new document can be added which is associated with the ticket</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The document versions can be updated by using the &amp;quot;add version&amp;quot; link</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>UpdateTicket</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOppComponents.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>InsertFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Search</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Lists the Accounts present and also lets you create an account</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the account name shows complete details about the account</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new account</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The select button in the Action column allows you to view, modify and archive the account. Archiving makes the account invisible, but it is still in the database.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Page shows all the versions of the current document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download all the versions of the documents</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Modify the current document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify / update the current document information, such as the subject and the filename</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Account Details</title>
<description>Displays the details of the account, which can be modified. Each account can have folders, the contacts, opportunities, revenue, and tickets. You can update several documents associated with each account.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the account can be modified here. The details can be saved using the Modify button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call details</title>
<description>The details of the call are shown here which can be modified, deleted or forwarded to any of the users.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or forward the calls using the corresponding buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add / update a call</title>
<description>You can add a new call to a contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the new call can be saved using the save button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The call type can be selected from the dropdown box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Call details</title>
<description>The details of the call are shown here, and can be modified, deleted or forwarded to any of the employees</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or forward the calls using the corresponding buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsCalls.do</action>
<section>ForwardCall</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Forward Call</title>
<description>The details of the calls that are associated with a contact can be forwarded to different employees.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select the list of the recipients to whom you want to forward the particular call to by using the &amp;quot;Add Recipients&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>ViewOpps</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Opportunities</title>
<description>Opportunities associated with the contact, showing the best guess total and last modified date.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify and delete the opportunity associated with the contact.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the description of the opportunity is clicked, it will display more details about the opportunity and its components.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add an opportunity.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Select an opportunity type from the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountContactsOpps.do</action>
<section>DetailsOpp</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about the components here and also add a new component to a particular opportunity. The opportunity can be renamed and its details can be modified</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can rename or delete the opportunity itself using the buttons below.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify, view and delete the details of any particular component by clicking the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new component associated with the account. It also displays the status, amount and the date when the component will be closed.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>TicketDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Details</title>
<description>This page lets you view the details of the ticket, and also lets you modify or delete the ticket.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Lets you modify or delete the ticket information</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the tasks and documents related to a ticket along with the history of that document by clicking on the corresponding links.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>ModifyTicket</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify ticket</title>
<description>This page lets you modify the ticket information and update its details</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also have tasks and documents related to a ticket along with the document history.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Lets you modify / update the ticket information.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketTasks.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Task Details</title>
<description>This page lists the tasks assigned for a particular account. New tasks can be added, which would then appear in the list of tasks, showing their priority and their assignment.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the task can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update the task by clicking on the description of the task.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a task which is associated with the existing ticket.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Uploading a Document</title>
<description>Upload a new document related to the account.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The document can be uploaded using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountTickets.do</action>
<section>ViewHistory</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Log History</title>
<description>This page maintains a complete log history of each ticket from its creation till the ticket is closed.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>All the versions of the current document are listed here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download all the different versions of the documents using the &amp;quot;Download&amp;quot; link in the Action column.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Document</title>
<description>Modify the document information</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The subject and the filename of the document can be modified.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AccountsDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Upload New Version</title>
<description>Upload a new document version</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The subject and the file name can be changed. The version number is updated when an updated document is uploaded.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Accounts.do</action>
<section>ExportReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Exported data</title>
<description>The data can be filtered, exported and displayed in different formats. You can then view the data and also download it.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The exported data can be viewed as a .csv file or in html format. The exported data can also be deleted when the select button in the action field is clicked.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also choose to display a list of all the exported data in the system or the exported data created by you.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>New export data can be generated using the &amp;quot;Generate new export&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Revenue Details</title>
<description>Details about revenue</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Revenue details along with the option to modify and delete revenue.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>RevenueManager.do</action>
<section>Dashboard </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunityForm.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Opportunity</title>
<description>A new opportunity associated with the contact can be added</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add / update an opportunity here and assign it to an employee. The opportunity can be associated with an account or a contact. Each opportunity created requires the estimate or the probability of closing the deal, the duration and the best estimate of the person following up the lead.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Opportunities.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add opportunity</title>
<description>A new opportunity associated with the contact can be added</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add / update an opportunity here and assign it to an employee. The opportunity can be associated with an account or a contact. Each opportunity created requires the estimate or the probability of closing the deal, the duration and the best estimate of the person following up the lead.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Opportunities.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Opportunity Details</title>
<description>You can view all the details about the components here like the status, the guess amount and the current stage. A new component can also be added to a particular opportunity.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>An opportunity can be renamed or deleted using the buttons present at the bottom of the page</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the select button lets you view, modify or delete the details about the component</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the component would show the details about the component</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new component which is associated with the account.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Opportunities.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Opportunity</title>
<description>The details of the opportunity can be modified</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The description of the opportunity can be changed using the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunitiesComponents.do</action>
<section>DetailsComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details</title>
<description>This page shows the details about the opportunity like what is the probability of closing the opportunity, what is the current stage of the opportunity etc</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify and delete the opportunity created using the modify and the delete buttons</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunitiesComponents.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a component</title>
<description>A component can be added to an opportunity and assigned to any employee present in the system. The component type can also be selected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &#147;select &#148; link</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employee present using the dropdown list present.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunitiesComponents.do</action>
<section>ModifyComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Component</title>
<description>The details of the component can be added / updated to an opportunity and assigned to any employee present in the system. The component type can also be selected.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The component type can be selected using the &#147;select &#148; link</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can assign the component to any of the employee present using the dropdown list present.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the update button can save the changes made to the component</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>OpportunitiesComponents.do</action>
<section>SaveComponent</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Component Details</title>
<description>This page shows the details about the opportunity like what is the probability of closing the opportunity, what is the current stage of the opportunity etc</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify and delete the opportunity created using the modify and the delete buttons</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>AccountsServiceContracts.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contracts</title>
<description>This page lists all the service contracts associated with the account. Based on your permissions you would be able to add new service contracts and modify exting ones from this page. &#13;
&#13;
A service contract describes the terms and conditions in a contract including the start and end dates, the contract value, the number of hours, service models and other details.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsServiceContracts.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Contract</title>
<description>This page allows you to add a service contract to the account. &#13;
&#13;
A service contract describes the terms and conditions in a contract including the start and end dates, the contract value, the number of hours, service models and other details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page is contains a general information section, a block hour information section and service model options section.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The general information section allows you to enter a service contract number, the start and end dates, the contract value, category, type, labor categories and free form description and billing notes.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The category and type of for service contacts are configured by your administrator to suit your business requirements. If you find, that a category or type required to describe the contract is not available in the list, please contract your manager of administrator to add the options. The options can be added using the administrator view.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The block hour information allows you to specify or adjust the hours associated with the contract.  The adjust link opens a pop up that allows you to enter hours credited or hours subtracted (preced with a '-' for negative numbers) a description and choose from a pre-configured list, the reason for the change. Again, if you do not find the required reason, please contact your manager or administrator to add the new option.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When your company performs work as a result of requests to the help desk department, the hours remaining is modified based on the travel and labor hours counted towards this contract.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The service model options allow you to specify the terms of the service contract for various types of services (telephone, onsite, email or a general response time.) All the service model options are mandatory. If  one of the service model options is not relevant to the account, it is required to explicitly choose the option that specifies that this option is not not applicable. Hence, it is recommended that each of these lists be pre-configured with at least the &amp;quot;not applicable&amp;quot; option.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The select link in the labor categories field, allows multiple labor categories to be assigned to this service contract. The select link opens a pop up that displays labor category codes and a description of these codes. These labor category records were either setup during initial system installation or through the products module of this CRM application. If you require a labor category that is not available in the list view of the popup, you may add one using the catalog module if you have permission to add them, or contact your manager or administrator who has permissions to add labor categories using the catalog module.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>The current end date should be greater than the current contract date if the current contract date is specified. If current contract date is not specified, the current end date should be greater than the initial contract date.</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>The current contract date is not required. If it is left blank, it is prefilled with the initial contract date when this contract record is saved.</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsServiceContracts.do</action>
<section>Modify Contract</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Contract</title>
<description>This page allows your to modify contract information.&#13;
&#13;
A service contract describes the terms and conditions in a contract including the start and end dates, the contract value, the number of hours, service models and other details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page is contains a general information section, a block hour information section and service model options section.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The functionality and business rule for the general information section and the service model options section are similar to those of &amp;quot;add contract&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The block hour information section allows you adjust the hours for this contract. The adjust link is similar to that in the &amp;quot;add contract&amp;quot; page and allows you to either reimburse or subtract (precede with a '-') the hours for this contract. The new hours as a result of the adjustment is displayed when the pop up closes and is saved only when the service contract is updated.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsServiceContracts.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Service Contract Details</title>
<description>This page displays the information of a service contract. The information is divided into general information, block hour information and service model options</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A history link is visible if hours where specified for this contract or when as a result of work orders to the help desk department, hours were counted towards this contract.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The history link opens a popup that shows a list of entries that modified the hours. The hours may have been modified(or initially added)  when the service contract was created, or as a result of work orders to the help desk department or due to an explicit modification of the service contract details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The labor categories field displays a list of comma seperated labor category codes specified for this contract. A description of these codes can be viewed from the catalog module of this CRM application.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>AccountsAssets.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Assets</title>
<description>This page displays assets associated with the service contract of the account. Based on your permissions you would be able to add new assets or modify existing ones from this page.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsAssets.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Asset</title>
<description>This page allows you to add an asset to the account and associate it with a service contract</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The information about an asset is categorized into the specific asset information, asset category, the service contract information, the service options for this asset, the warranty information and financial information. It also allows additional notes to be entered for this asset.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The serial number is mandatory to add an asset. It is usually provided by the manufacturer of the asset.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The date listed is prefilled with the current date and specifies the date when the asset was recorded to be part of the service contract for this account.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Asset Tag is an internal identifier provided for the asset. The asset tag is usually unique for all assets associated with an account.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The category section allows you to categorize the asset to a fine level of detail (e.g., Hardware - Server - Blade Server). Level 1, Level 2 and Level 3 are drop lists where the contents visible in each level depends upon the item chosen in the preceding level.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The information in the drop lists of the category section are preconfigured in the admin module. If you have to add or modify the categories that need to be displayed, you may do so by configuring the asset module. An administrator or a person with access to the admin module would be able to configure the categories that need to be displayed in the category section of this page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The service model options section allows you to specify the service model options for an asset. The service model options for an asset are defaulted to the the service model options of the service contract that this asset is associated with. These may be changed by choosing another item from the respective drop lists.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the service contract section of this page, the select link opens a pop up and displays a list of service contracts associated with the account. Clicking on the add link against a service contract record in the pop up associates the specified service contract with the asset. The association is permanently recorded only when the asset is saved.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>For most assets it is percieved that the puchased date is earler than the expiration date. As the application does not enforce this rule, it is recommended that you verify the entry in these two fields before saving the information about the asset. It is possible for an asset to have an expiration date that is earlier than the purchased date if the asset is a pre-used asset, and its warranty expired during the time it was with the previous owner or if the warranty does not transfer with the transfer of the asset.</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsAssets.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Asset Details</title>
<description>This page allows you to view asset details associated with a service contract  of the account.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The asset details are categorized into specific asset information, asset category, service contract information, service options for this asset, warranty information and financial information.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The service model options for this asset displays the items chosen when the asset record was created or modified. If they are specified to default to the service options in the service contract, the option is preceded by the word 'Default'.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsAssets.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Asset</title>
<description>This page allows you to modify an asset  associated it with a service contract of this account.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>Similar to the adding an asset</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AccountsAssets.do</action>
<section>History</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Asset History</title>
<description>The page displays the maintenance history of the asset.  This history for the asset is generated when the help desk department initiates a maintenance for this asset. The asset is maintained based on the service model options specified for the asset.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Account Contact</title>
<description>This page allows you to add an account contact and to permit the account to use the CRM application as a portal user</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The account contact information  consists of the contact's name and contact information (email, telephone and postal addresses.)</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The 'select' link of the contact type field open's a popup that allows you to choose the contact types that are applicable for this contact. The contact types are preconfigured in the admin module. If you do not find a contact type that you need, you may edit the types in the admin module or contact your supervisor or an administrator who has permissions to do so.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Checking the box at the end of this page enables you to provide portal access to this account contact. Since portal usage information is sent by email to the account contacts, to complete the process of providing portal access to an account contact, it is mandatory for the account contact to have an email address.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>An account contact may have a number of email addresses, this page allows one email address to be chosen as the primary email address. The primary email address is by default used to email the account contact about portal usage information. However, if the account contact has only one email address, it is not required to choose it as the primary contact.</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Contacts.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify contact</title>
<description>The details of an account contact can be modified or updated here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The 'select' link of the contact type field open's a popup that allows you to choose the contact types that are applicable for this contact. The contact types are preconfigured in the admin module. If you do not find a contact type that you need, you may edit the types in the admin module or contact your supervisor or an administrator who has permissions to do so.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The details can be updated using the update button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The account contact information consists of the contact's name and contact information (email, telephone and postal addresses.)</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>An account contact may have a number of email addresses, this page allows one email address to be chosen as the primary email address. The primary email address is by default used to email the account contact about portal usage information. However, if the account contact has only one email address, it is not required to choose it as the primary contact.</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ContactsPortal.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Contact Portal</title>
<description>This page displays the portal information (username, expiration date) of this account contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Based on your permissions, you can provide portal access to an account contact who does not have portal access, edit the portal user information and disable(or enable) the portal user from this page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the account contact does not have an email address, you will not be allowed to add or edit the portal user information for the account contact.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ContactsPortal.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Contact Portal</title>
<description>This page allows you to modify the portal information of the account contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The information that is modified in this page affects portal access to the application for the user.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The information than can be modified are, the portal role (if more than one role exists,) the expiration date and the password.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The password is automatically generated and mailed to the account contact, hence, for this purpose it is mandatory for the account contact to have an email address when the portal information is modified.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ContactsPortal.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Contact Portal</title>
<description>This page allows you to allow the account contact access to this appication as a portal user. A portal user is allowed to see account information only for the account to which he is listed as a contact.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page allows you to specify the portall role, the expiration date and the email to which portal access information (username and password) is sent.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The password is automatically generated and mailed to the account contact, hence, for this purpose it is mandatory for the account contact to have an email address when the portal information is modified.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Communications" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>Communications is a &amp;quot;Campaign Manager&amp;quot; Module where you can manage complex email. fax, or mail communications with your customers. Communications allows you to create and choose Groups, Messages, and Schedules to define communications scenarios from the simple to the very complex. Groups can range from a single contact chosen from a pick list to the result of a complex query of the Account/Contact database. Messages can be anything from a single-line email to a rich, multimedia product catalog to an interactive survey.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>The Communication module has six main features.

Dashboard: Track and analyze campaigns that have been activated and executed.
Messages can be sent out by any combination of email, fax, or mail merge. The Dashboard shows an overview of sent messages and allows you to drill down and view recipients and any survey results.

Add: This page lets you add a new campaign.

Campaign List: This page lets you add a new campaign into the system.

Groups: Each campaign needs at least one group to send a message to. Use criteria to filter the contacts you need to reach and use them over and over again. As new contacts meet the criteria, they will be included in future campaigns. This page lists the group names. It shows the groups created by you or everybody i.e. all the groups. 

Messages: Compose a message to reach your audience. Each campaign requires a message that will be sent to selected groups. Write the message once, then use it in any number of future campaigns. Modified messages will only affect future campaigns. Displays the list of messages, with the description and other details.

Attachments: Customize and configure your Campaigns with attachments. Attachments can include interactive items, like surveys, or provide additional materials like files.</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Dashboard</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Communications Dashboard</title>
<description>Track and analyze campaigns that have been activated and executed.

Messages can be sent out by any combination of email, fax, or mail merge. The Dashboard shows an overview of sent messages and allows you to drill down and view recipients and any survey results.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking the select button under the action column gives you the option to view the details about the campaign, download the mail merge and also lets you to export it to Excel.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the campaign name gives you complete details about the campaign.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can display the campaigns created and their details using three different views by selecting from the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a campaign</title>
<description>This page lets you add a new campaign into the system.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This creates a new Campaign. This takes in both the campaign and its description.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign List</title>
<description>Create or work on existing campaigns.

The Campaign Builder allows you to select groups of contacts that you would like to send a message to, as well as schedule a delivery date. Additional options are available.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view, modify and delete details by clicking the select button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>For each of the campaign, the groups, message and delivery columns show whether they are complete or not. Clicking on these will help you choose the group, message and the delivery date.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the name of the campaign shows you more details about the campaign and also shows the list of the things to be selected before a campaign can be activated</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view your incomplete campaigns or all the incomplete campaigns. You can select the view with the drop down list at the top.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a campaign</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>View Groups</title>
<description>Each campaign needs at least one group to which to send a message. Use criteria to filter the contacts you need to reach and use them over and over again. As new contacts meet the criteria, they will be automatically included in future campaigns. This page lists the group names. It shows the groups created by you or everybody; i.e. all the groups.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the Action column for viewing, modifying or deleting the details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the group name will show the list of contacts present in the group.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a contact group using the link &amp;quot;Add a Contact Group&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can filter the list of groups displayed by selecting from the drop down.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Group</title>
<description>A new contact group can be added. Separate criteria can be specified when creating the group. The criteria can be defined to generate a list. The list to be added can be previewed before saving the group details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can preview the details of the group by clicking on the preview button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also select from the list of &amp;quot;Selected criteria and contacts&amp;quot; and remove them by clicking the remove button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can define the criteria to generate the list by using the different filters present and then add them to the &amp;quot;Selected criteria and contacts&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select the criteria for the group to be created. Clicking the &amp;quot;Add/Remove Contacts&amp;quot; can choose the specific contacts.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message List</title>
<description>Compose a message to reach your audience.
Each campaign requires a message that will be sent to selected groups. Write the message once, then use it in any number of future campaigns. Modified messages will only affect future campaigns. Displays the list of messages, with the description and other details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view, modify, clone or delete each of the messages.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The dropdown list acts as filters for displaying the messages that meet certain criteria.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the message name will show details about the message, which can be updated.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new message</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a Message</title>
<description>You can add a new message for the campaign, which would show up in the message list.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The new message can be saved by clicking the save message button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The permissions or the access type for the message can be chosen from drop down box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CampaignManagerAttachment.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Create Attachments</title>
<description>Customize and configure your Campaigns with attachments. Attachments can include interactive items, like surveys, or provide additional materials like files.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the &amp;quot;surveys&amp;quot; will let you create new interactive surveys.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Contacts of the group are displayed</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can use the preview button to view the details about the contacts in a group.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify or delete a group.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>version change of a document</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can change the version of the document when ever an updated document is uploaded.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Dashboard </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>New documents can be uploaded and be associated with the campaign.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can browse to select a new document to upload if its related to the campaign.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ResponseDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Preview</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Here details about the contacts, i.e. the name, their company, and their email address are displayed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also go back from the current detailed view to the group details criteria.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>PrepareDownload</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Details</title>
<description>This page shows the details about the campaign and also shows the list of available documents.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download from the list of documents available by using the &amp;quot;download&amp;quot; link under the action column.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewGroups</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Groups</title>
<description>The group name along with the contacts present in the Group are listed</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a survey</title>
<description>You can add a new survey here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The name of the survey is a mandatory field for creating a survey. A description, introduction and thank-you note can also be added.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>MoveQuestion</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Details</title>
<description>Campaign details are the number of groups selected for the campaign, the text message of the campaign, when is it scheduled to run, how the delivery of the message done, who entered these details and who modified it are shown here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download the mail merge shown at the bottom of the details.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>All Versions of this current Document are shown here with the details like the size of the uploaded file, the number of downloads etc.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Different versions of the document can be downloaded using the &amp;quot;download&amp;quot; link in the action column.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>ViewReturn</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Details </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewSchedule</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>For the campaign you can schedule a delivery date to send the message to the recipients.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update the campaign schedule by filling in the run date and the delivery method whether it's an email, fax or letter or any other method.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerGroup.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Here you can update the group details and also the update contact criteria.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also generate a list of contacts be selecting from the filters and adding them to the &amp;quot;selected criteria and contacts&amp;quot; list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can choose the contacts in the group using the &amp;quot;Add / Remove contacts&amp;quot; link present.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update the name of the group</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>PreviewRecipients</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Recipients</title>
<description>The page displays a list of recipients with their name, company name, the date when the campaign was sent to those recipients and its status.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>PreviewMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>The message details are shown here, in the form of an email with a subject and message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>There can be multiple attachments to a single message. The attachment that needs to be downloaded has to be selected first and then downloaded.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>PreviewSchedule</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Schedule</title>
<description>This shows the delivery date and the delivery method or the campaign.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewResults</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Results</title>
<description>This page shows the results of the responses received from all the recipients in the group. This also shows the Last response received.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewResponse</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Response</title>
<description>This page shows the responses of all the recipients along with their system IP addresses and their email address</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Document details</title>
<description>This page lists all the documents associated with this campaign and for each document it lists the size of the file, the extension and the version of the file.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the documents can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details, modify, download or delete the documents associated with the account.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new document can be added to the account.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The document versions can be updated by using the &amp;quot;add version&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Campaign Details</title>
<description>This is the detail page for the campaign, where step-by-step information is given on how to activate the campaign; i.e. what should be selected before a campaign is activated.

This campaign can be configured and can now be activated.
Once activated, today's campaigns will begin processing in under 5 minutes and cannot be cancelled.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The name of the campaign can be changed or deleted by using the buttons at the bottom of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can choose a group / groups, a message for the campaign, and a delivery date for the campaign to start. You can also add attachments to the messages you send to recipients.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>AddGroups</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Choose Groups</title>
<description>Selecting or updating the group / groups for the campaign can be done here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can check the groups you want for the current campaign.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also add attachments to the messages you send to recipients by clicking the preview recipient's link next to each group.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view all the groups present or the groups created by you just by choosing from the drop down box.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewMessage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>Updating a message for the campaign</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select a message for this campaign from the dropdown list of all the messages or just your messages.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The messages can be of multiple types, which can be used as filters and can be selected from the drop down list. For each type you have further classification.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewAttachmentsOverview</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Attachment Details</title>
<description>For each message, we can add the attachments.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The attachments configured are the surveys or the file attachments. Using the links &amp;quot;change survey&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;change file attachments&amp;quot;, you can change either of them.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ViewAttachment</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Surveys</title>
<description>A survey can be selected for this campaign.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view and select from all, or only your own surveys.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>ManageFileAttachments</section>
<subSection/>
<title>File Attachments</title>
<description>Campaign can also have a file as an attachment</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download or remove the file name. You can also upload files using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Campaign Details</title>
<description>Updating the campaign name /description</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The name and the description of the campaign can be changed.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>This page shows the details of the message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or clone the message details by clicking on corresponding buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Message</title>
<description>This page lets you Add/Update a new message. The message can have an access type, limiting who can view a message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select font properties for the text of the message along with the size and indentation.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The name of the message and the access type can be given, which specifies who can view the message.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Message Details</title>
<description>This page shows the details of the message.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete or clone the message details by clicking on corresponding buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerMessage.do</action>
<section>Clone</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a Message</title>
<description>This page lets you Add a new message or Update an existing one. The message can have an access type, defining who can view it.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can select font properties for the text of the message along with the size and indentation.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The name of the message and the access type can be given, which specifies who can view the message.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Surveys</title>
<description>This page displays the surveys created and lets you update them.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also view, modify and delete the details of a survey.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the name of the survey shows its details.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new survey</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view all or your own surveys using the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>InsertAndAdd</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Survey Questions</title>
<description>Here you can add a new survey question. If the question type is &amp;quot;Item List&amp;quot;, you can edit the list of items present in that list and also mark whether the particular question is required or not.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Save &amp; Add&amp;quot; button saves the current question and lets you add another one immediately.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also specify whether the particular question is required or not by checking the checkbox.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the selected question type is &amp;quot;Item List&amp;quot;, then an Edit button is enabled which helps in adding new elements to the existing list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new question type can be selected through the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Survey Details</title>
<description>The details about the survey are displayed here along with the option to modify, delete and preview the survey.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The preview button shows you the survey questions in a pop-up window.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can modify, delete, and preview the survey details using the buttons at the top of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the survey introduction text, the questions and the thank-you text.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManagerSurvey.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Survey Details</title>
<description>This page displays all the questions added to a particular survey. It also enables you to add new questions. The order of the questions can be changed by moving questions up or down in the list. Questions can also be edited or deleted.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add questions to the survey here.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the &amp;quot;Done&amp;quot; button can save the survey and you can also traverse back by clicking the &amp;quot;Back&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The survey questions can be moved up or down using the &amp;quot;Up&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Down&amp;quot; links present in the action field.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can edit or delete any of the survey questions using the &amp;quot;edit&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;del&amp;quot; link under the action field.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add new survey questions here.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CampaignManager.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>You are looking at the communications module. This page reviews and manages campaigns with the following options: Dashboard, Campaign Builder, Build groups, Create messages and create attachments.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click on &amp;quot;Create Attachments&amp;quot; and include interactive items, like surveys, or provide additional materials like files.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking the &amp;quot;Create Message&amp;quot;  link lets you compose a message to reach your audience.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click the &amp;quot;Build Groups&amp;quot; link to assemble dynamic distribution of groups. Each campaign needs at least one group to send a message to.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Campaign Builder&amp;quot; can be clicked to select groups of contacts that you would like to send a message to, schedule a delivery date, etc.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click on the &amp;quot;Dashboard&amp;quot; to view the sent messages and to drill down and view recipients and survey results.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Help Desk" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>You are looking at the Help Desk module home page. The dashboard shows the most recent tickets that have been assigned to you, as well as tickets that are in your department, and tickets that have been created by you. You can add new tickets, search for existing tickets based on different filters and export ticket data.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>The Help Desk module has four main features.

View: Lists all the tickets assigned to you and the tickets assigned in your department. Details such as the ticket number, priority, age, i.e. how old the ticket is, the company and the tickets assignment are displayed.

Add: You can add a new ticket here.

Search: Form used for searching the tickets that already exist in the system based on different filters and parameters.

Export: This page shows exported data. The data can be exported to different formats. The exported data can be viewed with its subject, the size of the exported data file, when it was created and by whom. It also shows the number of times that particular exported file was downloaded. The exported data, created by you or all the employees can be viewed in two different views. A new data file can also be exported.</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Details</title>
<description>This page lets you view the details of the ticket also lets you modify or delete the ticket.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Lets you modify or delete ticket information</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also store tasks and documents related to a ticket.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a Ticket</title>
<description>You can add a new ticket here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>For each new ticket you can select the organization, the contact and also the issue for which the ticket is being created. The assignment and the resolution of the ticket can also be entered.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>SearchTicketsForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search Existing Tickets</title>
<description>Form used for searching existing tickets based on different filters and parameters.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The search can be done based on different parameters like the ticket number, account associated, priority, employee whom the ticket is assigned etc.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Reports</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Export Data</title>
<description>This is the page shows exported data.
The data can be exported in different formats. The exported data can be viewed with its subject, the size of the exported data file, when it was created and by whom. It also shows the number of times that particular exported file was downloaded. A new data file can also be exported.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the subject of the exported data shows you the details of the ticket like the ticket ID, the organization and its issue (why the particular ticket was generated).</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the select button under the action column lets you view the data, download the data in .CSV format or delete the data.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can filter the exported date generated, by you or by all employees using the dropdown list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can generate a new exported data by clicking the link &amp;quot;Generate new export&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Ticket</title>
<description>Here you can modify ticket details like information, classification, assignment and resolution.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can save the details of the modified ticket by clicking the &amp;quot;Update&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Ticket Details</title>
<description>Here you can modify the ticket details like ticket information, it's classification, the ticket&#146;s assignment and it's resolution.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can save the details of the modified ticket by clicking the &amp;quot;Update&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketTasks.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Tasks</title>
<description>This page lists the tasks assigned for a particular ticket. New tasks can be added, which would then appear in the list of tasks, showing their priority, their assignment and other details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the task can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update the task by clicking on the description of the task.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a task which is associated with the existing ticket.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Documents</title>
<description>Here the documents associated with a ticket are listed. New documents related to the ticket can be added.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details of the documents can be viewed or modified by clicking on the select button under the Action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the details, modify, download or delete the documents associated with the ticket.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new document associated with the ticket can be added.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The document versions can be updated by using the &amp;quot;add version&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>Fields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Folder Records</title>
<description>New folders can be created for each ticket. New Folders are defined and configured in the Admin Module. This page also displays a list of records with their details such as when the record was created, last modified, the action performed on the record etc.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A new record is added into the folder using the link &amp;quot;Add a record to this folder&amp;quot;. Multiple records can be added to this folder if the folder has the necessary settings.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select the custom folder using the drop down list.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>AddFolderRecord</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Folder Record</title>
<description>The details of the record are added</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details are saved by clicking the save button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>ViewHistory</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Ticket Log History</title>
<description>The log history of the ticket is maintained.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A chronological history of all actions associated with a ticket is maintined.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Insert</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>InsertFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>GenerateForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Details </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Update</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>ExportReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>ModifyFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Folder Record</title>
<description>This lists the details of the folder record, which can be modified.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The changes can be saved using the &amp;quot;Update&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsFolders.do</action>
<section>UpdateFields</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Folder Record Details</title>
<description>The details about the folder along with the record information such as when the record was created and when it was modified is displayed here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify the folder information along with the record details by clicking on the Modify button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>SearchTickets</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Home </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a Document</title>
<description>A new document related to a ticket can be uploaded.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The document can be uploaded using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Details</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Document Details</title>
<description>This page shows all the versions of the current document.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can download all the versions of a document.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Document Details</title>
<description>This page lets you modify the ticket information and update the details.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also have tasks and documents related to a ticket.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Lets you modify / update the ticket information.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTicketsDocuments.do</action>
<section>AddVersion</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add version number to Documents</title>
<description>You can upload a new version of an existing document.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A new version of a file can be uploaded using the browse button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>TroubleTickets.do</action>
<section>Home</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>This page displays the complete list of the tickets assigned to the user, the list of the tickets present in his department and finally the list of the tickets created by the user. For each ticket, the details about the ticket, such as the ticket number, priority, age of the ticket, the company and finally the assignment details are displayed. The issue details are also shown separately for each ticket.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can delete a record by clicking on &amp;quot;Del&amp;quot; next to the record.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a record by clicking on &amp;quot;Add Ticket&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view more records in a particular section by clicking &amp;quot;Show More&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view more details by clicking on the record.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update a record by clicking on &amp;quot;Edit&amp;quot; next to the record.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>Other tickets in my Department: These are records that are assigned to anyone in your department, are unassigned in your department, and are open.</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>Tickets assigned to me: These are records that are assigned to you and are open</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>Tickets created by me: These are records that have been entered by you and are open</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips>
<tipDescription>Make sure to resolve your tickets as soon as possible so they don't appear here!</tipDescription>
</tips>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTicketActivityLog.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Activity Log</title>
<description>This page lists the services (activities performed) rendered to a client after a ticket has been created.  Each Activity Log is usually a sequence of descriptions of the work done during the business days of the week. To resolve the issues listed in a ticket,  multiple activity logs (usually one for each business week) may be required.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The first activity date displays the date at which work started in an activity log and the last activity date displays the last date that work was done for the activity log.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You may view, add, edit and delete activity logs from this page based on your permissions</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Adding, editing and deleting activity logs with hours counting towards a service contract changes the hours remaining in a service contract. The hours remaining is displayed in the ticket header.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketActivityLog.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Activity Log</title>
<description>This page allows you to describe the activity performed on each day in order to resolve the issue specified in the ticket.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page is divided into the general information, per day description of service and additional information sections</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The 'General Information' section displays the associated service contract.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The 'Per Day Description of Service' section that allows you to enter description of work done.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The 'Additional information' section that allows you to enter the follow up information and phone and engineer response time.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>If the follow up field is checked, the alert date and description are mandatory.</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>The phone and engineer response time are text fields that allow you to enter the &amp;quot;time of day' when the response was made.</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>All fields in a row of the description of service section is mandatory.</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>The travel time and the labor time can be selected from the drop list. If you choose the values in these duration fields to count towards a service contract, the hours remaining in the service contract is changed accordingly when this activity log is saved.</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketActivityLog.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Activity Log Details</title>
<description>This page displays activities performed on each day in order to resolve the issue specified in the ticket. It also displays follow up information if they are recorded during creation or modification of the activity log.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page is divided into the general information, per day description of service and additional information sections</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The travel time and the labor time in the per day description section are summed and displayed to you for reference.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketActivityLog.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Activity Log</title>
<description>This page allows you to edit the activities performed on each day in order to resolve the issue specified in the ticket.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page is divided into the general information, per day description of service and additional information sections</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The 'General Information' section displays the associated service contract.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The 'Per Day Description of Service' section that allows you to enter description of work done.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription># The 'Additional information' section that allows you to enter the follow up information and phone and engineer response time.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules>
<ruleDescription>All fields in a row of the description of service section is mandatory.</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>If the follow up field is checked, the alert date and description are mandatory.</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>The phone and engineer response time are text fields that allow you to enter the &amp;quot;time of day' when the response was made.</ruleDescription>
<ruleDescription>The travel time and the labor time can be selected from the drop list. If you choose the values in these duration fields to count towards a service contract, the hours remaining in the service contract is changed accordingly when this activity log is saved.</ruleDescription>
</rules>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>TroubleTicketMaintenanceNotes.do</action>
<section>List</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Maintenance Notes</title>
<description>This page displays a list of maintenance notes performed on an asset.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page displays information about an asset that is relevant for maintenance work to be done on the asset and then displays the maintenance notes for the asset created to resolve the issue recorded in the ticket.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You may view, add, edit and delete maintenance notes from this page based on your permissions.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketMaintenanceNotes.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Maintenance Note</title>
<description>This page allows you to create a maintenance note.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page is divided into a general maintenance information section and a replacement parts section.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The general mainetenance information section allows you to enter a description relating the reason for failure of the asset, or a description relating to the neccessity to service or upgrade the asset to keep it performing optimally or to include additional features.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The replacement parts section allows you to enter the part number and a description of the part in each row. It initially displays three rows, allowing three parts to be entered. If additional parts need to be entered, you may save this maintenance note and choose to modify it. The modify page allows you to enter an additional part. Alternatively, to add more replacement parts, you may create another maintenance note.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>TroubleTicketMaintenanceNotes.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Maintenance Note</title>
<description>This page allows you to modify a maintenance note.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page is divided into a general maintenance information section and a replacement parts section.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The general mainetenance information section allows you to modify the description relating the reason for failure of the asset, or a description relating to the neccessity to service or upgrade the asset to keep it performing optimally or to include additional features.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The replacement parts section allows you to enter the part number and a description of the part in each row.  It displays one additional row to allow you to enter an additional replacement part. If more parts need to be entered, you may update this maintenance note and choose to modify it again. Alternatively, to add more replacement parts, you may create another maintenance note.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Employees" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>You are looking at the Employee module home page. This page displays the details of all the employees present in the system.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>The main feature of the employee module is the view.

View: This page displays the details of each employee, which can be viewed, modified or deleted. Each employee record contains details such as the name of the employee, their department, title and phone number. This also lets you add a new employee into the system.</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>ListEmployees</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>The details of each employee can be viewed, modified or deleted and a new detailed employee record can be added.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>A new detailed employee record can be added.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The details of each employee can be viewed, modified or deleted using the select button in the action column.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>EmployeeDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Employee Details</title>
<description>This is the employee detail page. This page displays the email, phone number, addresses and additional details of each employee.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can modify or delete the employee details using the modify or delete buttons.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>Prepare</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add an Employee</title>
<description>You can add an employee into the system. The details of the employee such as his email address; phone numbers, address and other additional details can be given along with his name</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Save&amp;quot; button saves the details of the employee entered.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Save &amp; New&amp;quot; button lets you to save the details of one employee and enter another employee in one operation.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>ModifyEmployee</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Employee Details</title>
<description>Employee details such as the name of the employee, email address, phone numbers and address can be modified here.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the update button saves the modified details of the employee.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>CompanyDirectory.do</action>
<section>Save</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>This page shows the details of the employee record, which can be modified or deleted.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The employee record can be modified or deleted from the system completely.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Reports" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>You are looking at the Reports module home page. This page displays a list of generated reports that are ready to be downloaded. It also displays a list of reports that are scheduled to be processed by server. You can add new reports too.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>The Reports module has two main features.

Queue: Queue shows the list of reports that are scheduled to be processed by the server.

Add: This shows the different modules present and displays the list of corresponding reports present in each module, allowing you to add a report to the schedule queue.</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>ViewQueue</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>This is the home of the reports. 

A list of customized reports can be viewed and the queue of the reports that are scheduled to be processed by the server are also displayed. Each report that is ready to be retrieved is displayed along with its details such as the subject of the report, the date when the report was generated, report status and finally the size of the report for the user to download.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can cancel the reports that are scheduled to be processed by the server by the clicking the select button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The generated reports can be deleted or viewed/downloaded in .pdf format by clicking the select button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a new report</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>RunReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Modules</title>
<description>This shows the different modules present and displays the list of corresponding reports present in each module.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>There are four different modules and you can click on the module where you want to generate the report.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do </action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>CancelReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>ParameterList</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Parameters specification</title>
<description>This page takes the parameters that need to be specified to run the report.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can use the &amp;quot;generate report&amp;quot; button to run the report.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>If the parameters exist, you can specify the name of the criteria for future reference and click the check box present at the bottom of the page.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>ListReports</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Lis of Reports</title>
<description>In this module, you can choose the report that you want to run from the list of the reports.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can run the report by clicking on the title of the report.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>CriteriaList</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Criteria List</title>
<description>You can choose to base this report on previously saved criteria, or continue and create new criteria.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>If the criteria are present, select the criteria, then continue to enter the parameters to run the report.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section>GenerateReport</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Reports Added To Queue</title>
<description>This page shows that the requested report is added to the queue. Also lets you know the details about the report and queue status.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the queue either by using the link in the text or using the view queue button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Reports.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description/>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can cancel the report that is scheduled to be processed by the server by clicking the select button and selecting &amp;quot;Cancel&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the reports generated, download them or delete them by clicking on the select button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>A new report can be generated by clicking on the link &amp;quot;Add a Report&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Admin" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>The admin module lets the user review the system usage, configure modules, and configure the global/system parameters.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>This Admin System has five main features.

Users: This section allows the administrator to view and add users and manage user hierarchies. The users are typically employees in your company who interact with your clients or customers, but can be outsides that you have granted permissions on the system.

Roles: This page lists the different roles you have defined in the system, their role description and the number of people present in the system who carry out that role. New roles can be added into the system at any time.

Modules: This page lets you configure various parameters in the modules that meet the needs of your organization, including configuration of lookup lists and custom fields. There are four types of modules. Each module has different number of configure options. The changes in the module affect all the users.

System: You can configure the system for the session timeout and set the time limit for the time out.

Usage: Current System Usage and Billing Usage Information are displayed.</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>ListUsers</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Users</title>
<description>This section allows the administrator to view and add users and manage user hierarchies. The users are typically employees in your company who interact with your clients or customers.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The alphabetical slide rule allows users to be listed based on their last name. Simply click on the starting letter desired.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The columns &amp;quot;Name&amp;quot;, 'Username&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Role&amp;quot; can be clicked to display the users in the ascending or descending order of the chosen criteria.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Add New User&amp;quot; link opens a window that allows the administrator to add new users.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;select&amp;quot; buttons in the &amp;quot;Action&amp;quot; column alongside the name of each user opens a pop-up menu that provides the administrator with options to view more information, modify user information, or disable (or inactivate) the user.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The list is displayed with 10 names per page by default. Additional items in the list may be viewed by clicking on the &amp;quot;Previous&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Next&amp;quot; navigation links at the bottom of the table or by changing the number of items to be displayed per page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The users of the CRM system are listed in alphabetical order. Their user name, role and who they report to are also listed to provide a quick overview of information for each user.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The drop list provides a filter to either view only the active or only the inactive users. Inactive users are those who do not have the privilege to use the system currently either because their user names have been disabled or they have expired. These users may be activated (enabled) at a later time.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>InsertUserForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a New User</title>
<description>This form allows new users to be added to the system and records their contact information.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The 'Reports To&amp;quot; field allows the administrator to setup a user hierarchy. The drop list displays all the users of the system and allows one to be chosen.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Role&amp;quot; drop list allows a role to be associated with a user. This association determines the privileges the user may have when he accesses the system.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Password&amp;quot; fields allows the administrator to setup a password for the user. The password is used along with the Username to login to the system. Since the password is stored in encrypted form and cannot be interpreted, the administrator is asked to confirm the users password. The user may subsequently change his password according to personal preferences.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The Username is the phrase that is used by the user to login to the system. It must be unique.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>An &amp;quot;Expire Date&amp;quot; may be set for each user after which the user is disabled. If this field is left blank the user is active indefinitely. This date can either be typed in the mm/dd/yyyy format or chosen from a calendar that can be accessed from the icon at the right of the field.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The contact field allows the administrator to associate contact information with the user. The administrator may either create new contact information or choose one from the existing list of contacts. This information provides the administrator with the user's e-mail, telephone and (or) fax number, postal address and any other information that may help the administrator or the system manager to contact the user.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>ModifyUser</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify User Details</title>
<description>This form provides the administrator with an editable view of the user information, and also allows the administrator to view the users login history and view points.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Cancel&amp;quot; button allows current and uncommitted changes to be undone.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When the &amp;quot;Generate new password&amp;quot; field is checked, the system constructs a password for the user and uses the contact information to email the new password to the user.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Disable&amp;quot; button provides a quick link to the administrator to disable the user.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Username&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Role&amp;quot;, &amp;quot;Reports To&amp;quot; and password of the user are editable. For more information about each of these fields see help on &amp;quot;Add user&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>ViewLog</section>
<subSection/>
<title>User Login History</title>
<description>Provides a login history of the chosen user.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The list is displayed by default with 10 items per page, additional items in the login history may be viewed by clicking on the &amp;quot;Previous&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Next&amp;quot; navigation links at the bottom of the table or by changing the number of items to be displayed on a page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The login history of the user displays the IP address of the computer from which the user logged in, and the date/time when the user logged in.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>ListViewpoints</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Viewpoints of User</title>
<description>The page displays the viewpoints of the employees regarding a particular module in the system. Lets you add a new viewpoint. The details displayed are when the viewpoint was entered and whether it is enabled or not.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the select button under the action column would let you to view the details about the viewpoint also modify them.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can click on the contact under the viewpoint column to know more details about that viewpoint and its permissions.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new viewpoint using the link &amp;quot;Add New Viewpoint&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>InsertViewpointForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Viewpoint</title>
<description>The contact name can be selected and the permissions /access for the modules can be given.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add a new viewpoint by any employee by clicking the add button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The permissions for the different modules can be given by checking the Access checkbox.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The contact can be selected and removed using the links &amp;quot;change contact&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;clear contact&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>ViewpointDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Update Viewpoint</title>
<description>You can update a viewpoint and set the permissions to access different modules.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The details can be updated using the update button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can also set the permissions to access different modules by checking the check box under the Access column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can enable the viewpoint by checking the &amp;quot;Enabled&amp;quot; checkbox.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section>ListRoles</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Roles</title>
<description>You are looking at roles. 

This page lists the different roles present in the system, their role descriptions and the number of people present in the system who are assigned that role. New roles can be added at any time.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also click the select button under the action column to view or modify the details of roles.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the role name gives you details about the role and the permissions it provides.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a new role into the system.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section>InsertRoleForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add a New Role</title>
<description>This page will let you Add/Update the roles in the system. Also lets you change the permissions. The permissions can be changed or set for each module separately depending on the role.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking the update button updates the role.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section>RoleDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Update Role</title>
<description>This page will let you update the roles in the system. Also lets you change the permissions. The permissions can be changed or set for each module separately depending on the role.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The update of the role can be done by clicking the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>Config</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Configure Modules</title>
<description>This page lets you configure modules that meet the needs of your organization, including configuration of lookup lists and custom fields. Depending on permissions, each module that you can configure is listed and each module has a different number of configure options. The changes typically affect all users immediately.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the module name will display a list of module items that can be configured.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>ConfigDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Configuration Options</title>
<description>You can configure different options in each module.The following are some of the configuration options that you might see in the modules. Some of these options are specific to the module so they might NOT be present in all the modules.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Scheduled Events: A timer triggers a customizable workflow process.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Object Events: An Action triggers customizable workflow process. For example, when an object is inserted, updated, deleted or selected, a process is triggered.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Categories: This lets you create hierarchical categories for a specific feature in the module.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Lookup Lists: You can view the drop-down lists used in the module and make changes.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Custom Folders and Fields: Custom folders allows you to create forms that will be present within each module, essentially custom fields.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>ModifyList</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Edit Lookup List</title>
<description>This page lets you edit and add to the list items.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can create a new item type using the add button and add it to the existing list. You can position the item in the list using the up and down buttons, remove it using the remove button and also sort the list. The final changes can be saved using the &amp;quot;Save Changes&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>AdminFieldsFolder.do</action>
<section>AddFolder</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Adding a New Folder</title>
<description>Add/Update the existing folder here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update the existing the folder, set the options for the records and the permissions for the users.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="5">
<action>AdminFieldsFolder.do</action>
<section>ModifyFolder</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Existing Folder</title>
<description>Update the existing folder here</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can update the existing the folder, set the options for the records and the permissions for the users.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>AdminConfig.do</action>
<section>ListGlobalParams</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Configure System</title>
<description>You can configure the system for the session idle timeout and set the time for the time out.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Edit&amp;quot; link will let you alter the time for which the users session ends.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>AdminConfig.do</action>
<section>ModifyTimeout</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Modify Timeout</title>
<description>The session timeout is the time in which a user will automatically be logged out if the specified period of inactivity is reached.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The time out can be set by selecting the time from the drop down and clicking the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>Usage</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Resource Usage Details</title>
<description>Current System Usage and Billing Usage Information are displayed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The usage can be displayed for the current date or a custom date can be specified. This can be selected from the drop down of the date range.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The start date and the end date can be specified if the date range is &amp;quot;custom date range&amp;quot;. The update can be done using the update button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do </action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>DisableUserConfirm</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFieldsFolder.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Custom Folders</title>
<description>This page lists all the custom folders created in the General Contacts; let's you edit them and also allow you to enable/disable the folders.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also enable or disable the custom folders by clicking &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;no&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the custom folder will give details about that folder and also lets you add groups.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update an existing folder using the edit button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update an existing folder using the edit button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a folder to the general contacts module.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFieldsFolder.do</action>
<section>ListFolders</section>
<subSection/>
<title>List of Custom Folders</title>
<description>This page lists all the custom folders created in the General Contacts; let's you edit them and also allow you to enable/disable the folders.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also enable or disable the custom folders by clicking &amp;quot;yes&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;no&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update an existing folder using the edit button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the custom folder will give details about that folder and also lets you add groups.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can update an existing folder using the edit button under the action column.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a folder to the general contacts module.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFields.do</action>
<section>ModifyField</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>ListGlobalParams</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>ModifyTimeout</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminObjectEvents.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Object Events:</title>
<description>The list of Object Events are displayed along with the corresponding Triggered Processes. The number of components and whether that Object Event is available or not is also shown.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can view the process details by clicking on the select button under the Action column or by clicking on the name of the Triggered Process.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can view the process details by clicking on the select button under the Action column or by clicking on the name of the Triggered Process.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFieldsGroup.do</action>
<section>AddGroup</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>Add a group</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can add a group name and save it using the &amp;quot;save&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFields.do</action>
<section>AddField</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>UpdateList</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description>The Lookup List displays all the list names, which can be edited, the number of items can be known and the ones present can be previewed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click &amp;quot;Edit&amp;quot; in the Action column to update or delete a contact type.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can preview all the items present in a List name using the drop down in the preview column.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminScheduledEvents.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>Config </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section>EditLists</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Lookup Lists</title>
<description>The Lookup List displays all the list names, which can be edited, the number of items is displayed and the ones present can be previewed.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can click &amp;quot;Edit&amp;quot; in the Action column to update or delete a contact type.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can preview all the items present in a List name using the drop down in the preview column.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminFieldsGroup.do</action>
<section>ListGroups</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Folder Details</title>
<description>This page lists the folder details and the groups added to this folder. Each group can further have a custom field created or deleted. You can also place it in the desired position in the dropdown list.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>You can also delete the folder and all the fields using the &amp;quot;Delete this folder and all fields&amp;quot; at the bottom of the page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The groups can also be moved up or down using the &amp;quot;Up&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Down&amp;quot;. They can also be edited and deleted using the &amp;quot;Edit&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Del&amp;quot; links.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The custom field can also be edited and deleted using the corresponding links &amp;quot;Edit&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Del&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The custom field created can be moved up or down for the display using the corresponding links &amp;quot;Up&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Down&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can add a custom field for the group using the &amp;quot;Add a custom field&amp;quot; link.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Add a group to the folder selected</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select the folder by using the drop down box under the general contacts module.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminCategories.do</action>
<section>ViewActive</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Active Category Details</title>
<description>The four different levels for the &amp;quot;Active&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Draft&amp;quot; categories are displayed. The level1 has the category name, which is further classified into sub directories/levels. The level1 has the sublevel called level2 which in turn has sublevel called level3 and so on.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the list of categories displayed in level1 shows you its sub levels or sub-directories present in level2 and clicking on these in turn shows its subdirectories in level3 and so on.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select to display either the Active Categories or the Draft Categories by clicking on the tabs &amp;quot;Active Categories&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Draft Categories&amp;quot; respectively.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>AdminCategories.do</action>
<section>View</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Draft Category Details</title>
<description>The four different levels for the active and the draft categories are displayed. The level1 has the category name, which is further classified into sub directories/levels. The level1 has the sublevel called level2 which in turn has sublevel called level3 and so on. The draft categories can be edited and activated. The activated draft categories would be then reflected in the Active Categories list. The modified/updated draft category can also be reverted to its original state.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The activated list can be brought back / reverted to the active list by clicking the &amp;quot;Revert to Active List&amp;quot;.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can activate each level by using the &amp;quot;Activate now&amp;quot; button.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>In the draft categories you can edit your category using the edit button present at the bottom of each level.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>You can select to display either the Active Categories or the Draft Categories by clicking on the tabs &amp;quot;Active Categories&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Draft Categories&amp;quot; respectively.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the list of categories displayed in level1 shows you its sub-levels or sub-directories present in level2 and clicking on these in turn would shows their subdirectories in level3 and so on.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>InsertUserForm </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>UpdateUser</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>AddUser</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Users.do</action>
<section>UserDetails</section>
<subSection/>
<title>User Details</title>
<description>This form provides the administrator with more information about the user, namely information pertaining to the users login history and view points.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Modify&amp;quot; button in the &amp;quot;Details&amp;quot; tab provides a quick link that allows the users information to be modified without having to browse back to the previous window.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Employee Link&amp;quot; in the 'Primary Information&amp;quot; table header provides a quick link to view the user's contact information.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Details&amp;quot; tab displays the information about the user in a non-editable format.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The &amp;quot;Disable&amp;quot; button provides a quick link to disable/inactivate the user.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Roles.do</action>
<section>ListRoles </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>InsertViewpoint </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Viewpoints.do</action>
<section>InsertViewpoint</section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Admin.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Overview</title>
<description>You are looking at the Admin module home page. Here you can manage the system by reviewing its usage, configuring specific modules and system parameters.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>The user and module section allows the administrator to manage users, roles, role hierarchy and manage modules.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The global parameters and server configuration module allows the administrator to set the session timeout parameter.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The usage section allows the administrator to view the total number of users, memory used, and system usage parameters for various time intervals.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The administration module is divided into distinct categories such as managing users, module configuration, setting global parameters, server configuration and monitoring system usage and resources.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Auto Guide" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>Auto Guide Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>Auto Guide Detail</detailDescription>
</module>
<module name="Help" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>Help Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>Help Detail</detailDescription>
</module>
<module name="Demo" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>Demo Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>Demo Detail</detailDescription>
</module>
<module name="System" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>System Brief</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>System Detail</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Search.do</action>
<section>SiteSearch </section>
<subSection/>
<title/>
<description/>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>Search.do</action>
<section>SiteSearch</section>
<subSection/>
<title>General Search</title>
<description>You can search the system for data associated with a particular key term. This can be done using the search data text box present on the left side of the window. The data associated with the corresponding key term is looked for in different modules for a match and the results are displayed per module. The search results are shown with detail description.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Clicking on the different links of the search results will direct you to the corresponding details in the modules.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Product Catalog" contentLevel="0">
<briefDescription>Brief description for product catalog</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>detail description for product catalog</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProductsCatalog.do</action>
<section>ListAllProducts</section>
<subSection/>
<title>a</title>
<description>b</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
<module name="Projects" contentLevel="2">
<briefDescription>The Project management module allows individuals and organizations to share up-to-the-minute information with others. Whether you are sharing information with employees, clients, vendors, friends, and family, the information is easily and securely accessible.</briefDescription>
<detailDescription>Project detail description</detailDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section/>
<subSection/>
<title>Dashboard</title>
<description>This page provides a snap shot of all recent items (of the last 7 days) of all the projects that a you are a member of.&#13;
&#13;
By changing the filter, you can choose to view information over a longer time period (14 days or 30 days), or a shorter time period(24hrs or 48hrs.)&#13;
&#13;
The menu allows you to add a project, search for information in projects, list existing projects, and view invitations to join projects
</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>AddProject</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Project</title>
<description>This page allows you to create a new project.&#13;
&#13;
The following fields are requested: &#13;
1. Title -  A brief name for your project.&#13;
2. Short Description -  A brief description for your project&#13;
3. Start Date - The date in which the project started or will start 4. Estimated End Date  - The date in which you believe the project will be finished .&#13;
5. Requested By -  The name of a person that may have initiated the reason for the project; could be the name of a client.&#13;
6. Organization - The organization that may have initiated the reason for the project; could be the name of a company.&#13;
7. Budget  - A high-level view of the project budget; this figure generally is an estimate.&#13;
8. Status - Specifies whether the project has been approved or if it is closed (finished.)&#13;
&#13;
Once the fields have been successfully submitted, a new project is created. You should see the name of the project you created and several tabs underneath that will contain all the information for your project.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>RSVP</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Invitations</title>
<description>This page displays the projects to which you have been invited to.  By accepting an invitation, you become a team member of the project and assume a role (applicable to this project alone) assigned by the owner (or creator) of the project.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagementSearch.do</action>
<section>ShowForm</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Search</title>
<description>This page allows you to search for items in a project based on the search item. For advanced search options, you may click on the &amp;quot;tips&amp;quot; link.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Details</subSection>
<title>Project Details</title>
<description>This view displays information about a project.&#13;
&#13;
The General Information section displays the project status, the title (also the project name), a description, the budget and relevant dates (start date, entered, modified and estimated close date)   for the project.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Setup Project Module</subSection>
<title>Setup</title>
<description>Within the  Setup  tab you also have the choice to  either &amp;quot;Configure Permissions&amp;quot; or &amp;quot;Customize Project&amp;quot;  for this project. &#13;
&#13;
Configuring Permissions allows you to define what members of your project can be allowed to view, add, change, or delete.&#13;
&#13;
Customizing the project allows you to show(or hide) the tabs and change the tab names according to your preferences.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>CustomizeProject</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Customize Project Module</title>
<description>This &amp;quot;Customize Project&amp;quot; view allows you to change the names for each of the project subtabs. Changing the names of the tabs does not change any of the existing functionality for that tab.&#13;
&#13;
It also allows you to turn off the subtabs based on your preferences.  Turning tabs off can be helpful if you do not intend to have any information under that tab. Making things simple for your team members certainly helps to streamline the usage of your project.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ConfigurePermissions</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Configure Permissions</title>
<description>The &amp;quot;Configure Permissions&amp;quot;  screen shows you a list of all permissions that can be adjusted in your project. Each tab is represented and has a variety of permissions that can be adjusted.&#13;
&#13;
For example, the first group is entitled,  Project Details,  which contains three permissions that can be adjusted:&#13;
1. View project details   defines which role(s) can view the project  Details  tab.&#13;
2. Modify project details   defines which role(s) can modify the information on the project  Details  tab.&#13;
3. Delete project   defines which role(s) can permanently delete this project&#13;
&#13;
The screen also allows you to define what members of your project can be allowed to view, add, change, or delete. Later on, when you add users to your project, you will need to know the answer to  what will each user be able to access in my project?</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Users can be assigned one of the following roles, namely, Guest, Observer, Contributor and Project Lead. The Guest role is the least privileged role in a project and the Project Lead role is the most privileged role.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When a role is allowed a permission, the permission is also available to more privileged roles. For e.g., if a the permission &amp;quot;View project details&amp;quot; is allowed for the &amp;quot;Guest&amp;quot;, all superior roles namely, Observer, Contributor and Project Lead also inherit this permission. Similarly, if the &amp;quot;Modify Project Details&amp;quot; is assigned to &amp;quot;Project Lead&amp;quot; no other role inherits this privilege as the &amp;quot;Project Lead&amp;quot; role is the most superior (as in most privileged) role among preconfigured roles in the projects module.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>News</subSection>
<title>News</title>
<description>News articles are essentially bits of news that you can add to your project for others to review. Others can also add news items if you provide them access.&#13;
&#13;
To add a news article, select the  Add News Article  link. You will be presented with a form with fields that allow you to describe the news item.&#13;
&#13;
You can also filter the list of news items you want listed based on prec-configured criterias namely &amp;quot;Current News,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Archived News,&amp;quot; &amp;quot;Unreleased News,&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;New Drafts.&amp;quot;</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>ProjectManagementNews.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add News</title>
<description>This screen allows you to add a news item.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page contains the following fields</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Status: Determines whether the article is shown when users view news articles; there are three possible choices: a) Draft if you are not finished with composing the article, choose Draft and you can finish the article later; even though you will see this article in your Current News list, other users will not unless they have access to to view Draft  articles b)Unapproved if you are finished, but would like the article to be approved before allowing others to view, choose Unapproved; even though you will see this article in your Current News list, others will not unless they have access to view Unapproved  articles c)Published indicates that the article is finished, approved, and ready to be seen by other users.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Position: Articles are typically displayed in the list by the most recent date first; if you would like certain articles to appear before others, no matter what their date is set to, then you can group them by position in which lower numbered articles always appear before higher numbered articles; by default 10 is used for all articles, so a number of 1-9 would appear before 10.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Start Date/Time: The specific date and time in which the article should be allowed to be viewed; prior to this time, only users who can see unreleased articles have access to this article; when the date/time occurs, the article will automatically be visible in Current News for the rest of the users in your project with access to the News Article list.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Archive Date/Time: The specific date and time in which the article should automatically be archived from the default view; users who have access to archived articles will be able to review these.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Subject: Each article needs a headline that gets displayed.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Intro: Each article can have an unlimited amount of text, however you might want to have an introduction to the article and require that the user choose to read any additional pages by selecting a  read more  link that appears when an article has an additional page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Once you have finished your news article, and have completed the fields, choose to  Save  the article. If you would like to add an additional page to the article, choose  Save and Add a Page.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Viewing the  News  tab will now show your article.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Team</subSection>
<title>Team</title>
<description>Lists the currently added team members and some information about them. You will always be added when you create a new project.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="0">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Setup</title>
<description>Within the  Setup  tab you also have the choice to  Configure Permissions  for this project. Permissions allow you to define what members of your project can be allowed to view, add, change, or delete.&#13;
&#13;
To setup team members, choose the  Modify Team  link. At this point you will now have a page with four (4) lists, some of which are empty. The right most list shows you the team members of your project. The left most list shows you ways in which you can add a team member.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>ProjectManagementTeam.do</action>
<section>Modify</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Manage Team</title>
<description>This page allows you to modify (add and remove) members from the project team.&#13;
&#13;
This page shows you four (4) lists, some of which are empty. The right most list shows you the team members of your project. The left most list shows you ways in which you can add a team member.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>Team members can be invited from: 1. Open projects   if you have existing projects, that are open, then you can begin by adding contacts from your open projects 2. Closed projects   if you have existing projects, that have been closed, then you can begin by adding contacts from a closed project 3. Email address   if the contact is not listed in one of your projects, then you can invite them by their email address.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>The first list allows you to choose a method for inviting your contact. Depending on your choice, you will either be asked to choose a project in which to select a contact from, or you will be asked to input an email address. When you have selected a contact, make sure they show up in the right most list before continuing.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>To remove a team member from your project, simply select them in the right column and they will be removed when the team is updated.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When you are finished modifying the team, choose  Update Team  to finalize the changes. If you added a contact by email address, and the CRM application is not familiar with that address, then you will be asked if you are certain you would like to invite them to the project. Choosing  Yes  will require that you input their first and last name.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When contacts are added to a project, whether they are users (have accounts) of CRM or not, each contact will be sent an email inviting them to your project.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When you return to the list of users, you can modify their role in the project by using the drop-down menu next to their name. As soon as the drop-down is changed, the system immediately updates the user's role.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>All added team members are initially identified as  invited.  This means that you would like them to be on this project, but the contact will need to be informed of this action and asked to accept the invitation. If the contact does not have an account, then they will receive an email that allows them to easily obtain an account before accepting your invitation.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Issues_Categories</subSection>
<title>Discussion</title>
<description>While news articles provide a formal way to announce and disseminate project happenings, discussion groups allow for more informal camaraderie and collaboration.&#13;
&#13;
Discussion groups are comprised of forums, topics and messages.&#13;
&#13;
Forums provide some sort of categorization among what is being discussed. For example, you might have forums for  Suggestions,   Status Reports  and  Resources.  Small projects might have just one forum, while larger projects may require multiple forums.&#13;
&#13;
Once a forum has been created, it's time to create a topic for discussion. A topic is simply a subject and a message. Forums can have multiple topics in which users can reply to and comment on.&#13;
&#13;
Once a topic has been posted, other team members can reply.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>File_Library</subSection>
<title>Documents</title>
<description>The Projects module comes with a sophisticated document management tool. You can use it to store versions of documents in a hierarchy of folders. When you select the  Documents  tab you are presented with a list of folders and files that belong to the project.&#13;
&#13;
To create a folder, select the  New Folder  link. To store a file, select the  Submit File  link. When uploading a file you can specify a subject for the file that gets displayed in the list. You can store documents at the top level, or you can navigate into any available folder and then store a file there.&#13;
&#13;
Once a file exists in the document library, you will see it appear in the list. By choosing the  Select  button next to the file, you are presented with several options,namely&#13;
&#13;
1. View File History:  Viewing the file's history shows the versions that exist for a file and how many times each version has been downloaded.&#13;
2. Download File:  This will begin downloading the file to your computer.&#13;
3. View File Contents:  The file will be displayed in a popup window; only certain types can be displayed, for example PDF, Excel, HTML, Text, and Word documents.&#13;
4. Rename File:  This will allow you to modify the subject of a file.&#13;
5. Add Version: This allows you to upload a new version to an existing document; the existing file will not be altered and can be downloaded or deleted separately; version numbers can be indicated as: (a) Major -  Generally a substantial amount of content has    been added or modified (b) Minor -  Generally some amount of content has been added or modified (c) Changes - Generally a small amount of content has been added or modified.&#13;
6. Move File:   This allows you to move the file to another folder.&#13;
7. Delete File:  This will delete the file and all versions of the file; to delete just a version of the file.&#13;
You can choose the  View File History  link for additional options</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Lists_Categories</subSection>
<title>Lists</title>
<description>Lists allow you to place items on a list that you can mark as incomplete or complete.&#13;
&#13;
Projects can have any number of lists and each list can have any number of items. An item on the list can also have a memo area if necessary.&#13;
&#13;
Lists are good for jotting down related items to be referenced later. While to-do items can be added to the list and checked off, they can also be done in the  Plan  or  Tickets  tabs.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Requirements</subSection>
<title>Project Plan</title>
<description>The plan tab is perhaps the most functionally rich feature of the projects module.&#13;
&#13;
Plans can be used for creating a high-level view of project milestones or objectives and then proceeding to low-level details.&#13;
&#13;
1. Start with an outline. Outlines can be used to organize objectives for the project. To create a new outline, click the  &amp;quot;New Outline&amp;quot; link. You are presented a number of fields that allow you to describe all the information for the outline.&#13;
&#13;
2. Detail the outline with activities and assignments.</description>
<features>
<featureDescription>This page lists all the project plans. Each item in the list provides a snapshot of the outline including the outline's start date, the start date, the description and status, the progress made in completing the items of the outline and the effort expended in completing the items of the outline.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>Using the drop list as a filter you can choose to view only open outlines, only closed outlines or view all outlines.</featureDescription>
<featureDescription>When you click on the select option, you are presented with a choice view, edit or delete the outline.</featureDescription>
</features>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>ProjectManagementRequirements.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Outline</title>
<description>This page allows you to add an outline. Listed below is a description of the fields shown in this screen.&#13;
&#13;
a) Title  - a project milestone to be displayed.&#13;
b) Requested By -  The name of a person that may have initiated the reason for the milestone; could be the name of a client.&#13;
c) Department or Company - The organization that may have initiated the reason for the milestone; could be the name of a company.&#13;
d) Expected Dates - The date in which the milestone is expected to begin and the date in which the milestone is expected to be completed on.&#13;
e) Level of Effort  - An estimate as to how much time this milestone could take, and a field for how long the milestone actual took.&#13;
f) Status -  Indicates whether the outline is approved and/or closed (complete.)&#13;
g) Details - Text describing the goals of this outline&#13;
&#13;
When all required fields of the screen are entered, you can save the outline. The saved outline appears in the outline list.&#13;
&#13;
Once you create the outline, the next task would be to elaborate the outline with activities and assignments.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Assignments</subSection>
<title>Plan Outline</title>
<description>This page allows you to view outline details, add activities, and activity folders&#13;
&#13;
When you click on  the name of the outline, a drop-down menu appears with the option to &#13;
a) Add Activity Folder &#13;
b) Add Activity &#13;
&#13;
An Activity Folder allows you to create sections in your outline. This can be useful when you are building the outline and haven't yet decided how to group Activities.&#13;
&#13;
Activities are specific items to be completed toward this project objective or&#13;
milestone.&#13;
&#13;
Activities have several fields: &#13;
a) Description - A specific task to be completed; this will be displayed on the outline. &#13;
b) Indent Level  - since the outline is hierarchical, each item on the outline can be moved to the left or right; by selecting the left/right arrows the indent level will increase and decrease; items with a higher number then the item above will appear indented.&#13;
c) Priority - Indicates the importance of this activity; there are three (3) options: A Low, A Normal (default,) A High.&#13;
d) Assigned To  - The activity can be assigned to any member of the project.&#13;
e) Status -  Describes the state of this activity; there are six (6) options: &#13;
  (i)A Not Started&#13;
  (ii)A In Progress&#13;
  (iii)A Complete&#13;
  (iv)A Closed  - Similar to complete, but used when the activity    may no longer be necessary and the item was not completed.&#13;
  (v) A On Hold -  Indicates that this activity is waiting on some other factor; for example, another activity needs to be completed before this one.&#13;
  (vi)A Waiting on Requirements - Indicates that more information is needed in order to complete this activity.&#13;
f) Keywords -  additional words to keep track of activities; for example, maybe the expected output of this activity: Excel, Java, Press Release, etc.; a future version of the software might allow for searching keywords.&#13;
g) Level of Effort -  The estimated time it should take for this activity to be completed; an additional field is used to record the actual time this activity took.&#13;
h) Due Date  - The date in which this activity should be completed by.&#13;
&#13;
When all of the information on the activity has been recorded, choose  Save  or  Save &amp; New.   Save  will simply record the activity, and refresh the outline.  Save &amp; New  will record the activity, refresh the outline, and then provide another form to continue adding activities.&#13;
&#13;
Once an activity is in the list, you can select the activity from the list and a menu will appear with the following options: &#13;
a) Arrow buttons -  The arrows allow you to move this Activity item up and down the list, or indent the activity to the left and right.&#13;
b) Add Activity Folder - Adds an Activity Folder below this Activity.&#13;
c) Add Activity -  Adds another Activity below this one.&#13;
d) View/Update this Activity - Depending on your permissions, and whether the activity is assigned to you, you can modify the activity, otherwise you can only view the activity without making changes.&#13;
e) Delete Activity</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="3">
<action>ProjectManagement.do</action>
<section>ProjectCenter</section>
<subSection>Tickets</subSection>
<title>Tickets</title>
<description>Once the project gets going, you might run into some unexpected issues that need to be recorded and resolved. The  Tickets  tab is a good place to capture these.&#13;
&#13;
This page displays a list of tickets for this project. Each item in the list gives a snapshot of the information of the ticket.&#13;
&#13;
The list can be filtered to view only the open tickets, only the closed tickets or to view all tickets.&#13;
&#13;
The snapshot includes, the ticket Id, the status, the ticket issue (only partially displayed if it is elaborate,) the priority, the team member it was assigned to, the age of ticket and when the ticket was last modified.&#13;
&#13;
The displayed list can be sorted based on all the underlined column headers of the list.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
<pageDescription contentLevel="4">
<action>ProjectManagementTickets.do</action>
<section>Add</section>
<subSection/>
<title>Add Ticket</title>
<description>Tickets  are issues that can be assigned to a team member. A ticket has the following fields:&#13;
1. Issue  - The complete issue that has come up; this can be a request for information or a problem that has occurred, be specific without adding comments.&#13;
2. Severity -  Describes the impact on the project using one of three (3) choices: (a) Normal (b) Important (c) Critical &#13;
3. Priority -  Describes when the issue should be resolved, possibly ahead of other issues; there are three (3) choices: &#13;
(a) Scheduled -  The team member assigned should schedule this issue and take care of it when convenient. &#13;
(b) Next  - The team member assigned should take care of this issue ahead of other lower priority items. &#13;
(c) Immediate  - The team member assigned should take care of this issue right away, typically because the impact is severe.&#13;
4. Assign To -  The team member that has been assigned this ticket.&#13;
5. User Comments -  Any additional comments to provide that are not part of the issue; a ticket can have any number of comments; each comment is dated and attributed to the user that made a comment and can later be seen in the ticket history.&#13;
6. Solution - A description of how this ticket was resolved.&#13;
7. Close Ticket   Indicates whether this ticket is complete and needs no further action.&#13;
&#13;
Once a ticket has been added, its details can be reviewed. A ticket also has a history in which you can see the progress or escalation that has occurred with the ticket. Once a ticket has been closed, it can be re-opened later, if necessary.</description>
<features/>
<notes/>
<rules/>
<tips/>
</pageDescription>
</module>
</helpSystem>
